[This drama is fictional and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
It was two lines.
That day.
That night, that man.
[Chapter 1 Fateful Encounter]
[4 Weeks Ago]
[Episode 1]
Hui Won, did you get in safely?
Of course. All thanks to someone
personally putting a wig on me.
Sorry, you know how my dad is.
He acts like his life goal
is marrying his daughter off well.
He can't stand seeing me skip events.
He knows this place is basically
a solo party for the young and rich.
Anyway, don't worry about me.
Just go enjoy your favorite concert.
Whether in college or now,
you go crazy for MeloMance.
They're so sweet.
Sweetness is poison to me.
Hey, why don't you look around
for a decent guy yourself?
- Let's end your lifelong singlehood.
- Ugh, no thanks.
I'll just have a beer and leave.
Excuse me...
Hold on, I'll call you back later.
- Yes?
- We're running a survey for a company event.
'Cherry Blossom Wedding' is
the concept. Want to join?
[Marriage Fantasy Test]
A world where marriage is
a choice, not a requirement.
If someone asks me about marriage...
Choose when you dream of getting married?
[Immediately, if I'm ready;
After becoming financially stable]
[After achieving my goals;
When my partner seems ready]
[When I don't want to
be apart from them; Other]
I can say for sure.
I won't get married in this lifetime.
[In the next life]
[Team Leader Bang]
Yes, Team Leader Bang.
Does yesterday's PPT
include the Q4 work plan?
Weren't we supposed to add that
at the end of the month?
We need it for Monday's team leader meeting.
So, revise it and email it to me by tomorrow.
By tomorrow?
Yeah, I've got something urgent today. Sorry.
Thank you.
Wow, so many good-looking men here!
Having a good cousin really pays off.
Why is Team Leader Bang here...
Could she be starting strange rumors at work?
Excuse me, could you back me up?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
My darling, even your smile is adorable.
Oh, dear.
[Chapter 2 Coincidence]
Oh, Du Jun.
Hello.
Well, look who's early...
No, I should be formal here, Director.
Cut it out. No need between us.
Ah, I see all the sons and daughters
from J Land, Sangwoo Electronics,
and Semo Corporation are present.
Go on, go greet them too.
There must be friends you met
while studying abroad, right?
That's exactly why I'm avoiding them.
Just 30 minutes. I'll leave
in exactly 30 minutes.
Since when do you last 30 minutes?
If I can endure just 30 minutes,
then she'll never
bring up the blind dates again...
- Why?
- A big catch!
Looks like you got tricked by her again.
Tricked? So, you need to handle this well.
You're here as a witness.
I wondered why you invited me.
You...
What?
As your secretary,
I must be an excellent witness.
Stop looking at me like that. It's stressful.
Don't you know I get a sensitive
stomach when I'm stressed?
If you don't know... oh, no.
Nature's calling. Bathroom...
You can stay here by yourself, right?
Bathroom...
Where are you going alone?
You've gotten so much more attractive.
Maybe, you should make a move on...
I'm not sure what I'm here for.
Excuse me, could you back me up?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
My darling, even your smile is adorable.
Oh, dear.
What are you doing right now?
How is your skin so baby-soft?
What? You're hungry?
Shall we go get something
delicious over there?
- Oh.
- I said what are you doing?
Well... the thing is...
Huh?
Your cheeks are red.
Oh, I'll go get you something cool.
No, hey, wait...
Here's grape juice...
Oh!
Oh, no.
Are you okay?
Oh no, oh no.
- Napkin, napkin!
- Stop it.
I'll just go to the restroom
and bring it right back.
Enough!
[Chapter 3 Inevitability]
Wow, I never thought I'd see Kang Du Jun
wearing this kind of outfit.
Seriously, this is all
the clothes you've got?
And why on earth do you
have this silly outfit in your car?
My oldest nephew bought it for me.
Let's not bring family into this.
Well, I heard this kind of silly outfit
is trending these days.
Geez, that woman has some nerve.
She actually got Kang Du Jun
all worked up and ran off.
Never bring that up in front of me again.
It just came back to me.
Ah, sorry.
But, it hasn't even been 30 minutes.
It's okay to leave now, right?
You expect me to stay like this
for another 20 minutes?
Right, I wouldn't last there either.
But seriously, why don't you
want to get married?
Don't tell me you're weighing
marriage efficiency or something?
Why wouldn't I?
Think of the time and cost spent dating,
dining, and having coffee.
Plus all that unnecessary emotional labor
you'd have to endure.
When I'm already short on work hours
and stealing from sleep,
why invest in such inefficiency?
Alright, I get it.
Convince your mom efficiently on your own.
Yellow tee.
This is hilarious.
Enough!
Oh, my.
So? You just ran away like that?
Ugh, I don't know.
When I came back with tissues
and dry-cleaning money, he was already gone.
Am I going to get sued?
Ah, would he really go that far?
Ah, who knew I'd run into my boss there?
True, thinking about seeing
them at work... ugh!
Seriously creepy.
I didn't want Team Leader Bang to see me,
so I pulled all kinds of stunts
with a total stranger.
Does he really think I've lost my mind?
Yeah, the odds are definitely high.
But what does he look like? Handsome?
I don't know. He had sunglasses on,
couldn't really see.
Ah, what a waste.
It's not about getting splashed
by grape juice. You should've locked eyes.
Oh, what are you saying?
Oh gosh,
here comes Miss Prim again.
From what I see,
your rigid walls ruined an entire
truckload of potential romance.
Hey, what walls did I even put up?
Hey, don't you remember?
[Ten years ago]
- Why? What?
- Oh my.
- What are you touching right now?
- Oh, hey.
Every guy who tried flirting
with you eventually gave up.
That's because they tried
to rush things way too fast.
Hui Won, you need to
drop that old-fashioned idea
that you must 'take it slow'
when seeing someone.
If the vibe's right,
you can get everything done
in half a day.
Hey.
You're only against marriage,
not dating, right?
Of course, I'll date.
I even have someone I like.
Oh you? Who?
There is. Don't be surprised later
when you see how handsome he is.
Alrighty then, okay.
Drink up. Let's drink ourselves
to death tonight.
Hey, you're paying for everything
here tonight, okay?
Cheers!
Ah, this is so funny.
Oh.
I had such a rough day today, seriously.
Sir, give me a bottle of Try...
No, no, make it two bottles, please.
Cheers.
- You're going down tonight.
- I'm gonna beat you today.
- No sipping!
- I finished it all.
Sad?
Huh? I'm not drunk.
- You know, I'm usually super cool, right?
- It's not that, seriously.
- Three, six, nine. Three, six, nine!
- Bang!
Drunk?
Wake up. Time for round two.
Sir, another bottle of Try here, please.
So then, he suddenly disappeared?
Got it for now.
Oh, my head...
See?
I told you I should go keep an eye on him.
You know that blind date the other day?
He set Chae Yeon's childhood pictures
as his phone wallpaper
and even pretended to be her father.
Oh, my head...
I had to explain that mess...
He's that desperate not to get married,
so let's give him some time.
You calm down too.
Jeong Eum will be here soon.
How could I possibly calm down?
Do you think I don't know
how the board's been itching to tear
Du Jun apart ever since your sabbatical?
- I'll try to handle that...
- Oh, dear.
How exactly?
Like last time, when everything blew up,
and you only showed up to clean the mess?
He's not acting this way for no reason.
It's that pointless
sense of responsibility of his.
From what I see, Jeong Eum must be
pressuring Du Jun somehow...
Pressuring him how?
Oh? You're here.
Sit here.
Se Hyeon has plans?
Yes.
Oh.
Let's continue the conversation
you two were having.
I love talking about myself.
Oh.
Well, since Du Jun
keeps avoiding blind dates
and refuses to get married...
Is marriage really necessary?
It's not like marriage guarantees
you won't end up alone.
Just like me.
Excuse me for a moment.
Yeah, I'm with my in-laws.
Mr. Lee?
Has that punk lost his mind?
Tell him to get out.
Show him what happens
when he stabs me in the back.
Sorry, it's work-related.
Oh, yes.
It's okay.
But seriously, why don't you
want to get married?
I can't.
I said I can't do it.
No! No!
How could I dare think of marriage,
after destroying a family with my own hands?
[Beer]
[It's Beer Time]
Fourteen bottles of beer?
See? She didn't become
the youngest manager for nothing.
What, did she even brag about proving it?
Even without that, the Germany slot
is obviously Manager Jang's.
Germany?
Guess you haven't heard, Se Hyeon.
Every three years, the company
picks top-performing employees
for a study program in Germany.
But competition's insane these days,
so rumor is they're even
scoring creativity now.
Still, who could possibly beat Manager Jang?
I've never seen anyone so relentless
in new product development.
She heard minerals were
used in medicine and cosmetics
and went mining for ones
that could work in beer.
That's not all. She planned
limited-edition beer with rare fruit
and went trekking through jungles.
Wow, is she some kind of Tarzan?
Last month, for some special Himalayan yeast,
she was scaling ice walls...
Manager Nam In Nam?
You went around calling me
Tarzan again, didn't you?
Because of you, there are all
these weird rumors going around.
Did I say anything that wasn't true?
Just exaggerated a tiny bit.
A tiny bit? About...
- 70%?
- Assistant Manager Choi.
It just shows Manager Jang's
unmatched role
in our New Product Development Team.
Our ace.
Absolutely, you are my role model.
I'm telling the truth.
- Hey quiet now.
- Shut it.
What? Why did everyone
suddenly stop laughing?
Conference room. Now.
No ideas at all?
You, intern.
- Yes?
- Got any brilliant ideas?
They say Gen Z these days
come up with fresh, creative ideas,
but I guess not all of them do.
You must've learned something in a month.
Didn't your supervisor teach you anything?
Just scold me already.
I think that's what you wanted to say to me.
Fine, you talk well.
Now, show me what you've got.
Set an example as a senior.
You think you can just sit back
now that Germany's basically a done deal?
I suppose that's smarter than getting
involved and docking your own score.
So, I just need to bring it
by the next meeting, right?
A groundbreaking idea to boost beer sales?
So, you went head-to-head
with your boss again?
I worked all weekend because of her,
and now she's messing with my junior.
Why's she always obsessed
with taking me down?
Because a junior who's better
than her keeps threatening her turf.
She blames you for last year's
failed promotion, right?
No, that was
because she tried to claim
our team's all-nighter as her work.
Anyway, I stormed out in anger earlier,
but where do I find such an idea?
Took a while to find.
You were a handful in middle school,
and you still are.
[14 years ago]
[Cha Min Uk]
At this point, you owe your knees an apology.
It hurts.
Stop whining.
Here too.
Are you okay?
Had a blind date over the weekend?
Did Mi Ran say that?
No, I was hoping the three of us
could grab a drink after so long.
But she said you have a very important date.
No, it's not that. Not at all.
I thought maybe you'd finally
started thinking about marriage.
You know how my parents are.
Get out! Get out!
Why should I leave? This is my house!
Since when?
How could you do this to us?
Dad, Dad!
Dad, please don't go.
Dad.
Huh?
You still think your parents' divorce
was your fault?
So, why would anyone marry without love?
Even if it hadn't been Dad's affair,
they would've divorced anyway.
They weren't compatible.
When well-matched people meet,
they might go a lifetime without fighting.
Then, you...
Even if you meet someone
you truly love later, you won't marry?
Huh?
Never mind.
Why am I asking so much
to someone who prioritizes work?
I should go. The team leader called for me.
Ah, what? You said you'd help me
figure out the beer issue.
Don't overthink it.
Being overly cautious can be poison.
The path lies where you seek the answer.
Beer problems get solved at a pub.
I'll get going.
Hey.
I really have to go.
I became more careful because of you...
Oh.
What brings you here?
Hey.
Say hello to him.
This is Manager Song, a good friend of mine.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Manager Song.
Apologies, but I need to step out.
Please get straight to the point.
Huh?
Oh.
You remember the commercial
building project I mentioned before?
I was thinking of doing that
together with Manager Song.
I believe I addressed that last time.
There's already a qualified person for that.
More importantly, Q2 operating profits
for the resort business hit a historic low.
With your approval, Vice Chairman,
I'll reassign the lead.
Are you saying you'll fire Team Leader Park?
More like relocating the team
to a suitable position.
No, but still...
Team Leader Park has handled
the resort project since the beginning...
Compensation is repaid with results.
Not loyalty or diligence.
If there's nothing else, I'll take my leave.
I have a meeting.
That insolent little...
That's right, that's right.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're here.
Doing this at the office too?
Wrong question.
I can only do this at work.
Your mom would smack my back if she saw this.
That's right, that's right.
Mom's still really mad, huh?
She's always been like that.
[Finish]
That's right, yay!
[Mari]
I came in first place.
This game's great for relieving stress.
Still busy these days?
Rumor has it you're working like a warrior.
I'm just doing what needs to be done.
That gesture with your hand...
Never mind.
Ah, Du Jun, first you need
recognition from the board.
It seems Moo Young is trying
to shake up the board with this issue.
Now, hand over
the trading company affairs to me.
- Father.
- Instead, from now on,
you report to Taehan Liquor.
As president, not managing director.
With spicy greasy food, lagers
completely lose their flavor and aroma.
'You're better off with something aromatic.'
'Stout works well, IPA's fine too.'
I want to tell them that.
But I should hold back, right?
Do you know him?
Huh? No, nothing.
Boyfriend?
Ugh, your face turned bright red.
He's a bit older, but a total romantic.
Though whether it's 3 months or 30 years,
we'll have to live together to find out.
Live together?
Cohabitation. I firmly believe in
living together before marriage.
Well, true.
Breaking up is better than getting divorced.
You have a boyfriend, right, Manager?
Someone this perfect
can't possibly be single.
I'm dying to know.
What kind of unicorn is your boyfriend?
Unicorn?
Makes sense. I've never seen him.
Let's drink. Drink.
Here.
Cheers!
[Min Uk]
Did you get off work? Have you eaten?
I'm dying to know.
What kind of unicorn is your boyfriend?
When well-matched people meet,
they might go a lifetime without fighting.
Even if you meet someone
you truly love later, you won't marry?
Yeah, someone like Min Uk would be fine.
Ugh, what am I even thinking right now?
Get a grip.
[Did you get off work? Have you eaten?]
He should be off work by now.
Did he pass out from exhaustion?
I even bought tteokbokki
from his favorite spot.
But he's not answering.
It's only good for Hwang Mi Ran, then.
Why is she out there?
Cha Min Uk?
I told you about her, right? It's Mi Ran.
- Cheers!
I even have someone I like.
Oh you? Who?
You report to Taehan Liquor.
As president, not managing director.
Oh, no.
Why did it have to spill out like this?
[Chapter 4 Fate]
What?
Darn it.
Hey!
Come out here, please!
How could you do this to me, huh?
What did I do wrong?
Why are you treating me like this?
What? Is she drunk?
I'm sorry.
I'll compensate you however much you want.
You could've at least given me a heads-up.
How could you stab me in the back like this?
What's wrong with her?
I'm sorry.
Hey there.
Why is your tint so dark?
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing in there?
Hey!
Hey! Don't you dare drive away!
That crazy...
[Check: One million won]
Jeez.
Is... he an angel?
Suddenly telling me to buy
every type of beer? What now?
Whew, almost had a disaster today.
Goodness, is our director
going through puberty?
You're drinking beer
you normally wouldn't touch...
You just decided to run wild?
What are you talking about?
I was holding back before.
And now?
Because I need it now.
Have you ever had a drink with me
besides during study abroad?
Back then, I felt sorry for you
whining about having no friends.
Anyway, as of today, I'm stepping back from
the foundation and trading company.
What?
Once the handover is done, I'll
start at Taehan Liquor immediately.
No, wait. Suddenly?
Giving up something good
for gossip-filled Taehan Liquor...
Demand it confidently from the chairman.
Tell him you have something
you want to do! A dream!
Do I even have something like that?
Anyway, schedule me for
all liquor-related events going forward.
And make sure to clip every article
about competitors, got it?
- Got it.
- Why drink before finishing the work?
Huh?
What?
Just go.
Darn, I really want a drink.
I'm sending you because
you said you wanted a drink.
You know that Yellow beer launched in Korea?
The party's there today,
at the flagship store in Itaewon.
Just make a good impression
and capture the vibe of the place.
Come on!
[Yellow Beer]
Perfect timing.
I was craving a drink.
Ta-da!
Ah, mixing it like that ruins the flavor.
Jang Hui Won, calm down.
Just drink quietly and don't meddle today.
Calm down.
Drink, drink, drink.
Take it easy. Are you here to party?
So Du Jun's here to study, huh?
You go home first.
I'm not going home today.
No, I can't go home. I can't.
Want me to ban you from the office too?
Don't look at me like that.
I'm so stressed. Just seeing your face...
Don't you know I have a sensitive stomach?
I really have stomach trouble...
I've got the signal...
Gotta run to the bathroom.
- Here we go again.
- Jeez.
Bathroom! Bathroom!
Jeez, I should really need to
handle things alone next time.
Why does it taste like this?
Wait, that woman...
That crazy woman from back then.
Oh no, I could get in trouble.
- You scared me!
- What now, again?
Again? Do you know me?
No, I absolutely don't know you.
But isn't this a bit much?
What do you mean?
When pouring wheat beer,
tilt the glass at 45 degrees
and fill only 70%.
Then,
[Yeast]
you should pour in the rest
including the settled yeast
to deepen the flavor.
Finish it
with this caramel popcorn.
The sweet-salty combo
will balance the subtle bitterness.
How is it?
I'll take my leave then.
Are you some kind of
beer expert or something?
Pardon?
I want to know more.
[Stout, Dark Chocolate]
[Wheat Beer, Churros]
[IPA, Chicken Wings; Lager, Sausage]
So, how was my recommendation?
My nickname is Beer Master!
No, no, no.
Beer Legend!
Not sure about legend...
Hey!
But isn't this way too much?
Ah, this is nothing.
Now, the current high score is 340 points!
Any more participants
for the basketball game?
The prizes include
a premium home-brew beer maker
and a Love It doll.
Here you are, come on out, come on out.
A craft beer brewing machine.
I really want that.
- Shall I buy you one?
- Oh, never mind.
- No need to buy me one.
- Anyone coming?
Then, why not give it a shot?
Give it a shot? No way...
With your height, I bet you're
good at basketball.
Why do you push so hard?
Jeez.
Ah, this is too...
Oh no.
Oh no, this is too much!
Three, two, one!
So close. Oh, no.
- It's okay!
Any other challengers?
Here.
Today's final challenger.
Can he actually surpass 340 points?
Are you confident?
Not confident, but I'll try.
What's that supposed to mean?
'No confidence, but I'll try?'
Amazing confidence. Let's see.
He's got an actor's face.
Alright, let's start.
340 points.
Starting now.
I'm nervous.
Why's he taking his jacket off
for basketball?
It's just uncomfortable.
Now, we're extremely uncomfortable too.
Why roll up sleeves now?
- It's just a basketball game...
- Also uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable? Seriously?
You're making everyone uncomfortable.
If you don't beat 340 after this,
it'll be truly awkward.
Cool.
- Go for it!
- Let's start.
[Hunt for the Scoring King]
[Highest Score, Time, Total Score]
What?
Seven seconds left.
[Highest Score, Time, Total Score]
Six, five, four, three,
[Challenge Failed]
two, one.
Yes!
- That was close.
- Wait!
They cheated over there.
They just blinded me.
Blinded what?
They used phone flash to blind me.
That's cheating! Fraud!
No, I didn't.
Did you blind him with flash?
No, no, not at all.
- No.
- Not true.
He doesn't even have a phone!
Handsome guys get away with anything?
[Highest Score 340, Time 0, Total Score 339]
Games are games, and scores are scores.
Machines don't lie.
The one who scored 340
is our winner.
Here's your prize.
I can't just let myself be pushed around.
How fast are you?
- Run on three.
- Wow, it's big.
- Three!
- Oh, wait.
Hurry up.
Ah, so tired.
I can't run anymore.
They're not chasing us now.
But how could you think of
running off with the prize?
It was originally mine anyway.
He's the one who stole it!
But why is this beer maker so light?
- What is this?
- Oh?
You're more clumsy than you look.
Forget it. I let it slide because
your effort was admirable.
Aren't you thirsty?
Anyway, after coming back from the trip,
I kept searching for that flavor.
That's when I made up my mind.
I've decided that I must
study in Germany next.
I've decided to create my own beer
that will captivate foreigners' taste buds.
That's my dream.
You like drinking, have a lot you want to do,
and are full of passion.
I'm passionate, but I lack courage,
so I guess I borrow strength from alcohol.
What about you? What's your dream?
I don't have anything like that.
You don't have anything you want to do?
Do I have to have one?
Just handling my responsibilities
is overwhelming enough.
You live so rigidly.
Are you a perfectionist, something like that?
Well, I guess if a person ever loosens up,
all that happens is mistakes.
How does a person like that
even drink alcohol?
So, I usually don't drink much.
Don't you know this is like an oxygen tank?
Did you know?
Some of the most beloved beers in history
were created by accident or mistake.
This lager
was created by accident
when beer was aged in a cold cave.
If you live too intensely,
you can easily miss
the unexpected moments that come along.
What's so great about having a dream?
Being composed in the face
of mistakes is also a dream.
Then, is this also a mistake?
[Chapter 5 Destiny]
I must be crazy.
Do people usually pay when they leave?
Did I do it when I came in?
If it shows that it's my first time,
it'll be embarrassing.
Right,
[Check: One million won]
this money wasn't really mine from the start.
Goodbye, my money.
What?
Married man? Girlfriend?
Oh my, the ladies are here?
Mrs. Park, I didn't know you were
interested in sponsorship projects like this.
He's sparkling and pretty, isn't he?
Please spread the word a lot.
Say he's an artist with a bright future.
Isn't he the one Taehan Hotel sponsored?
Really?
If President Han finds out,
she won't stay quiet.
Is there anything
money can't solve?
President Han?
Mr. Lee, it's been a while.
You've gotten even prettier
since I last saw you.
Oh, ma'am.
In a world where practicality rules,
loyalty is old-fashioned.
Well done. I'm impressed.
President Han.
Mr. Lee is mine now.
What are you doing, getting all clingy now?
I'm not here to take him away.
I'm not interested in everyone's sweetheart,
but I came to tell you
your calculation is off.
Did you underpay a penalty?
No, no.
President Han!
Now, the calculation is a bit more accurate.
Ugh, my head...
[Check: One million won]
What is this?
This woman is ridiculous.
How can she
just throw the doll away like that?
That's too much.
[Si Hyeong]
- Hey.
- Finally answering.
I thought something happened to you.
- What?
- Do you know how many times I called?
You're a light sleeper.
What on earth happened?
What are you talking about?
I never got any calls...
[Si Hyeong (10)]
What? I slept this deeply?
You said you'd let Mr. Lee go.
- I did let him go.
- But you caused a ruckus.
I said I'd let him go, but I never said
I'd give him away to someone else.
If word gets out about this...
Secretary Yoon.
What brings you here?
Do I have to answer?
You're not here to see me, huh?
Okay, I get what you mean.
Are you sure you have
no plans to get married?
Your mother keeps worrying about you.
But you have no intention to do so at all.
Isn't that right?
[15 years ago]
You ruined my life!
How are you going to take
responsibility for this?
How?
I thought he only worked,
but apparently he does everything.
Find out who was with him.
Yes.
I'm crazy, I'm crazy.
What on earth was I thinking with a stranger?
But that necklace looked
like a gift for a woman.
Could he be married?
Ah, I'm going crazy, I'm losing my mind!
Manager Jang.
They say your proposal got approved.
I mean, that logo placement!
According to Manager Jang,
raising the logo placement on the glass
increases the amount of beer and soju poured.
If sales increase,
management won't object much.
First, we'll produce a small batch
with the new print,
and distribute 50 glasses to each partner.
Everyone, get ready.
Right, Manager Jang,
finalize the proposal details,
including estimated development costs,
and submit it by next week.
Talk to the procurement team,
and get the schedules
from the beer glass manufacturer
and the printing company too.
Yes.
We'll help too.
Right, just tell us what to do.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
That's when I made up my mind.
I've decided that I must
study in Germany next.
I've decided to create my own beer
that will captivate foreigners' taste buds.
That's my dream.
[Day 1, 2, 3]
[Day 3, 4, 5]
I think it's better to raise it
just this subtly.
We could even name it specifically
for soju-and-beer mixes.
The 'Try' Golden Ratio Glass.
Alright, cheers! Cheers!
Cheers!
[Day 5, 6, 7]
Try!
How is the change
of resort project manager going?
Well, the Vice Chairman said he wants
to give Team Leader Park another chance...
This project is so important to us. Are you
still looking for loyalty over capability?
Find a competent person to handle it,
before I leave.
- Move on, please.
- At the Jeju resort,
they plan to include locally crafted
brewery products in the room packages.
A craft beer brewing machine.
I really want that.
Shall I buy you one?
Hey!
President.
They also plan to release
a separate beer set.
Yes, that sounds good.
It connects with the local community.
Let's extend the duration by about a week.
[Day 7, 8, 9]
Next.
Over here, please put it on the desk.
Thank you.
[Day 9, 10, 11]
When pouring wheat beer,
tilt the glass at 45 degrees
and fill only 70%.
Then, you should pour in the rest
including the settled yeast
to deepen the flavor.
[Day 11, 12, 13]
[Day 13, 14, 15]
[Day 16, 17, 18, 19, 20]
Okay.
- Nice.
- Great!
- It's done.
- Wow.
I knew this would be successful.
- Fine.
- I knew this would be a hit.
Go ahead.
[Pharmacy]
One digestive medicine, please.
What stomach issues are you having?
I'm having indigestion
and feeling a bit nauseous.
My back hurts,
and I'm shivering a little too.
Well... yes.
Could you possibly...
No way.
I'm pregnant?
[5 Years Ago]
It is indeed an endometrial cyst.
Moreover, your uterus is congenitally weak,
so pregnancy might be difficult.
They told me that pregnancy
might be difficult for me.
What is this?
Ah, it hurts.
Hui Won, what are you doing?
Exercise, exercising.
Hurry up, I'm hungry.
Yeah.
Did you think I'd say that?
You're acting weird today.
What is it? What are you hiding?
- It's nothing.
- Got you.
Mi Ran, let me explain first...
Did you have a man?
Last time you said you
liked someone. Is it him?
Tell me quickly, who is it?
Who on earth is he?
Mi Ran, wait a second.
Well, that's...
I don't know who it is.
No, I know who he is.
But I don't know his name or what he does...
What should I do?
You're now five weeks pregnant.
Today, we checked
the gestational sac and yolk sac.
You should be able to hear
the heartbeat around week seven.
It might be slightly delayed
depending on your menstrual cycle.
Shall we schedule your next appointment?
Even now, you're worried about
seeing someone you know?
What did the doctor say?
Are you actually pregnant?
What should I do now?
What do you mean?
You need to find that man first.
Don't you remember anything
about the baby's father?
Well...
He's about 6'1", maybe?
He has double eyelids, thick eyebrows.
He looks chic when not smiling,
but like a puppy when he does.
You observed him in great detail.
Could it be him you're talking about?
Oh? Manager!
Is she from your company?
Wait, that necklace...
He's a bit older, but a total romantic.
Girlfriend?
You punk.
That's her.
- Se Hyeon.
- What's wrong?
- Is this the punk you were talking about?
- Manager.
Who are you? Do you know what you've done?
Manager, this is my uncle.
That woman who's been haunting
my thoughts since that day.
Ms. Jang Hui Won.
You left the baby's ultrasound photo.
The woman I was searching for
now has a baby.
Am I your baby's father?
Let's just go our separate ways.
Are you going to be a father?
I'm ruined.
Are you really the Jang Hui Won I know?
Do you like him? Are you dating him?
Why is he here?
Wait a minute.
Manager Jang Hui Won,
people will misunderstand.
Ah, you can't do this to me.
No, this is exactly the kind of situation
that invites misunderstanding.
Like falling in love at first sight...
Kang Du Jun?
[Jang Hui Won]
She's pregnant?
How amusing.
Uncle, you're not getting married
because of me, are you?
I'll take responsibility.
Let's get married.
What?