UNDERCOVER MISS HONG
What an odd resemblance.
Ms. Hong.
Do you have an older sister?
An older sister?
Me?
Ms. Song!
Code red, level two
has been activated, ma'am.
What's "code red, level two"?
You work here.
How could you not know that?
Would I ask if I did?
Gosh, that was so close.
When will you stop neglecting my Nora?
Forcing her to be an entry-level minion
and live in the dorms
was all your doing, wasn't it?
I suggested it to the chairman
for Ms. Kang's sake.
You suggested for her sake?
I expected as much.
You, a complete stranger,
worry about my Nora?
Such an important matter should've been
discussed with me, her mother.
After you divorced the chairman,
you got remarried, divorced,
married a third time,
before landing your third divorce.
Meanwhile, the one who took care of
her school life and her peer relationships
was me.
Why you…
If you really care about Ms. Kang,
I suggest you refrain
from visiting the office.
Ju-ran.
Do I look like some pathetic woman
who needs to rely on a man to live?
I never said such--
And what makes you so different?
You're worse if anything.
You're just an elevator girl
who lucked out and scored the chairman.
"Chief of Staff"? Please.
But did you know?
The house you live in,
the car you drive, and even this office
can disappear into thin air
with a word from the chairman.
At least, I got my divorce settlement.
You'll be kicked out with nothing.
Remember that.
"Outstanding Women"?
What the hell is this?
How tacky.
You're wasting the company's money
on this sort of nonsense, aren't you?
Save it for a decent outfit.
The Outstanding Women Employees' Club
was established in October 1993
to benefit Hanmin's female staff.
I'm only doing this as a favor to you.
- This will be your responsibility.
- Yes, sir.
Ms. Song Ju-ran
decided the female staff
needed an employee association
and persuaded Chairman Kang
to support the cause.
OUTSTANDING WOMAN
KIM I-GYEONG
Congratulations.
Please look over here.
Each quarter,
a female employee is selected
to be honored with a plaque
and a cash prize.
It actively promotes inclusion and morale
among the female staff.
HANMIN OUTSTANDING WOMEN'S CLUB
SEOUL CITY DORMITORY
FOR SINGLE FEMALE WORKERS
This quarter,
you'd be a prime candidate.
You prevented that order error too.
No, I don't think so.
Come on now.
I hope it's you.
Well, that would be nice.
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
EMPLOYEE PERSONNEL RECORD
HONG CHUN-SEOP, FATHER
KIM SOON-JUNG, MOTHER
Hong Jang-mi is an only child.
I think that explains
why she has no manners.
May I ask
why you have taken
such an interest in Hong Jang-mi?
The president also asked about her before.
President Shin did? When?
It was around the time she was involved
in the trading order incident.
I see.
I'm just checking some things
for the Outstanding Woman selection,
that's all.
- You may leave.
- Yes, ma'am.
The Outstanding Women Employees' Club
was founded in 1993,
after real-name banking was introduced.
I secretly reviewed Ms. Song's
out-of-town business trip expense reports.
I'll fax it over, so please verify it
with the local financial institution.
Those are the transaction details.
Twelve billion won was deposited
to Kim I-gyeong at Songwi Branch
and another 12 billion
was deposited to Go Bok-hee.
As expected, the funds were spread across
three financial institutions in Chungseo.
They moved accounts every quarter
to launder that money.
But there's also this.
Take a look.
It turns out the body discovered
at the reservoir belonged to Kim I-gyeong.
This is serious business.
These bastards have
no respect for human life.
No wonder Yehppee went into hiding.
Something felt off,
so I looked into Onemillion's CEO as well.
He disappeared and has gone missing.
He could've left the country
or he might be in hiding.
If we dig deeper, I'm sure we'll find
something like we did with the club.
Song Ju-ran recently asked me
if I had an older sister.
Boy, it sent chills down my spine.
What? Were you caught?
Then how are you here?
I was saved by a visit
from Kang Nora's mother.
I'll just have to deny it.
I am Hong Jang-mi,
no matter what anyone says.
Hong Jang-mi.
OUTSTANDING EMPLOYEES
EPISODE 6: THE SILENCE OF THE MISSES
OUTSTANDING WOMAN AWARD NOMINATION
REQUIREMENT:
RECOMMENDATION FROM DIVISION HEAD
WOULD YOU LIKE TO PRINT?
YES
Mr. Oh.
Will you write me
a recommendation for the OW Award?
Now.
You need to write a reason.
What should I write?
"Recommendable"?
"Ms. Hong Jang-mi is diligent."
"She performs her duties with passion
and sets an example for others…"
"Particularly, in September 1997,
she identified an order error
made by Hanmin
and swiftly resolved the issue."
- "Thus, I strongly recommend her
- for the OW award."
One's full of self-praise,
and the other one's writing her legend.
Going all out, aren't we?
Intranet planning and development,
order-entry error remediation,
and the trading system enhancement.
I, Hong Jang-mi,
proved myself in all three instances.
You should write all that down
and number them.
"One…"
"Intranet planning and development."
You want an Outstanding Woman nomination?
For free?
How much do you want?
I'm not interested in chump change.
Besides,
don't talk about money
in front of the kid.
Let's keep it educational.
Fine.
Thank you.
Let's dig in!
Bom.
Why aren't you eating
and just staring at Auntie Jang-mi?
The director said we should start eating
after the oldest one
at the table starts eating.
The oldest…
Queen Bee.
The eldest should take the first bite.
All right, let's eat.
Eat up, Bom.
Okay.
HANMIN'S OUTSTANDING WOMEN EMPLOYEES
She must really want to be on the list.
She's treating this like it's a talisman.
Will Hong Jang-mi become the 17th?
Kim I-gyeong?
OUTSTANDING WOMEN EMPLOYEES
= SLUSH FUND CUSTODIAN
I was the 16th!
There must be money in my account as well.
I should check as soon as possible.
Did you win the lottery?
You scared me.
Something like that.
Fine. I'll do it.
I'll nominate you.
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
Sales performance
across all business divisions
has fallen by 30% compared to last year.
I assume the challenging
global economic conditions
and heightened equity risk
- have investors pulling back--
- Listen.
Back when I worked
as a currency exchanger in Namdaemun,
the shop next door
was a raw-fish restaurant.
Some days, the fish prepared
in anticipation of demand went unsold,
and they'd have leftovers.
If they kept it in the fridge,
they couldn't sell it raw the next day.
But still,
do you think the restaurant owner
just threw away perfectly good fish?
No. Of course not.
They would use that less-fresh fish
to make spicy fish stew.
Or they would pile on the chili powder
to make a braised dish to sell.
I'm saying, they sold it
one way or another to turn a profit.
If they won't sell as individual stocks,
get creative and try cooking with them.
Put them out there as an equity fund.
But Hanmin Asset Management
is in charge of equity funds.
Do you want us Securities to pursue them?
Come on now,
all lucrative ventures belong to
Hanmin Investment & Securities.
Even if
I fail miserably
and I'm forced to sell off
all our subsidiaries,
Hanmin Investment & Securities
will remain standing.
Sir.
Wouldn't Research be
well-equipped to handle this,
considering they specialize
in domestic and global economic data?
General Manager Cha,
your division does have
most of the overseas-trained, sharp minds.
That's right, sir.
We'll make it happen, no matter what.
Albert.
You too, you punk.
Me? Me too?
Research and Risk Management,
combine forces
to come up with a real gem of a product.
Bang, you should take a backseat
on this task force.
What do you mean?
Albert will remain unaffected
by your performance.
But we're different.
We need to prove our worth this time
if we want to survive.
We do need to prove ourselves somehow
to make up for the last incident.
We'll have you serve
as an advisor on this,
so don't worry.
Just let me have the spotlight this time.
I'll be sure to produce a winner.
I'm not doing this just for my livelihood.
We all need to survive, man.
Got it.
You know what the chairman likes.
He wants maximized profits and efficiency,
something that makes a lot of money.
Ms. Hong.
Where do you think you're sitting?
Do you even know what a task force is?
We need Ms. Hong.
Mr. Lee, do you want out too? Leave.
No, don't leave.
Since you're good with computers,
you can type.
Take the meeting minutes.
Ms. Hong.
You know what to do.
Do your job.
Why that little…
Jeez.
Every project has a lead
and a supporting role.
For this new fund product
development task force,
Research will be leading,
and Risk Management will be supporting.
I hope that works for you.
- Why--
- Okay!
Okay.
It seems Hong Jang-mi
used to attend beauty school
and now assists a celebrity stylist.
The other photo
is a group shot with Hong Keum-bo
that was taken when she joined the FSS.
Should I dig deeper?
No, that's enough.
Thank you.
I really like steak.
It's so good.
I'm glad.
Your employment at Hanmin
remains a secret, correct?
My mom, dad,
Mr. Oh, Albert, and Ms. Song.
Only these people know about it,
but you were just added.
To tell you the truth, I live in a dorm,
and not at my dad's place.
That's why I can't get caught.
The dorms…
Ms. Go lives there as well, right?
Along with Ms. Hong Jang-mi.
We live in the same apartment.
We're roommates.
Right.
Have you ever tried
chicken skewers in Seoul?
No.
Are they tasty?
Let's get some next time.
I know of a good street vendor in Yeouido.
Okay.
I knew you'd make a cute couple.
How does Christmas Eve
for the engagement sound?
It would be so romantic.
For that to happen…
Nora.
- That's enough steak for now.
- Wait…
Let's try some salad.
You'll need to fit in your wedding dress.
Shall we clink?
Not you.
- Cheers.
Man, that's sweet.
It feels a bit empty
eating all this with just you
when Mr. Lee and Ms. Hong
are still back at the office.
You almost sound believable.
They're just too much.
Why go out of their way
to find work for themselves?
By the way,
how did you ever manage to escape
that infiltrator hunt?
Why don't you ask your dad?
Come on.
I already did,
but he refused to answer
and just got angry at me.
He told you to come to his office
by noon that day,
but you didn't show up.
That's because I took
my concrete evidence somewhere else.
Where?
Look.
You've grown on me,
so let me give you a piece of advice.
As long as Ms. Song Ju-ran is around,
you and Executive Director Oh
don't stand a chance.
So if I want to move up,
I need to be on her good side
and not my dad's?
Yeah.
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
Ms. Go.
These letters keep coming for you.
SENDER: GO BOK-CHEOL
AHNHYANG CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
Bok-hee.
Did you change jobs again?
I put a lot of effort
into writing you all those letters,
but seeing them all sent back
is starting to bother me.
Then someone told me they spotted you
near the Hanmin building in Yeouido.
I'll be released at the end of November.
See you then.
And make a fat deposit
into my inmate fund before then.
I came looking for treasure
And it came to me
That's my money. I earned that money!
- Let go of me.
- Who do you think you are?
Me? Your older brother.
I'm just borrowing it.
You'll gamble it away again
and lose every last cent!
You damn brat!
Hey.
What? You think those onlookers
are going to help you?
Huh?
You little shit!
What?
Enjoying the show?
Well? Are you going to help her?
Go on. I dare you.
Bok-hee.
You're not wasting money when it's on me.
We're family.
You and I only have each other.
Here's some pocket money.
Jeez.
Goddamn it!
Hey, Bok-hee.
Wait.
SENDER: GO BOK-CHEOL
AHNHYANG CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
RECIPIENT: GO BOK-HEE
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
SENDER: GO BOK-CHEOL
AHNHYANG CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
NOVEMBER, 1997
He said he'll be released
in the last week of November,
so I'll just steal it all before then.
GO BOK-CHEOL'S RELEASE DATE
This year, an average of 40 companies
have gone bankrupt each day.
With total bankruptcy expected
to top 20 trillion by the year-end…
After months of barely hanging on
under severe financial strain,
Hantae Group
finally declared bankruptcy today.
Following today's announcement,
the government has settled on
court receivership
and a third-party acquisition
as its solution
to the Giheon Motors crisis.
The government will convert
320 billion won in loans
extended to Giheon Motors
by the Korea Development Bank into equity…
All right, don't just sit there.
Make some calls to clients.
- Yes, sir.
Hello, this is Kim Mi-sook
calling from Hanmin's Magang Branch.
Please note that the amount
is deliberately set
at a conservative level.
Now, shall we move on to the next one?
So…
What? What is it?
The third line from the bottom of page two
has Sedu Trading
listed under top holdings.
Their second consecutive audit disclaimer
makes delisting imminent.
Where?
Sedu… Oh this?
That's just a typo.
You're good at finding those.
Right, let's move on to the next page.
And Ogyu Construction listed below that.
They went bankrupt last week.
I was just about to say that.
You just told everyone to flip the page.
That's enough from you.
Know your damn place!
Mr. Cha Jung-il.
You're too loud.
Sir, I meant no disrespect.
I'll be more mindful.
Done.
Big Al.
Salute!
- Amazing.
- Here you go, Mr. Oh.
RESERVED
Let's drink.
Man, that's bitter.
That man is a ball
of disrespect and typos.
You saw how he caved
when Albert, his very much junior,
said something.
It's delicious.
He's a real piece of work.
Exactly.
Still, I've never seen Big Al
do that before.
I think he was really angry.
But they're all buddy-buddy now,
having a blast.
Mr. Lee.
Should restaurants sell
food that has gone bad, or not?
They should not.
Should a securities firm sell a fund
made up only of struggling companies
that could go bankrupt any day, or not?
They should not.
That's my point.
We should help fill people's pockets,
not bleed them dry.
It's not like I can lead the charge.
It'd be better
if we made it ourselves, right?
The two of us?
If it's with you,
I'm willing to do anything,
- whenever…
- What's with the reserved table here?
I heard a VIP is coming.
A VIP?
Hello?
Have you arrived? Yes, sir.
Oh, he's here?
Yes.
Please come in, sir.
- Thank you for all your hard work.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Please take a seat.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Hong, that damn brat.
At least she's consistent.
Your tireless efforts
in the new product development
are very much appreciated.
I must say I'm pleased
to be working again with such capable
and irreplaceable talent.
Let's cheers to that.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Ms. Hong.
Grab us some cigarettes
and popsicles from the supermarket.
Help yourself, sir.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
- Sir?
- Sure. Thank you.
My goodness, thank you for joining us.
Allow me.
Really?
Thank you, sir.
Is he doing that on purpose
to mess with me?
Does he know it's me?
I do.
Time to be shameless.
Sir, would you like to choose one?
Were you the one who sent in
that anonymous tip about Mr. So,
Ms. Hong Jang-mi?
You secured a three-billion-won
cancellation agreement
from Onemillion's CEO,
fresh off a stock-rigging windfall.
Hong Jang-mi,
the 20-year-old entry-level employee,
couldn't have easily pulled off
such feats on her own.
But still, I got it done.
You made me do it.
Because I wanted you to leave quietly.
But you managed to survive.
Don't you realize
that only makes you more suspicious?
Or are you
just playing dumb?
There you are, Ms. Hong.
You haven't answered me yet.
I don't know.
It's almost curfew time at the dorms,
so I'll be off now.
Ms. Hong!
Shin Jung-woo,
you grew up to become an evil man.
Don't look back and don't lock eyes.
Remember, you're Hong Jang-mi.
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
About the cash
from Kim I-gyeong's account…
Deposit it into
Go Bok-hee's account for now,
until the new account is ready.
Thanks.
RISK MANAGEMENT DIVISION
Is it the HR announcement board?
Yes.
An employee passed away.
OBITUARY
NAME: KIM I-GYEONG
She must've been young
if she was at a branch.
What a shame.
OBITUARY
NAME: KIM I-GYEONG
WE REGRET TO ANNOUNCE THE PASSING
OF MS. KIM I-GYEONG AT SONGWI BRANCH
DATE OF PASSING: OCTOBER 22, 1997
Kim I-gyeong?
DOMESTIC SLUSH FUND CUSTODIANS
SONGWI BRANCH, KIM I-GYEONG
Jang-mi.
Are you asleep?
Don't use a sweet tone with me like that.
It's scary.
If, by any chance,
you come across money
that falls out of the sky, leave it.
Just walk away, okay?
Worry about yourself.
What did I do?
I give you words of wisdom,
yet you'll refuse to listen.
If only I'd grown up in a normal family
like the ones you see on TV…
If only I'd gone to college…
If only I worked for a company
where people addressed me by my full name…
I would've led an ordinary life.
I wouldn't wish for much more.
It's still not too late for you.
Go to college while you can.
Risk Management submitted
a separate proposal
for a new fund product.
Mr. Oh.
What's the objective?
We adjusted the portfolio
to prioritize investment risk management.
Then the expected return would be too low.
How low are we talking?
It was set conservatively,
given domestic
and global economic concerns.
Was this proposal discussed with Research?
Not at all.
We've already taken those factors
into account, of course.
Ms. Hong Jang-mi.
Don't feed your words to another,
and speak for yourself.
All the points I wanted to make
are reflected in the improvement proposal.
Bundling together junk stocks
with credit ratings of C or D
is a form of client deception.
Without risk, there's no return.
The Research Division
will continue to take the lead.
Yes, sir.
Worry about your own risks.
Good job.
Well done.
BREAK ROOM
That report…
Did you write it?
No.
Ms. Hong did.
How does she manage to produce
assistant-manager-level…
No, manager-level quality work
every damn time?
She's smart.
Too smart, in fact.
Where's Bok-hee?
Queen Bee?
She said she's going to Chungseo tonight
for a business trip.
She has some important business tomorrow.
Chungseo?
Is she accompanying the president?
No.
She said
she's taking the train by herself.
Damn it.
Wait.
Seriously, Go Bok-hee?
That money is nothing but trouble.
Sir, I'm in a rush.
Go Bok-hee, the Queen Bee…
I need to find your assistant
to ask her something.
Ms. Go just left for the day.
Damn it.
I need to hear the answer
I never got back then.
Why has Hong Keum-bo
lied to plant herself in Hanmin?
Can you try to make a little more sense?
Why do you keep asking me about my sister?
EMERGENCY STOP
I asked you first.
What are you doing here?
It sounds like you already know.
OUT OF SERVICE
Big Al, maybe we should take
another elevator.
I can't help but wonder.
Who's trapped in there?
If they're alone, it's horror.
If there are two, it's romance.
- If there are three…
- Oxygen deprivation.
Where did Ms. Hong go?
I saw her bag at her desk.
She's slacking off already,
leaving her desk during business hours.
Call her.
All right.
Why did you sneak into Hanmin?
Didn't you think I'd kick you out?
I did,
but you already failed once.
I'll let my sister know you said hello,
though I doubt she'll be thrilled.
The elevator is fine.
Hello, sir.
Bok-hee.
It's been a while.
How…
How are you out so soon?
Your brother got released early
for good behavior.
You don't seem too thrilled about that.
Did you not get my letters?
I told you I'd find you.
You must've forgotten about my temper,
haven't you?
Damn it. I ought to just…
How dare you try to hit a woman!
Who the hell are you?
What the hell?
Come on, bro.
Let's just do as I say.
Bok-hee.
I'll be back.
- You lucked out today.
- Why you…
Hi, Mommy!
- Hi, Mommy!
- Hi!
- Let's try this one.
We're home now, so talk.
Who was that crazy bastard earlier?
Your boyfriend?
No!
He's my brother.
My older brother.
How is he out already?
His release was set for late November.
Release?
Prison!
Oh my god.
The letter you dropped in the locker room,
from Ahnhyang Correctional Institution.
SENDER: GO BOK-CHEOL
AHNHYANG CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
Why would I still be here at my age,
living in the dorms with you all
if I had normal parents
or siblings with stable jobs?
I'm sick and tired of this life too!
I don't want to spend my life
being drained by a leech.
Was she trying to make a quick score
and run before her brother's release?
I need to withdraw it all
before they announce
the Outstanding Woman next week.
I have a train to catch.
I need to go.
Let go.
I asked you first.
What are you doing here?
It sounds like you already know.
I should've held back.
I should've just ignored it.
I never asked you for help.
I wasn't talking about you.
You regret helping me earlier.
You're scared of his criminal record!
I couldn't care less about that right now.
That bastard will
eventually track down this dorm.
I've been all over the country
trying to get away from him.
What are you…
I'll write a recommendation
for my replacement.
Who?
You. Hong Jang-mi.
No thanks. What's wrong with you?
Why are you packing?
You're not going anywhere.
- Take it all out.
- Stop it.
Where would you even go?
He was over 180 cm tall,
and he had thick hair
with sharp-looking eyes.
He was also wearing a trench coat.
If we see a man matching that description
suspiciously lurking around the dorms,
let's take him down immediately.
Where are you going?
To work.
This isn't a midnight run, okay?
Bok-hee, wait.
This is pepper spray for self-defense,
and this is your lunch.
Eat your lunch in the office for now.
Bok-hee,
I'm always praying for you.
My mommy prays every day.
I don't need any prayers.
Thanks anyway.
I'm not feeling the cafeteria today.
I want to eat out.
Let's go.
What about that place out front?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
You've reached Hanmin's Admin Office.
Hey, you asked me last time
about Hong Jang-mi
from Jemulpo Girls' Commercial High.
Well, I looked into her.
You did?
JEMULPO GIRLS' COMMERCIAL HIGH SCHOOL
Apparently she was a total delinquent.
She was a notorious brawler.
Hey.
Don't you know who I am?
Shut the hell up.
She became top dog
as soon as she enrolled,
and she led the charge
whenever they fought other schools.
How did such a delinquent
even submit employment paperwork?
She has a sister
who's a lot older than her.
I heard she tried to force her
into a junior college, but failed.
She has a sister?
And her parents run
a fried chicken place in Jemulpo.
I think it was called Ullala Chicken.
All right, thanks.
What is it?
It's weird.
It's after hours,
so I can put my head down.
All of you slack off all the time.
Not that.
The new fund product development
task force.
I couldn't care less about it.
The chairman forced it on me,
and I was just going to go along
with whatever Research decided.
But seeing you get scolded
and our proposal get shot down,
I feel…
upset.
Because you're the leader,
and we're on the same team.
We're one team.
Because you're the leader.
I heard The Contact,
a romance movie with Han Suk-kyu
and Jeon Do-yeon, is a hit.
Have you seen it?
What does that movie
have to do with the fund?
I'm…
asking you out on a date.
Do you want to see it with me?
Tomorrow, Saturday night.
At seven o'clock.
There's quite an age gap between us.
Is twenty
and twenty-five too big a gap?
It's inappropriate.
I mean, it just feels wrong.
While I was downing makgeolli
by the bowl in college,
Albert was in elementary school,
learning kids' stuff,
probably drawing in his journal and stuff.
This is too much.
Oh gosh.
Jeez.
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
It's just absurd.
He's ten years younger than me.
He's a kid.
To Albert, you are Hong Jang-mi,
and he probably thinks
he was rejected by a 20-year-old.
The more I think about it,
the angrier I get.
I mean, if he asked you out,
you should've just said yes.
You could set a honey trap
to dig up some first-rate intel
about the Kang family.
How could you just toss away that chance?
Do I look like Mata Hari?
Why would I weaponize my beauty?
What?
It's much better to be a pretty spy
than just a regular spy.
Others would kill to be one.
Don't forget.
When you stand in front of
Shin Jung-woo or Albert Oh,
you're Hong Jang-mi.
The beautiful 20-year-old.
Jeez, I was really hoping to avoid
setting a honey trap.
That's the fate of a beautiful woman.
Saturday morning duties are done.
It's time to go home.
It was seven o'clock, right?
At the Piccadilly Theater at Jongno 3-ga?
Yes, seven is when it starts.
Then I'll see you at the cafe
in front of the theater at 6:40.
LONG PALE YELLOW DRESS, FLATS
He was over 180 cm tall,
and he had thick hair
with sharp-looking eyes.
He was wearing a trench coat.
If you see a man matching that description
suspiciously lurking around the dorms,
let's take him down immediately.
So this is the dorm where
Hong Keum-bo is living as Hong Jang-mi.
Why in the world
is she going to such great lengths?
Jang-mi, do you have a date?
I guess you really are seeing somebody.
You look like a princess.
Hey, you're back.
Over 180 cm tall,
with thick hair and sharp-looking eyes.
He matches the description perfectly.
Should we call the police?
Queen Bee, lock the door
and stay here with the kid.
And you two,
get the RA and the security guard.
Okay.
Bom, stay here with Auntie Bok-hee, okay?
Jang-mi!
Mr. Go Bok-cheol?
What the…
You…
have become quite savage.
- What are you doing?
- Over there!
How dare you!
Stop right there!
You bastard.
How dare you!
What the…
Ms. Kim, stop.
He's not the bad guy!
Then who is he?
Oh no. Are you okay?
I mean, are you okay, sir?
Water…
Damn it.
Ms. Hong.
Ms. Hong Jang-mi, explain yourself.
I heard a violent, abusive member
of Go Bok-hee's family was here.
And now, he's not him?
Who in the world
is this unidentified male?
Well, you see, he is…
No, please, let me explain.
"Hanmin Investment & Securities,
President Shin Jung-woo."
President?
The president?
President Shin?
Did he come to see
Kang Nora in secret,
only to get dragged into this mess?
I'm so sorry, sir.
I completely forgot to fax
that document you asked for.
Please accept my sincerest apology.
Yes, sure. Well…
My apologies for the misunderstanding
and the collar grabbing.
Please understand it was necessary
for the safety of my residents.
It's all right.
I should apologize.
Let's go, sir.
You three, disperse.
Jang-mi, you go on your date.
What are you looking at?
I can take that.
This way.
Ms. Go, the truth is--
Taxi!
I'll make sure they stay quiet.
- What…
- Here you go.
Wait.
Okay then.
Queen Bee.
That was a lie before, right?
What kind of president comes to
his assistant's dorm to pick up a file?
Could he have been here to see me?
Maybe he likes me?
I just left the worst impression
on the president.
I'm never going to be full-time now, am I?
Was someone here?
Don't be curious,
and don't be concerned.
Why? Because tonight, no one was here.
Let's go home.
I'm late.
I'm a 20-year-old Hong Jang-mi.
A-E-I…
I can't believe even the
midnight screening was sold out.
Well, it's Saturday night.
Do you slice your pork cutlet
before every bite?
Or do you slice it all up first?
I slice it up first.
I'd rather get it done before.
Okay.
Go on and slice mine up too.
Bite-sized, please.
I'm kidding.
By the way, I read on Yeouido Pirates
that you all live at the chairman's place.
You, Executive Director Oh,
and even Ms. Song?
Is it like round-the-clock assistance
or something?
I'm actually…
more curious about
what you discussed with President Shin
that day in the elevator.
Oh, that?
What did I ask him again?
Right.
I asked him if he already signed off
on this quarter's Outstanding Woman.
That's nice.
Pass me my phone.
Hello?
Hey, Nora.
The president came
all the way to the dorm.
I mean, who else does he know here but me?
What?
He showed up at your place
in the middle of the night?
This is 100% romance.
That's really how he feels about me?
He never said that to me though.
You just don't know.
When it comes to men,
what matters is how much time and money
they spend on a woman.
That's all.
He did say he wanted to take me
to a tasty restaurant next time.
That's spending money and time,
you big dummy.
That was
a declaration of love.
PRESIDENT SHIN JUNG-WOO
Ms. Go, can I get something to drink?
Thank you.
Gosh, what brings you by?
Did I surprise you?
Yes, a bit…
Well, I was even more surprised.
Don't come to the dorms!
I must survive
the three-month probationary period
and become a full-time employee.
Why?
If I do,
my father will give me an additional 9%
of the company's shares.
So my mom insisted that I do.
Anyway,
I understand how you feel,
but I'm not there yet.
Stop liking me so much already!
I…
FULL-SERVICE SHOE REPAIR
That's good.
Thank you.
- Excuse me for a moment.
- Sure. Go ahead.
The police closed the Kim I-gyeong case
as a suicide,
but her family refuses to accept it.
The funeral has been postponed.
And it seems
someone else is also looking for
the CEO of Onemillion.
HORANG AUTO REPAIR SHOP
BONG DAL-SU
Horang Auto Repair Shop.
I hear he might be an investor
who got scammed.
But his address
is on the outskirts of Seoul.
I'll check him out.
Can we take a rain check
on the movie tonight?
Okay. I'm being dragged to
a family gathering tonight as well.
Is he not here yet?
No, but Albert is on his way.
There must be a lot of traffic.
Traffic in Seoul is nothing new.
How could he have
all these adults waiting for him?
He's been so busy.
Oh, that must be him.
Gosh, President Shin!
Surprise, Chairman!
I also invited President Shin.
He's future family, after all.
Welcome.
I knew.
He reached out to me.
He didn't want to intrude
on a family gathering.
It was about time everyone met like this,
so I told him it was fine.
How considerate.
President Shin,
you can take that second chair.
Go on, sit.
Right.
It always looks like
there's food for everyone
but none for me.
Let's eat now.
Sure.
Enjoy, everyone.
HORANG AUTO REPAIR SHOP
Albert?
What's he doing here?
This is why
you should know your place and not act up.
SPECIAL THANKS TO SHIN YU-NA
FOR HER APPEARANCE
UNDERCOVER MISS HONG
I thought he was just another deadbeat.
Who is he really?
For all we know,
Albert could be managing the slush fund.
Congratulations!
This quarter's Outstanding Woman
is Hong Jang-mi!
That OW money must be in
Hong Jang-mi's account now.
There's some easy money at the company.
Where did you get that notebook from?
Maybe she knows about Yehppee
and the slush fund ledger as well?
Hello, Yehppee.
I'd like to meet you.
No woman should be there alone this late.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim