UNDERCOVER MISS HONG
Stay still.
-Hurry up and hand these out too.
-Yes, sir.
-Is it centered?
-It's perfect right now.
Hey, this is backwards.
You're looking into a mirror.
Oh, you're right. "Over my dead body."
But if I'm being honest,
I support financial reforms.
All of it needs to be upended.
What is it?
What's that around your head?
Does it make me look old?
Man, you're something else.
Look at you, clawing your way back
to the head office to save your ass.
How dare you suck on a candy
in front of the director?
My roommate told me
to eat one at a time like this.
You got a problem?
Share if you have extra.
What's this?
Resignation…
Hey, kid.
That's just how things are
in the real world.
You need to know
how to own your failures--
Who said I failed?
I'm not done yet.
Why you…
Please process my resignation quickly.
I'll be off.
What?
Hey, take this back…
Stop! Hong Keum-bo!
Hold on!
Stop her! Hong Keum-bo!
Hong Keum-bo! You can't resign!
Not over my dead body!
Did Ms. Hong just resign?
Yeah.
She quit.
Why is she quitting?
She must be getting married.
That has to be it.
An older single woman
would only quit like that
when she's getting married.
Taxi!
-Damn it.
-Hong!
Sir, take me to Hanmin's head office.
I'll pay you double.
Hong, wait! Stop!
-Oh no.
-Why you…
I'm coming with you.
Damn it! Who said you could quit?
-Put your seatbelt on.
-What? Seatbelt?
Who cares about seatbelts right now?
Why won't this pull out?
Hey, are you protesting
because things didn't go your way?
This country's economy is in peril.
Nobody cares about
a chairman embezzling money.
They're not going to pursue it!
How can you not understand that?
Given the economic crisis,
they're willing to let charges like
illegal slush funds and tax evasion slide.
Turning a blind eye like this
only lets the big crooks run wild.
The higher-ups letting them slide
are basically accomplices.
Accomplices?
You must be joking. Watch it!
INVESTMENT AGREEMENT
INVESTMENT AMOUNT: 300 BILLION WON
KANG PIL-BEOM
All right.
Here.
My goodness.
Thank you.
-Great.
-Thank you, sir.
It was a pleasure.
Thanks.
Chairman Kang won't change his mind
now that the smoke's cleared, right?
Hanmin can't even cover
the promissory notes due in two weeks.
They keep up appearances,
but they're a house of cards
at this point.
Even now,
I think your decision
to target Korea next was spot-on.
I guess you enjoyed the report
from the "advance scout."
Most definitely.
Chairman Kang may try to rein us in later,
given that he's naturally distrustful.
I'll have the shell company we set up
start buying up bonds as well.
Okay.
Are there any issues
like someone you're wary of?
There was someone,
but I took care of it.
The IMF crisis has emerged
as a major variable,
shaking up the 15th presidential election.
The candidates continue to fiercely debate
over who bears responsibility,
calling for a reckoning
within both parties and pressing voters
to demand accountability
at the ballot box.
Experts say major variables
will remain in flux
until the election's final days.
As we reach the final stretch…
I'm going to become a major variable.
Sir, you can drop me off up ahead,
and please drive him back to the FSS.
Where are we?
Hey, where are we?
What about the fare?
I didn't bring my wallet.
Just call Nam Dong-gi down
once you've arrived at the office.
Hey! Hold on a second.
-Sir, can't you roll the window down?
-Bye.
Hey, wait! Hong!
I hope you trip and fall!
Hong Keum-bo!
EPISODE 10: CLASH OF THE TITANS
I went into the FSS today
and saw Hong Keum-bo.
It's her.
She's the one that came to the auto shop
with Chairman Kang's grandson.
Really?
She came in today
and handed in her resignation.
People were talking about
her getting married or something.
Her boss followed her out
and begged her to stay,
but she never looked back once.
She must've known it was a lost cause.
It seems she's not a complete idiot.
But how does Hong Keum-bo and Albert Oh
know each other?
Well?
Should I dig deeper into Hong Keum-bo?
What could she possibly do
without her title?
No.
Her car must have been there for a reason.
Try tailing Albert.
We need concrete evidence
to get rid of Albert
and ensure a sure push for Nora
as the next president.
EMPLOYMENT AGREEMENT
This is your new employment contract.
Even amid difficult economic conditions,
we fought to preserve jobs
for our female staff,
but the recent round of restructuring
was an inevitable decision.
We hope you understand
that these new measures are designed
to strengthen internal cohesion
and help prevent future layoffs.
"Contract employment.
Terminable at any time."
"One female employee for three divisions."
So they'll work us to the bone, huh?
After stamping your seal or thumbprint,
leave the contracts here
and return to your divisions.
Collect them and bring them to me.
Yes, ma'am.
Being away from your post too long
will reflect poorly on all of us.
Stamp your seals and return at once.
What if it didn't burn?
By the will of the heavens,
it ended up in my hands.
Not a chance, Queen Bee.
You'll be laden with honors
if you return with that.
No.
I'm going to steal it all.
Are you in?
You're not reporting it to the FSS?
I already did, but the higher-ups
have no intention to pursue it.
Given that we're in an economic crisis,
corporate corruption
is apparently off the table.
The higher-ups are always the issue.
I want to steal all of this money
to oust the corrupt controlling
shareholder and complicit executives,
and save Hanmin's employees.
You saw the ledger,
so you know I can't do it alone.
You said you only went after dirty money.
Then again, Hanmin's slush fund
is the dirtiest money I've ever seen.
You have three days to decide.
I hope you're in.
Also,
I can stay with Mi-sook tonight.
I'm off to work now.
EMPLOYEE NAME: HONG…
Didn't you say Hong Keum-bo would return
to the FSS on December 8th?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I have that kid to blame
for my migraine right now.
She showed up at the office today
and threw a resignation letter in my face.
A resignation letter?
Director Yun.
Are you sure
you're not hatching another plan?
You put her to work again, didn't you?
Why you little…
You think she'd listen to me?
Don't you know her?
I wouldn't even be talking
if I had some sort of decent plan.
What could she even do there by herself?
She's just being stubborn right now!
Don't get me riled up.
It's making my headache worse.
She won't even answer my calls right now.
Can you just sweet-talk her
into coming back here?
-Director Yun!
-Just utilize your charm.
I'm sure you can do it.
Jeez, could you be any more frustrating?
Damn it.
SUCCESS WILL NOT WAIT FOR YOU
Why are you cracking a book here
when you've never been much of a reader?
You're surprisingly relentless
with maintaining your public image.
You're 17 minutes late.
I don't have much time.
I'll give you ten minutes.
I must say I'm curious.
Why did you ask to see me out here?
We're under constant surveillance
at the office and at the house.
I'm talking about Oh Deok-gyu.
Oh Deok-gyu?
He's been flipping out
ever since my daughter and I moved in.
He might have a hulking body
and giant bug eyes,
but he's the pettiest man alive.
I'm thinking about securing a position
for Ms. Kang at the company.
Why? Did the chairman tell you to?
You're scared you'll be kicked out
if Oh Deok-gyu becomes president,
so you'll use Nora and me
to shield yourself?
We're in the same boat.
After all, Mr. Oh's nemesis is you.
I can persuade the chairman.
How about officially introducing
Ms. Kang to the company
with a carefully crafted résumé
that's impressive enough to position her
as a successor?
Hold on a second.
Since Albert is a division manager,
my Nora should be ranked higher.
Give her something higher.
And she should have her own big office.
Let's discuss the details over a meal.
Shall we?
Then I'll have the full-course meal.
Okay.
Excuse me.
RISK MANAGEMENT, RESEARCH,
CONFERENCE ROOM
FEMALE STAFF DUTY ASSIGNMENT
HONG JANG-MI: RESEARCH, TRADING, IT
RECEIPTS FOR EXPENSE REPORTS
Hong Jang-mi, you dared to humiliate me?
An amateur would've wiped you out
with the rest of the layoffs.
However, I'm more than that.
I'll pay back that day's humiliation
with double the interest.
Have this translated
by 8:30 a.m. tomorrow.
Hey!
The company is struggling,
yet you're wasting paper.
Use scrap paper for that.
I am using scrap paper.
Hey!
Look at all those numbers.
Security is essential.
You can't just use any old document.
Seriously?
Does he expect me to harvest papyrus then?
Stop glaring.
Ms. Hong, you're always…
Just look at all this.
You're always unprepared
for even your basic duties.
From nine to noon, the Research Division.
From noon to three, the Trading Division.
And from three to six, the IT Division.
Those are my assigned duty hours.
If you'll excuse me,
I'll head to the Trading Division now.
Hey!
You don't get to tell me when you work!
You'll work after hours if you have to.
Why should I devote my time to a company
that could drop me at a moment's notice?
What the…
Get back to work.
I swear, one day,
I'll wipe that smugness off your face,
even if it's the last thing I do here.
Damn it.
Shouldn't we check with the boss
whether to scale back trading on this?
Come on, what would Stoobert know?
Who's "Stoobert"?
Albert the "Stooge" Division Manager.
"Stoobert" for short.
Hello?
Why make me come all the way here?
Director Yun told you to return
on December 8th.
Why are you still here?
You care way too much
about other people's jobs.
Ms. Song has hired someone
to go after Hong Keum-bo,
so get out of here
before you land yourself in trouble.
I should've insisted on firing you
during the restructuring.
You really are the worst.
You'd fire me over a personal vendetta?
Personal?
I'm only trying to eliminate
a risk factor as management.
Did it ever occur to you that I could
easily expose you for identity theft?
No, never.
You'll also be in trouble
if people learn about our past together.
Maybe you've been abroad for too long,
but Koreans eat up romantic entanglement.
Romantic entanglement?
The moment you expose my identity,
you'd be blowing yourself up too.
Unless you want messy gossip around you
and end up on Chairman Kang's bad side,
keep your mouth shut.
This is a threat, just so you know.
What is she thinking?
Chairman.
They say vitamins
help you feel energized in the morning.
-Enjoy.
-Jeez.
Let's see.
It's not bad.
Right?
Right.
It looks like
Nora's still off in dreamland.
Did she forget she now lives with elders?
She still has a lot of growing up to do.
Beauties run on extra sleep,
didn't you know?
Albert must get his looks from his mother.
He wouldn't be falling asleep
if he took after his dad.
I wasn't sleeping!
Oh, right.
Have you set a date
for Nora's first day of work?
She'll be starting next Monday,
and we're preparing a press release.
Good.
What? Nora's first day?
At our company?
No.
Not at your company, but at our company.
We live in a competitive society.
The sharpest one with the most potential
will become my successor.
Of course.
Oh gosh.
Ms. Kang will be
starting work here next week.
She'll be a director, not a staff member,
so she'll need her own office.
Madam Choi will inspect it closely
and be ready to nitpick,
so make sure it's properly set up.
Yes, ma'am.
She'll be frequenting the 12th floor
to prepare for Ms. Kang's engagement.
Just let Admin and the front desk know
about Madam Choi's visits.
An engagement?
With President Shin?
You saw her this morning.
As if that ditzy, naive girl
could ever become a successor.
Kang Nora's mere existence is
nowhere near meeting the qualifications.
I'm not exactly qualified either.
Son, have some confidence.
Be a man.
Dad.
I just know myself and my place well.
Why you…
We need to deal with Kang Nora
pushing her way in.
I mean, she's about to be engaged,
so why does she suddenly need a new title?
Oh, boy.
If President Shin joins her side,
things will get messy.
The patient's name is Kim Mi-sook, right?
-Yes.
-Here's the total amount due.
MEDICAL EXPENSE STATEMENT
TO BE PAID: 674,500 WON
I'll pay the full amount.
Sure.
She paid the hospital bill.
As if it's not infuriating enough
that his daughter was right under my nose.
Hospital fees are really expensive.
Besides, Mi-sook and I were really close.
The father claims
the company played no part,
while his daughter pays the hospital bill.
Are you playing arsonist and firefighter?
It's all Kang Pil-beom's money anyway.
Do you know how he made all that money?
How did he make it…
ma'am?
How do you know, big sis?
Don't call me that.
But you're ten years older than me.
Both of you, stop it.
Let her pay.
That won't even make a dent
in her account.
STRICT BED REST
KIM MI-SOOK
Mi-sook…
Besides, Mi-sook and I were really close.
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
Kang Nora?
Who's that?
Who could she be?
NOTICE OF NEW APPOINTMENT:
EFFECTIVE DECEMBER 15, 1997
NAME: KANG NORA
POSITION: DIRECTOR
Myeong-hwi and I were close friends.
Any sister of his
is a sister of mine too.
I wonder if that princess over there
feels the same way.
You know,
she looks familiar for some reason.
TO THE WORLD, TO THE FUTURE
HANMIN INVESTMENT & SECURITIES
She was the chairman's only daughter?
I'm so jealous.
She'll inherit the company, right?
Is she married?
I don't know about that,
but I read on Yeouido Pirates
that she used to be a successful
Wall Street fund manager.
Really?
What a joke.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
-It's an honor to serve you.
-I'm honored.
-Congratulations.
-You too.
-Yes, congratulations.
-I'll do my very best!
-I'll do my best too.
Hello.
Kang Eun-joo got a score of 210…
I mean, 21 points.
Apple!
It's Apple.
The clueless entry-level minion
from the Trading Division?
And the lowest score on the written exam?
It's you? Ma'am?
Hello, sir.
Who are you calling clueless?
So what if she scored the lowest?
Forget it. You may all leave.
Go on, leave.
The written…
Don't let it upset you, my darling.
What should we have for lunch?
Should we call Mr. Shin?
No, I don't have an appetite.
What?
Gosh.
You don't have an appetite?
That's great.
Let's go all out for this diet.
Nora.
If anyone bothers you at work
or gives you a hard time,
just let me know.
There's nothing I can't do
if it's for you.
Ms. Song Ju-ran and I are joining forces
to make sure you become the chairwoman.
So do as she says, okay?
Okay.
That's my girl.
Queen Bee, have you been well?
I'm back to work starting today.
We ran into each other earlier.
Director Kang Nora.
Have you ratted out
Hong Jang-mi or Go Bok-hee
to your mother?
No, I'm surprisingly loyal.
I do hope you remain loyal.
Especially
when it comes to Hong Jang-mi.
By the way,
is Bom doing all right?
Does she ask for me?
She does not, ma'am.
FEMALE EMPLOYEES' LOCKER ROOM
Where is Bom right now?
Why would the director,
who doesn't even wear a uniform,
come in here?
Just do as your parents say
and behave yourself on the 12th floor.
You're worried about Bom?
You left with your mom
and never looked back!
You're no better
than the trio who bullied you!
You're so mean.
I'll find Bom and bring her to my place!
Hey!
That little…
Ms. Hong.
Are you working late?
Big Al, aren't you going home?
I used to complain
that this office
felt like some tiny rented room,
but now I find it so comforting.
This is the first time I'm speaking today.
The Trading Division
treats me like I'm invisible.
Ms. Hong, I heard
you work for three divisions now.
Isn't it tough?
I'm just doing what I have to.
I'll have to get used to it.
You're still the head of a division.
You should hold weekly meetings
and offer encouraging words
in the morning.
I overheard in the men's room
that when the traders see you come in,
that's how they know it's nine o'clock
and get to work.
You know I'm never late.
Right, Mr. Bang?
I should head out now.
Get home safe.
Goodbye, Ms. Hong.
Ms. Hong is so mature for her age.
She has experience and wisdom
that a 20-year-old can't have.
Yeah.
She's quite big-hearted too.
She seems cold on the outside,
but her heart remains warm.
She really feels like
the senior sometimes.
Yeah, I agree.
Show respect to your senior.
Senior?
That day, Mr. Bang definitely said…
He said she was senior to us.
-No way.
-Come on now.
-Of course not.
-How could she be?
Come on now.
Gosh, Mr. Bang can be so silly.
-Mr. Lee.
-Yes?
Maybe one drink?
Seriously?
Just one.
Big Al.
-Let's go.
-Yeah, let's go.
Director Yun,
you really need to stop calling me.
Listen.
I called for a reason.
I heard Hanmin issued short-term bonds.
A private equity firm in Hong Kong
called DK Ventures bought in bulk,
and other firms bought some as well.
But you know, DK Ventures
is where Shin Jung-woo used to work.
I'll call you back later.
Are you here as a company representative?
No.
Then what are you doing here?
I told you, Ms. Song is looking into you.
I gave you several chances already.
Are you just refusing
to return empty-handed?
How are you so sure that I'm empty-handed?
You don't have it.
Back then and even now,
you don't have what it takes
to face Chairman Kang.
That's for the hospital bills.
Tell me if you need more.
Don't waste your time…
on misplaced sympathy.
I just came for a short hospital visit.
Don't get any wild ideas.
I only turned a blind eye
so she'd submit the untampered financials.
It got Chairman Kang off our back,
so she should at least be compensated.
I don't have what it takes?
Then did you use me
because you had what it took?
By throwing me on the task force
and playing dumb about the files?
You were after the same result.
And what did I want exactly?
The girl in there
is someone I used to live with.
What do you know about the guilt
of thinking that I'm the one to blame?
It wasn't your responsibility.
How have you not changed at all
in nine years?
Why shoulder the burden of something
that's not your responsibility?
Because I don't want
to be pathetic like you.
Back then and even now…
you're just a coward.
Auntie, that hurts.
Does it?
Filling in for your mom is no easy feat.
Sorry.
Of course, it isn't.
My mom, Kim Mi-sook, is special.
You're right.
She is special, so she'll wake up soon.
Just like Snow White?
What?
Like Snow White and like Sleeping Beauty.
Mi-sook will wake up.
The life of a princess
is a lonely and exhausting one.
But you have to endure it.
Bom, go to the small room
and read your fairy tale book.
The aunties need to chat.
Okay.
Hong Keum-bo,
you may be intelligent,
but you lack improvisational skills.
Have you thought about my proposal?
Let's clear a few things first.
One,
which slush fund will we steal first?
The one hidden under the names
of the OW award winners.
Don't tell me
you knew about it from the start.
Was that why you asked for a nomination?
Of course.
Do you remember
that obituary on the intranet system?
Of Kim I-gyeong, the OW award winner?
She died.
That puts both you
and your sister in danger.
Now my second question.
What will you do
with the real Hong Jang-mi
during this operation?
Don't worry.
The real Hong Jang-mi
is in a very safe place.
PERFECT FOR COLLEGE ADMISSION SUCCESS!
SANGOL BOARDING CRAM SCHOOL!
How is this even possible?
HONG JANG-MI
Lie low at the boarding cram school
for three months.
No outings are allowed, day or overnight.
Even so, you can't do this.
Why is everyone telling me
that I can't and shouldn't?
Because it's dangerous.
The fear that President Kang's death
might be on me
keeps me up at night.
Do you know how I ended up at Hanmin
after wandering the country?
Song Ju-ran summoned me.
She hired me on the condition
that I spy on President Kang.
And now,
she wants me to bug President Shin.
I knew Chairman Kang would say that.
He's stingy with his own,
but happy to rack up debt
with other people's money.
He'll issue short-term bonds
with a one-year maturity,
then ask to extend the repayment period
by another year or two.
In the meantime,
we'll quietly accumulate more bonds.
And if Hanmin goes bankrupt on its own?
That's a win for us.
What does that mean?
You understood, right?
When a company goes bankrupt,
the bondholders become its owner.
That's why Shin Jung-woo and DK Ventures
are buying up Hanmin bonds.
They're betting on Hanmin's demise,
based on inside information.
They intend to snap up
the company for cheap.
You can't trust any of them.
Forget the ledger,
this is completely out of our league.
I'm going to the hospital tonight
to say goodbye to Mi-sook.
I'm officially rejecting your proposal.
Gosh.
You're home, as expected.
Eun-joo, who used to live here,
called me today.
Eun-joo did?
Is that Auntie Eun-joo?
No.
I do think
what happened to Mi-sook is a tragedy,
but we are a dormitory
supported by the city
that helps unmarried women
achieve independence.
As such, all rules must be followed.
Outsiders are strictly forbidden
in this dormitory.
Even if it's…
a resident's child.
Sorry.
You two must figure out
what will be best for her.
After all, neither of you is her guardian.
I'll go back to the children's home.
So please don't get mad at the aunties.
I have a child here…
We're unable to take in
any more children right now.
I see.
All facilities have been full
since the IMF crisis began.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I was wondering
if you could take in a child.
Thank you. I'll call you back in a bit.
I found a spot.
We can drop Bom off tomorrow.
The RA is right.
We can't be responsible for her.
Don't say that when she can hear you.
How would you pull off a massive task
when you can't even take care of a child?
I knew from the start
that the New Korea Fund had issues.
But I couldn't stop Mi-sook.
No, I didn't stop her.
Because my work was more important.
The fact that I was one of those people
who refused to take responsibility
makes me so mad.
I can't do it.
I'll be your guardian from now on,
just until your mom gets better.
We can't live here together,
but I think we can try something else.
Eat up.
Now that everyone is here,
cheers!
-Cheers.
-Have a good dinner.
-Thank you.
Did our President Shin
date a lot of women in Hong Kong?
All he ever did was work,
so I worried about him.
He would never reveal
his ally's weaknesses.
It's the truth.
His last relationship was nine years ago.
I think he said
they were college sweethearts.
Really?
How classic.
Yes, he's one tidy person.
Wait, was that your sandglass?
Well,
that was a long time ago.
If it was nine years ago,
she must have a kid or two by now.
Yeah, probably.
Now,
I also have exciting news
about President Shin and Nora.
On January 16th,
the two are getting engaged.
Surprise, you two.
The chairman gave his blessing.
Congratulations.
Cheers. You'll be there, right?
Congratulations, you two.
Congrats, Auntie.
I guess you'll really be our family soon.
Congratulations, Ms. Kang.
CLOSED DUE TO A FAMILY EMERGENCY
You know,
our Keum-bo is pretty overall,
but her eyes especially sparkle like gems
because she gets them from me.
If you look closely,
this kid has got gems in her eyes too.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star
-Could it be…
-Your imagination is running wild.
You're wrong.
Sweetie,
can you tell me the name of the woman
who gave birth to you and raised you?
It's Ms. Kim Mi-sook.
Mi-sook…
She's my colleague's daughter.
I brought her here
because she has nowhere to go.
Her mom's in the hospital,
and she's still unconscious.
-My goodness.
-The children's homes are full too.
There are no empty spots.
Oh dear.
I guess the IMF crisis
has more parents dropping off their kids.
I know you're busy with the restaurant,
so I'm sorry to ask you this.
Don't be sorry. We're not busy.
Don't worry about the kid either.
Of course you should leave her with us.
We raised two wild,
unruly sisters ourselves.
By the way,
how'd it go with that young man last time?
You know,
the handsome man
you told us to zip our lips about.
He died.
Bom, have some more.
Yeah, eat up.
Have this too.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Goodness me.
All thanks to Mi-sook's child,
we get to hear our daughter
apologize and thank us.
What's your name?
It's Bom.
-Gosh. Bom.
-Hello, Bom.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
Eat up.
ULLALA CHICKEN
Why did you follow us
if you weren't going to come in?
I needed time to think.
It's cold.
I told you to come inside.
How can I, when your parents think
I'm Hong Jang-mi's senior alum?
Let's part ways here.
Have a nice life.
Thank you for everything, Go Bok-hee.
After being called Ms. Go
and Queen Bee all this time,
I'm Go Bok-hee in the end.
Damn it.
Come on.
I'm not a kid.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Hong Jang-mi.
As of today, you're officially recognized
as a resident of Room 301.
"We're college students."
Bok-hee, wait.
This is pepper spray for self-defense,
and this is your lunch.
Bok-hee, I'm always praying for you.
My mommy prays every day.
Why didn't you stop me?
You'd never be able to
steal that money by yourself.
Are you interested?
Walk me through the plan.
Steal 300 billion won and then what?
Shin Jung-woo is betting
on Hanmin going belly up.
Are you doing the same?
I'm going to save Hanmin.
If you look at
Hanmin's ownership structure,
Oh Deok-gyu has 9%
and Choi In-ja has 1%.
Oh Deok-gyu inherited his shares
after his wife passed away,
while Choi In-ja got hers from Kang
as a part of her divorce settlement.
Kang Nora, his only daughter, has 5%
and so does his grandson Albert.
After Kang Myeong-hwi died,
his 9% went to his father,
which leaves Kang Pil-beom with 48.6%.
So if all the shares
in his family are combined,
they have 68.6%.
Hanmin is basically
a family-owned business.
In other words,
Hanmin is Kang Pil-beom's kingdom.
You've been a goody-two-shoes
your whole life,
so how would you steal
that massive amount of money?
Teach me.
I'm a fast learner.
Unlike Shin Jung-woo,
we'll steal the slush fund
and buy Hanmin's stocks.
That'll take away
Kang Pil-beom's management rights,
and blow up Shin Jung-woo
and DK Ventures's theft.
Then we'll be able to protect
both Hanmin and its employees.
I'm not interested in destroying them
or in saving the company.
Set some aside for Mi-sook's
hospital bills and compensation,
and give me a little hazard pay.
If you can promise me that,
I'm in with Hong Keum-bo.
How much is a little hazard pay…
exactly?
Maybe 10%?
Ten?
Have you no shame?
Hold on.
She'll be stealing the slush fund
and also monitoring Shin Jung-woo…
That's right.
You'll be needing Go Bok-hee
for several reasons.
Based on how you do,
I can give you a discount
and only ask for a one-way ticket to LA.
I'll show you
what "the utmost best" looks like.
You just wait and see.
Let's see what the veteran can do.
You have to request time off first.
Cha is hell-bent on revenge
after that fiasco, right?
I'll have to coax him.
Maybe we should've asked
for help from Nora?
He'd listen to a director.
Why are you so submissive to authority?
Everyone's like that.
Everything about you,
from the unyielding integrity
to the petty pride,
needs to go now.
It's hard to earn money,
but it's even harder to steal it.
Especially in this tough economy.
Amid challenges in corporate management,
the burdens on ordinary citizens
are steadily increasing.
Soaring inflation
that shows no sign of slowing
and the threat of widespread unemployment
are raising fears
of an unprecedentedly cold winter ahead.
This place has really thinned out.
Well, a 40% reduction
is basically half the workforce.
By the way,
can we really trust DK Ventures?
-Why do you ask?
-They're treating this place
like occupied territory.
They summon the division managers
and grill them.
There's talk of a second restructuring,
and the air in the office is tense.
Big Al.
Have you heard anything?
Nothing.
I'm sure President Shin
knows what he's doing.
I hear President Shin was the facilitator
who acted as a bridge
between DK Ventures and Hanmin.
That's why his reputation
has been tanking.
Tell us.
I might not look it,
but I respect kinship.
I don't feel comfortable
badmouthing my uncle-to-be.
-Uncle?
Hey.
-Ms. Hong, this too.
-Sure.
-Ms. Hong, I need four copies of this.
It's all missing.
Seriously?
What's this? I never asked for coffee.
I'd like to take tomorrow off.
I'd also like tomorrow off.
But you see, we can't just do
what we want to do
all the time.
Say goodbye to your day off.
Hold on, Ms. Hong.
Let me ask you something.
Were you close to Director Kang Nora?
I've acquired intel
that you two used to eat burgers together.
Why don't you compile an extensive list
of what Director Kang likes?
Goodbye now.
DIRECTOR KANG NORA'S FAVORITE FOOD
AND PREFERENCES
Will that be enough
for Cha to grant you time off?
You could also go
and make that withdrawal yourself.
Why do I feel like
you're pushing me into danger?
The money in Hong Jang-mi's account
should be withdrawn by the account holder
to avoid suspicion.
Context also matters
in fraud and embezzlement.
Also, I'll be on standby on the 12th floor
in case of an emergency.
There's one person
who could help us with this…
Damn it. I don't want to.
I told you to lose that petty pride.
If you can't do it,
let's make a deal and not a request.
Ms. Song might get
a confirmation call from the bank,
so I'll have Madam Choi
keep her busy with her nagging.
But to make that happen…
KANG NORA
…we need her.
What's taking her so long?
I hear footsteps.
Why did you take the stairs
and not the elevator?
I figured I'd need
to avoid attracting attention
and maintain secrecy.
She's not completely clueless.
I'm just trying to meet your eye level,
big sisters.
You want to see Bom, right?
Yes.
If you fill me in for a day,
I'll tell you where Bom is.
I can totally do that.
But…
what am I filling?
OPERATION DAY
Ms. Hong?
Do you have a cold?
Ms. Hong.
HONG JANG-MI
Auntie?
What are you…
That was so rude of you.
How could you strip me like that?
Strip you?
-No…
-Auntie.
That could lead to a misunderstanding.
Your mask was taken off, not stripped.
It was about her mask.
I see.
I will apologize for that.
I'm sorry.
But you'll also need to explain yourself.
Why were you delivering lunches
with someone else's name tag?
Are you exercising
your right to remain silent?
Ms. Go.
Where's Ms. Hong Jang-mi?
I believe I've mentioned
this several times before,
but we're not friends.
Where else would Ms. Hong be?
I'm sure she's at the hospital
where her roommate is.
She probably couldn't take time off,
so Auntie Nora covered for her.
-Right?
-Right.
He's right.
I have to show up at the IT Division
by three o'clock.
Take care now.
I should get going too.
Is it just me…
or do you seem
particularly interested in Hong Jang-mi?
I can assure you this.
I am most certainly
not interested in Hong Jang-mi.
You got caught by him, of all people?
And your mom? Did you ask her to come?
She should be here soon.
Don't worry about me.
By the way, where did Ms. Hong go?
You have to withdraw funds
from a total of three different banks.
Breaking the large check into smaller ones
makes it harder to trace.
Typically, at lunchtime,
there are fewer tellers working
but more customers.
So they process
deposits and withdrawals quickly
to avoid holding up the line.
That's the time you want to target.
CHUNGSEO BANK
Everyone is saying
you're about to close down for good!
Help me withdraw the funds
from my five-year savings account first!
Hurry up!
My life and my friends' lives
are at stake here!
3 BILLION WON TRANSFERRED
TRANSFER OF 3 BILLION WON!
FARMERS' BANK
CHECKING ACCOUNT
There's one left now.
The one with the largest balance.
I have to do it today.
I mean, do you think this makes any sense?
My Nora is the only one
without an assistant of her own.
She's not some lightweight executive.
Just imagine how excluded she must feel!
This is ridiculous!
Ms. Song might get
a confirmation call from the bank.
I'll be on standby on the 12th floor
in case of an emergency.
Now serving customer number 217.
That's me!
S.J.R. CONFIRMATION REQUIRED
What's wrong?
It says I need to confirm with an "SJR."
Oh, that.
They sometimes use dual authorization
to hide the dirty money even deeper,
so take Song Ju-ran's
authorization letter, just in case.
"SJR."
It stands for Song Ju-ran, my boss.
That's why she gave me this.
It's an authorization letter.
AUTHORIZATION LETTER
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD
HONG JANG-MI
I am indeed Hong Jang-mi.
Yes, we've confirmed your name and face,
but we should be extra careful
with such a large sum of money.
Just a moment.
Madam Choi.
Let's talk in my office.
SPECIAL THANKS TO SHIN YU-NA
FOR HER APPEARANCE
UNDERCOVER MISS HONG
I think that "Captain" knows something.
Who could it be?
We must find them
and get them on our side.
You suspect someone, don't you?
-If it wasn't an insider…
-Yes?
An outsider must have done it?
He needs to get beaten up out there
for him to accept our hand.
And you know what happens next.
Why can't I log in?
Maybe you got banned
for writing something inappropriate?
Hong Keum-bo.
Any updates on Ms. Song?
She'll be on your tail
once she realizes the funds are gone.
Inspector of the Capital Market
Investigation Division at the FSS,
Inspector Hong Keum-bo.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim