INHERITANCE PROPERTY DIVISION AGREEMENT
"Inheritance property division agreement"?
SUN HEE-YEON
Sun Hee-yeon?
Why is the seal
of a dead person stamped here?
Sun Han-gyul?
Who… are you?
Who am I?
Well…
"Sun Hee-yeon."
It's my mom's name,
who you said died in a fire.
Han-gyul.
How did a dead person's seal
end up on here?
I'll explain everything, so calm down.
- People are sleeping inside--
- Is she alive?
I said, is she alive?
What is it? What's going on?
No, it's nothing.
It doesn't look like nothing to me.
Go inside. I'll get you a heated blanket.
EPISODE 9
Eat up, Han-gyul.
Your uncle made gaengsigi porridge
that you like.
Han-gyul.
- I'm off to school.
- Wait.
I need to give you an invite
to my grandma's 70th birthday.
You're going to school? It's too early.
Hey.
Evil Han-gyul.
Why?
"Sun Hee-yeon."
It's my mom's name,
who you said died in a fire.
Is she alive?
I said, is she alive?
I'll pay for the stay.
- There's no need for that.
- I need to take care of it.
I can't stand owing favors,
so this situation's uncomfortable for me.
Let's call it even on this day.
I'll buy you ice cream or something,
so hit me up when you come.
WORLD HISTORY
Hey.
I'm home.
Han-gyul.
Your mind's all over the place,
I bet it was hard to focus on the exam.
Whatever you're wondering,
don't keep it inside, just ask me.
I'll answer as best as I can, okay?
What could I possibly expect from you,
who lied to me for 18 years?
Han-gyul.
Dong-pyo asked me
to help with the party tomorrow.
I have to head out at dawn.
I'll go to bed early.
Okay, get some rest.
We'll talk after the party tomorrow, okay?
Ask me anything
you're curious about, all right?
I'm not going to ask you, Uncle.
I'll ask her directly.
"Seocho-gu, 33-5 Balpo-dong."
What's this?
It's a new marketing trick
from a small-town lawyer with no clients.
LEGAL BRIEFS
COURT RULINGS ON TEACHER ASSAULT
You mentioned
a colleague of your colleague
who got assaulted by a parent.
I put together the legal briefs
and court rulings from cases I worked on.
I thought they might be useful
for that colleague.
I appreciate it...
but I think that colleague
would rather bury it and move on.
Nothing in the world
should just be buried.
Once you bury something,
it's even harder to dig back up.
Then pass along this message.
I'll deal with the mess myself.
Don't forget,
Attorney Choi I-jun...
is always on your side.
Did Sun Jae-gyu make all of this
by himself?
No way.
At first, he seemed like
a total disaster as a bachelor,
but it turns out
he's the perfect husband material.
Thanks.
First of all,
I sincerely congratulate Mrs. Yang Bok-hee
on her wonderful 70th birthday.
Knowing that many elders would be here,
I focused on balancing
both health and taste.
If you look here,
for the marinated flounder,
I used pear juice instead of sugar
to be mindful of blood sugar levels.
As for the jeon,
I used half soybean oil
and half perilla oil
to keep the smoke point down
and bring out the flavor.
Make yourself at home,
there's plenty of food.
Enjoy as much as you like.
One more thing.
I'll grill the ribs on the spot.
LA galbi. Next person. Hope you enjoy.
Next in line.
What's going on?
You haven't answered my texts.
As you can see, I've got my hands full
with all the food prep.
I've been meaning
to discuss something about Han-gyul.
Okay.
How about yukhoe?
Here, grill it yourself.
Ms. Bom, come over for a second.
Did something happen with Han-gyul?
That's the strange thing.
He hasn't asked about his mom at all.
It's a party, so noodles are a must.
Yes, sure.
Here you go, enjoy.
Thanks.
- It's self-serve from here on.
- Sorry?
Geez, there are so many people here.
There's no time to talk.
So, where's Han-gyul?
Is he not here?
He headed out at dawn to help Dong-pyo.
I haven't seen him.
Then where is he?
Look at you two!
Standing side by side like this.
You two look wonderful together.
How is everything?
- Everything okay between you?
- Auntie!
Ma'am.
Saying things like that
could get us in trouble.
Wait!
Isn't that tuna?
There's only one tuna.
Only the fastest will get a taste.
- Really?
- Where is it?
So, have you guys started
working on having a kid?
Ma'am, I'll explain everything later,
so please keep it down.
There's nothing embarrassing
about trying to have a baby.
You're the man of the house,
so you need to work a little harder.
You said you were hoping for a daughter.
Did you just say...
"daughter"?
Mr. Choi, that's not it.
Hey, Bom-sik's mom and dad,
I didn't know you were here.
They come to the clinic together
and are inseparable,
and today's no exception.
All the people
at the market have been talking.
When she buys a pot,
he's there carrying it for her.
What a gentleman.
No, I didn't...
See? I knew it.
What's the point of me staying quiet?
You guys went around
basically telling everyone in town.
Mr. Jeong!
Don't.
You can't break your word--
Han-gyul's uncle,
let's make this absolutely clear.
I, Jeong Jin-hyeok,
swear I never told anyone
that you two were hugging in private.
I've never mentioned the fact
that you got down on your knees,
begging me to keep it a secret.
All the others here
have given their account.
Han-gyul's uncle is...
dating Ms. Bom?
What's taking him so long?
He hasn't called, what the heck?
Se-jin.
Why are you still out here?
The buffet's all set up inside.
Dong-pyo, haven't you seen Evil Han-gyul?
He went to Seoul.
Seoul?
He said he had to meet someone in Seoul.
He couldn't make it today, but he left
a gift for Grandma early this morning.
Right, he told me not to tell anyone.
Uncle! Han-gyul's uncle.
You see, Han-gyul...
Well, he...
What about him?
Sun Han-gyul went to Seoul.
Who is it?
Is that you, Han-gyul?
I'm glad you came.
I'm glad you came, Han-gyul.
I'm sure you have a lot of questions.
Can I ask?
You were alive and well.
So why did you make me live with Uncle?
Back then,
I was...
I was just too young.
I had no idea
what I was doing when I had you,
and I had to raise you alone.
I couldn't earn enough
to even afford formula,
so I left you with your uncle
and went to work to make money.
By the time I came back for you,
the house had already burned down,
and your uncle had left with you.
You seriously call that an excuse?
With a few phone calls,
you would've been able to find out
where I went or where I lived.
Are you saying you haven't contacted me
all this time because you couldn't?
Your uncle
wouldn't let me see you.
I know it was hard for you
growing up without a mom.
But all those years I lived without you
were a nightmare for me too.
But Jae-gyu must've thought
that if I wanted to start a new family,
I had to hide the fact
that you existed.
He thought it was what's best
for both you and me.
How's that supposed to be
what's best for me?
You know what?
I wasn't happy at all,
even when I came in first at school.
Others might have envied my report card.
But I... envied the kids
who were worried they would get yelled at
by their moms for bad grades.
All those award certificates and medals,
maybe Uncle was proud of them,
but I wasn't.
I could see I was using
those things to try and cover up
my insecurity of not having a mom.
May I take your order?
Han-gyul, let's eat something first.
You came all the way to Seoul
and haven't eaten anything, right?
I'll have the truffle oil gnocchi.
The same for him, please.
Is that all right, son?
What on earth is going on, Mr. Choi?
I acted like I was divorced so things
would work out between you and Ms. Bom.
I just gave Ms. Jeong an update
that everything's going well
between you two.
Mr. Oh.
I want to be alone and quiet
like a rock on a hill.
Could you please
go have some tuna belly or something?
Ms. Hye-suk,
why are you looking at me like that?
Seong-tae, have you never been married?
Sorry?
- It's true.
- Well...
Hye-suk, please hear me out.
Let me explain why I did that.
It's because of Ms. Bom.
So, Mr. Choi is interested in Ms. Bom.
I didn't have a way to help.
Then I heard
you're the one closest to her.
So basically, you didn't have
any feelings for me.
Well...
But...
Hye-suk.
Hye-suk!
This is driving me crazy.
I wish we could talk more,
but you didn't tell your uncle
you came here,
so I'm a little worried.
If he finds out you came here,
he might not let you come see me again.
Does that mean...
it's okay for me to come again?
Of course.
Can I really come by?
Is it okay if I give you a call?
Sure.
You have your family around.
Are you really sure it's okay?
You're my family too.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Can I call you "Mom"?
Right.
Her number.
I did what you told me to do.
I swear I did.
I told him I didn't leave him,
and that you wouldn't let me see him.
I told him I did try to find him,
but I just couldn't.
I also said he's my family too
and he can come anytime he wants.
I said exactly what you told me,
every single word.
Your uncle had left with you.
He wouldn't let me see you.
You're my family too.
If you hurt Han-gyul,
even a tiny bit, I won't forgive you.
From now on, whenever Han-gyul comes by,
you smile no matter what.
Whenever he calls,
you answer no matter what.
You haven't been there for Han-gyul
until now, so make it up to him.
Don't ever mention
that you abandoned Han-gyul.
And if he asks...
you blame me, no matter what.
That's the condition for me
to sign the agreement.
You understand?
Yes, I got it.
So that's a promise, okay?
I'm so relieved.
Yes, thanks so much.
Well, Han-gyul just left,
so he should be on the train soon.
One moment.
I've got to go pick up my kid.
So, shall we decide
when we'll sign the papers?
Are you coming to Seoul?
No, it's fine, I can go there. I'll go.
EVIL HAN-GYUL
What?
Wait, why's Han-gyul calling you?
Hey.
Yes.
What?
Yeah.
Okay, bye.
Jjun, give me a ride to Seoul.
Hold on.
So you want to go see Sun Han-gyul?
All the way to Seoul?
I'll tell you everything on the way.
Didn't you say you wanted to beat him?
You said you'd do anything
if I helped you crush Han-gyul.
But he needs me.
Yes, I do want to win against him
and I do want to crush him.
But for now, I have to go see him.
So please, take me there, okay?
Hurry up. Let's go now.
Wow, the bubbles are coming out nicely.
They're floating really far.
Try again.
Here, eat this.
Just sitting here won't solve anything.
Han-gyul used to be that small too.
Have I ever told you?
About Han-gyul
during his school performance.
SHINSU KINDERGARTEN TALENT SHOW
Ding-dong, the bell rings
I ran to open the door
And there was my dad I'd been waiting for
Standing in front of the door
I was so happy that I smiled
And called out, "Daddy"
But his face looked
A little sad today
Did something happen?
Is something worrying you?
Did something...
Han-gyul, I'm here.
Go wrong today?
- Cheer up, Daddy.
- Cheer up, Uncle.
I'm here for you
- Cheer up, Daddy
- Cheer up, Uncle
I'm here for you
Cheer up
Uncle!
People probably thought I was crying
because I was so moved,
but that wasn't why.
I cried because I was heartbroken.
He was growing up
not knowing what his parents looked like.
It broke my heart.
Sorry.
Everything with Han-gyul was so crazy,
I didn't even think about how you'd feel.
Now that people have found out,
you can't be feeling great either.
Laozi once said,
"When life gets overwhelming
and complicated, think simple."
For now, let's just think about Han-gyul.
You should eat.
It'll give you some energy.
Okay, I'll eat.
I should eat.
It's good.
- It's so good.
- Really?
I'm not in the mood to take your call.
Hang up.
What?
- Why you?
- That's exactly my point.
Why do I have to drive all the way
to Seoul to get your nephew?
Ever since he was tiny,
I'd comfort him, carry him, feed him,
and now he's making
my dear little sister go to Seoul?
Even so,
I'm letting you know
since I should update you
as his guardian.
So no need to worry, you punk.
Jjun.
Since when did you start
having feelings for Han-gyul?
Jjun... No, I-jun, I mean, dear brother.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
You and Han-gyul's uncle
already don't get along.
I was afraid talking about Han-gyul
might make you feel even worse.
I'll be around having some coffee.
Call me when you're done.
Will do.
I'll carry this gratitude
with me to the grave.
I promise.
Go on, someone's waiting for you.
This is where you wanted to come?
You really came?
"You really came"?
What are you doing?
Can't you see how hot this is?
Right.
Sorry.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
That darn jerk.
I should've known
from the moment he started sweet-talking
with his smug grin.
You knucklehead.
Ms. Seo.
Hey, Mr. Jeong!
It's you, Mr. Jeong.
Have a seat.
Mr. Jeong.
Mr. Jeong, where did you hear
about that slick jerk?
Well, of course I'd find out,
since I cared.
You were completely head over heels
for him. Why's that?
He's not even good-looking,
just boring and plain,
like a half-chewed rice cake.
My name.
What, your name?
He just looked at me quietly...
and then called my name.
He said, "Hye-suk."
Unbelievable.
Of all things,
I can't believe you fell for that.
When you get past 50,
everything starts to feel blurry.
Life doesn't feel vivid anymore.
But when he called my name,
everything suddenly felt so vivid,
like I was truly myself again.
My senses felt sharp,
like I'd put on a pair of glasses.
My instincts felt alive again.
And just like that,
I totally fell for him.
Never mind what I was rambling about.
Still, thanks for letting me know
and for coming here.
I'm a little drunk.
See you at school tomorrow.
My goodness.
Don't forget your bag again.
You always forget.
Thank you.
I'll get you a taxi. Let's go.
I'm dizzy.
Take care of the check with that.
I got this. How much do I owe?
When I found out my mom was still alive,
I just knew that she had abandoned me.
But... I couldn't bring myself
to accept it.
So I wanted to meet her
in person to see for myself.
It must've been the worst day ever.
Do you know what was even worse?
I'm not hurt because she abandoned me.
Then why?
Because we grew apart.
I only got to see her once,
and now it feels like
I'll never see her again.
Hey, Sun Han-gyul.
You're someone everyone loves.
She's just one person
out of eight billion people on Earth.
Can't you just accept
that there could be just one person
who might not love you?
It's not just... one person.
Geez, who else doesn't like you?
Me?
Hey.
Do you seriously think I came
all the way here to pay for my stay?
Can't you see my outfit?
Can't you see my shoes?
Can't you see my lip tint?
I was afraid it'd look too obvious
if it was too red,
so I patted it on with my fingers.
I tied my hair as if I didn't care,
but I actually followed a video
and redid it three times.
And if I didn't like you,
would I have begged my brother
to drive 400 km to see you?
Are you saying you actually like me?
Wait.
Am I being set up to confess here?
Sun Han-gyul.
I want to beat you.
I want to crush you and take you down.
But I keep finding myself drawn to you,
and it's driving me crazy.
And what really drives me crazy is
that I'm just one
of eight billion people who like you.
It's pretty humiliating
and incredibly unpleasant.
Still, I...
Well...
I like you.
I'm saying I like you.
Hold on.
Did Sun Han-gyul just confess to me?
Thank you...
for saving me from the worst day.
What? Don't look at me like that.
Why?
What?
I'm back.
Hey.
You must be tired. Go get some sleep.
Uncle.
What is it?
Is there something to eat?
You know, like those restaurants
you see on TV?
Is it called a "chandelier"?
There was something sparkling
hanging from the ceiling.
The server was wearing a suit
and asked, "May I take your order?"
Wow.
Looks like your mom took you
to the fanciest place.
I couldn't tell what was what on the menu.
She said, "Give my son what I'm having."
So I got a thing called "gnocchi."
It was this small,
kind of like a dumpling.
It came in a creamy sauce
and was soft and rich.
It slid down my throat smoothly--
I'm sorry.
If I knew you'd be this happy,
I should've let you see your mom sooner.
She told you to call her again
and come see her again, right?
She wouldn't stop telling me to come by
and call her again.
Good.
Go see her often from now on, okay?
I won't.
Why not?
It's too far.
It's not too far.
Just say when.
I'll take you there anytime.
It's not really my thing.
I just tried the gnocchi out of curiosity.
I prefer something spicy,
like gaengsigi porridge.
You got some more?
Of course!
I grabbed some fresh bean sprouts
at the market
and cooked up a big pot.
All right.
- Uncle.
- What?
I'm going out with Se-jin now.
For real?
Turns out, she had feelings for me too.
Hey.
Congratulations, Han-gyul.
Who could possibly not like you?
So, did you confess?
Did she say yes right away?
- We had ramyeon at the Hangang River.
- Look at you!
You're just like me.
- Well done. Congrats!
- Knock it off.
Eat up.
So, you officially became a couple today?
When's your anniversary?
When is your 100-day anniversary?
I don't know.
How could a teacher
who's supposed to teach students
date a parent?
Does this make sense?
It doesn't make any sense.
From a moral and ethical standpoint,
this is unacceptable, isn't it?
Principal, wouldn't you agree?
Well, the school needs to be cautious
about these matters,
but Ms. Bom isn't the type
to do anything wrong.
Yes, I agree.
And Han-gyul's uncle
may have looked rough at first,
but don't we all know
what he's really like now?
Yes, he's raising Han-gyul well
and taking good care of the elders.
Plus, the CEO of JQ Energy
is Sun Jae-gyu, right?
Snap out of it!
Look at this.
Didn't I tell you how I got this scar?
You've all lost your minds.
How can you possibly fall for that thug
and take sides with him?
I swear, just hearing his name
makes my blood boil.
I feel sick to my stomach.
He's tall as a beanpole,
and he looks full of lust.
Yoon Bom.
You've been through worse in Seoul.
All you'll get are bruises.
Stand up tall.
Brace your core.
Ms. Bom.
Do you know why
we have to maintain distance from parents?
Once you start
getting personally involved with parents,
you end up favoring one child,
and the damage inevitably falls
on the other students. That's my point.
Do you understand?
But you favor Choi Se-jin so much,
Mr. Hong.
What are you talking about?
When have I ever favored her?
Don't you remember?
You helped Choi Se-jin's dad
with his election,
emceed campaign events,
and threw yourself
into whatever the governor's doing.
Doesn't that count as getting
personally involved with parents?
No, that's not the same thing.
I was simply lending a small hand
to public service.
You're taking it the wrong way.
In a backwater town like this,
where you can barely find anyone under 50,
if two young people start dating,
you should quietly be happy for them.
Why are you making such a fuss
like it's some huge scandal?
Did Ms. Bom have an affair?
Did she cheat on someone?
Ms. Bom.
If there's someone you like, go for it.
If you want to be with someone,
don't hold back and be with him.
Spring may seem like it'll last forever,
but it's gone in a blink.
Live your life in full bloom, okay?
Thank you, Ms. Seo.
And...
I'm sorry for any concern
I've caused, teachers.
I'm fully aware of the concerns you have.
However, I will never do anything shameful
in front of the students
or neglect my responsibilities
as an educator.
I assure you that such a thing
will never happen.
I promise that, under any circumstances,
I will not cause any trouble
for the school.
So please trust me this once
and give me a chance.
I'd appreciate your support.
Ms. Bom.
Have you been waiting for me?
What if someone saw you?
Most people have already seen us.
Right.
We've already been busted.
I was waiting for you
since I was so anxious.
How was it at school? Was everything okay?
I did my best to explain.
Now I have to brace myself
for whatever comes next.
You don't need
to brace yourself for anything.
If anything were to happen to you,
I'll do whatever it takes to handle it.
So don't worry about anything at all.
Just stay calm and relaxed, okay?
Cover your ears, close your eyes,
and just keep smiling, all right?
That's all, okay?
The whole town knows about us now anyway.
Who cares?
Today, let's...
Don't smile.
...smile as much as we can.
Don't have fun.
Let's have fun, like crazy.
Don't be happy.
Let's be as happy as we can
and go to places we wanted to go
but couldn't before,
without holding back, okay?
Let's go.
BOM LOVES JAE-GYU
Ready? Smile.
One, two, three.
- One, two.
- Hi.
SASHIMI AND KING CRAB
Here, Ms. Bom. Open up.
How is it?
This is absolutely mouthwatering.
Try some.
How is it?
It's so plump and sweet.
Right?
My tongue is crying tears of joy.
Good grief, I can't watch this.
What on earth are they doing
with each hand?
Diving straight into the shell.
It looks so good.
I guess their other hands are busy
doing something else.
Get in there.
It's so plump. Wow.
What? With a parent?
Hasn't she still come to her senses
or is she deliberately
trying to drive me crazy?
After going through that mess here,
how could she go there
and get involved with a parent again?
I have no excuse.
I should have watched more closely.
Who is this guy anyway? What does he do?
It just so happens I know him...
Could it be
that jerk you've been looking for?
That dumb thug who's all muscle
and ran off with your money?
Honey, my meds.
Yes, sure.
Manager, cancel my entire schedule
for next week.
You're not seriously going, are you?
Ms. Jeong, calm down.
Doing this could backfire on Ms. Bom.
This whole mess is your fault,
and you're telling me to calm down?
I should've gone down to Shinsu
to talk to Bom myself back then.
Whether I go there and drag her back
or cut ties for good,
I'm settling this once and for all.
So both of you, stay out of it.
From here on out, I'll handle it.
You should go now.
Okay, go on inside.
I think I can only go if you let go.
I should let go.
Yes, let go.
Why won't my hand let go?
I know.
Strangely, it's stuck.
Then I have no choice.
I'll walk you to the front door
and then go.
What's going on?
It's still stuck.
Did we hold on for too long?
In that case,
I'll just walk you to your bedroom door,
and then I'll leave for real.
You didn't just walk me to the door.
You brought me inside the room.
I don't think there's anywhere else to go.
Right.
I let go. It came off.
We managed to let go, didn't we?
Right.
We let go.
Don't step out, it's late.
I'll go by myself.
Ms. Bom.
Did you just stop me from leaving?
Me? When?
Maybe you got caught on the doorknob.
There's no doorknob here.
Then was it a nail? Or maybe a hanger?
I thought maybe
you didn't want me to leave.
Who? Me?
So, are you saying you want me to leave?
Why would you say that?
I'm just saying that your clothes
probably got caught on something.
It doesn't mean I wanted you to leave.
So, you mean you wanted me to stay?
Well, it's not like
I specifically wanted you to stay.
I see.
But...
on second thought,
maybe staying isn't such a bad idea.
Maybe you should go today.
I see.
What I mean is...
I want to be with you,
but at the same time,
I feel like we shouldn't.
It's not like I want you to leave,
but maybe leaving is the right thing,
you know...
If you can't decide, I will.
Han-gyul.
I can't come home tonight.
BOM-SIK'S HOUSE
Did you sleep well?
Yes. I think I slept well.
Glad to hear it. I slept well too.
Why is that vase there?
Wait.
Stay in bed a little more. I'll clean up.
44-5 HAEEUN-GIL, SHINSU-EUP, JUAN-GUN,
GYEONGSANGBUK-DO
I'll find out what kind of person
that Sun Jae-gyu guy really is.
Jae-gyu. Oh, my!
Why are you here, Mom?
- You have a kid.
- He's my nephew.
How could you meet a guy like this
in a nowhere town?
Ms. Jeong.
Ms. Bom, listen carefully
to what I'm about to say.
Who are you, following me like this?
Ms. Bom!
Han-gyul's uncle got hit by a car
and has been taken to the hospital.
Translated by UGKim