ENDURE
AND YOU'LL SOON REACH THE SKY
WHAT MAKES US TRULY HUMAN
TREATING OTHERS
WITH KINDNESS
AND CARE
Why are you here?
Enough already, Yoon Bom.
It's the same dream for over a year.
It's about time I got used to it.
Time to start another gloomy day.
Don't smile.
Don't have fun.
Don't be happy.
You've got this.
Just when we thought
spring had arrived, winter returned.
Last week was unusually warm,
but a late cold snap
is moving in this week.
As cold air pushes south
from the northwest,
a nationwide cold wave warning
is now in effect.
Temperatures in most areas are set to drop
over ten degrees from yesterday morning.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
You know Ms. Bom?
She's been here for almost a year,
and I've never heard her talk.
I just don't get it, I really don't.
No matter how much time passes,
all she does is nod or sulk all the time.
She's always in those dull, dark clothes.
What's her deal?
I guess she's not much of a talker.
As if.
I never listened to my parents as a kid.
One day, when I was five,
my dad put me in the car
and dropped me off at an empty lot.
My goodness.
He said I wasn't his daughter anymore.
So what did you say?
I said, "Mister, drop me off
at the orphanage
instead of here, please."
Every time I spoke,
I totally slayed the audience,
so they called me the Story Slayer.
People said seeing the ethics teacher
gave them unethical thoughts,
so they called me
the Goddess of Temptation.
ETHICS GODDESS
There's something off about her.
I mean, the teachers here
are trying to leave for Seoul.
Why would she come to this countryside
on her own?
It's clear as day.
If she's here as an exchange teacher,
she's stuck for two years.
She must've caused some major trouble.
You'd know more than us, right?
She at least talks to you sometimes.
Not really. She only talks to me
when she's paying rent.
Trust me, it's best you don't know
for your own peace of mind.
Hello, Ms. Yoon.
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Hello.
- Hey, twins.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Hurry, get going.
- Hi, Ms. Bom.
Han-gyul!
Yeah, thanks.
Every time I see him,
it brings back memories of my school days.
- Right?
- Yeah, right.
He's in the same class as my twins.
How can they be so different?
I can't believe they're mine.
If that's how their mom sees them,
what about their homeroom teacher?
Hold on.
Han-gyul, look at me.
Stop pushing.
Han-gyul, come with me. Han-gyul!
- Good morning.
- Hey, Han-gyul.
I have a question for you, sir.
For me?
Follow me.
Wait, did the front door
lock properly today?
I've got a spare key.
If it acts up again, just let me know.
Let's all thank the teacher.
Thank you for today!
Midterms are already
just around the corner.
Starting tomorrow,
students won't be allowed
in the staff room.
Teachers, please make sure
- the exam papers don't get leaked.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sure you all know
that parent-teacher conferences
happen right after midterms, correct?
Yes, sir.
Homeroom teachers for each grade,
make sure to prepare in advance.
This Thursday, there's going to be
a midterm training session.
Everyone must attend the meeting
during lunch in the multipurpose room.
Please be on time.
- I'll take attendance.
- What's this?
Is the window open?
During exams,
both teachers and students are busy.
But this is the first written test
of the year.
I ask all teachers
to do their best to ensure
everything goes smoothly--
Emergency!
What's going on?
This is a strange feeling
I've never felt before.
He's coming.
What do we do? He'll be here in a minute.
Mr. Hong!
Tell him I'm gone for the day.
Out of the way.
- Mr. Hong!
- Hurry!
Get out of the way.
Quick, hide.
NO STAFF ROOM ENTRY
Is he here already?
There we go.
Move, get out of the way.
Darn it.
Don't come.
Who could that be?
The fabric appears
to be 84% polyester and 16% elastane.
Despite the snowstorm, his bare skin
doesn't even have goosebumps.
Is he an athlete?
No.
An athlete wouldn't have
a dragon tattoo on his arm.
Then, is he a gangster?
A thug? Or a local lowlife?
Welcome, Han-gyul's uncle.
Is that guy Han-gyul's uncle?
Sorry to bother you.
I'm here to see Mr. Hong Jung-pyo.
Oh, dear.
I'm afraid Mr. Hong had to take care
of something, so he left early.
Then I'll wait until tomorrow.
I've got plenty of time.
Goodness! Who do we have here?
Isn't this Han-gyul's uncle?
You were there?
I was busy with an urgent memo.
I'm sorry I didn't say hi sooner.
Welcome, Han-gyul's uncle.
I'm glad you're here.
What brings you to the school?
Apparently, Han-gyul
had been chosen
for the Filial Piety Award.
But he heard it was canceled
and asked Mr. Hong why this morning.
This is what Mr. Hong told him.
"A kid with no parents has no business
winning the Filial Piety Award."
So I came to have
a one-on-one talk with him.
Come on,
there's no way he actually said that.
Maybe Han-gyul exaggerated--
He would never say
anything like that to me.
I heard it from someone else.
Please calm down.
Coffee. Let's have some coffee.
Ms. Bom, a cup of coffee here, please?
Do you make
the female teachers fetch coffee?
Well, I feel like
I should offer you something.
I'll get my own coffee.
Beauty.
Where are you?
I haven't heard from you lately.
You've got a real knack
for getting on my nerves.
Did I scare you?
I've been calling you, but
you didn't hear me and kept texting.
Do we have anything to talk about?
Some of us are having tteokbokki,
let's go together.
What's she saying? Is she coming?
Move your head, will you?
I can't see!
You move yours.
Who gave you permission to cut in line?
She's leaving.
- She's gone.
- I knew it.
I told you.
She said no?
Geez.
Hey.
You're a freshman. Why are you here?
Without me,
who else would manage your fan club?
I was hoping to eat with Choi Se-jin
for the first time.
Why didn't she want to come?
My existence.
I prefer eating with someone I like.
I don't want to ruin
my precious meal with your existence.
I hope you understand.
Your existence?
What did I tell you?
It should've been
my existence there from the start.
Anyway, I think
she's the only girl in school
who doesn't like you.
Hey, your uncle's at school.
What?
Han-gyul, I overheard
what Hong Jung-pyo said to you earlier.
I happened to mention
that your Filial Piety Award got canceled.
Gosh, dang it.
Han-gyul!
How about a cigarette instead of coffee?
Why don't we go by the wisterias
and smoke a cigarette? Sound good?
Are you seriously smoking at school?
Sorry?
What the hell?
Smoking where students study?
Oh, my goodness.
I was just joking.
Let me ask you something.
How is the Filial Piety Award decided?
Well, the thing is...
I know Han-gyul is always
a respectful kid and a nephew,
but by the usual definition,
the award is meant for a child
and the parents who raised them.
Pneumococcal vaccines.
How many times do you get them?
Pneumo...
There are four shots.
At two, four, six,
and twelve months old.
On September 30th, 2008,
Han-gyul had his third shot.
After that shot, he ran a high fever.
He burned up to 38.4 degrees Celsius.
The pharmacy was closed,
and I had no one to call.
I carried that tiny kid
and ran the whole 5 km to the ER.
That must've been tough.
When my twins got
their pneumococcal shots...
On December 28th, 2013,
Han-gyul lost his very first tooth.
On October 19th, 2014,
he rode a bike for the first time.
His first day of elementary school
was March 2nd, 2015.
March 4th, 2024,
was his first day of high school.
You all remember he delivered
the entrance oath as student rep, right?
Yes, sir.
So, tell me.
Sorry?
If not me, who's Han-gyul's parent?
Who else could it be?
Is that what a gangster looks like
when he has logic?
I can't believe he made that oath
for this stupid school
that treats people unfairly.
You seem busy,
so I'll just leave it at that, okay?
I can't live like this.
I just can't.
Mr. Hong, he left.
You can come out now.
That fool won't quit running his mouth.
I was aware Han-gyul
was living with his uncle
after his parents passed.
How can someone like him
be Han-gyul's uncle?
Is he maternal or paternal?
Are they really related?
Do they have the same genes?
What does he even do?
Wow, you sure know how to talk.
Tell me about it.
What do you think he does?
He's obviously a gangster.
Let's go!
Yes, boss!
He's always surrounded by his gang,
doing who knows what.
What do you mean, "gangster"?
He's just a thug.
One time, I was drinking with some friends
at the local health center,
and he suddenly stormed in.
Why are you here?
A whole goat?
I checked it for my kid today,
but the color looked so thin.
It only looks like half to me.
Well, black goat tonic
gets thicker or thinner
depending on the ingredients...
If something rubs him the wrong way,
he smashes things.
That's nothing.
When we came back from hiking last time,
he was digging away that night,
sweating buckets
like he was burying a body.
I saw him too.
I saw my neighbor's car.
He was lifting it up like this.
He lifted the car?
- Yes.
- With his bare hands?
Yes.
Lifting a car is nothing.
When he's mad,
he could even smash the whole world.
I feel humiliated
that I was convinced by his logic
even for a moment.
I heard that Han-gyul lost his parents
when he was little
and was raised by his uncle,
never even knowing
what his parents looked like.
- Is everything okay?
- Hey.
Does this look okay to you?
He's got nothing better to do
than come and wreck school property?
Tell him to stop coming to school!
That's enough.
I didn't tell my uncle
because I knew he'd overreact.
I'm sorry.
What needs to be done needs to be done.
Once something's buried,
it's tough to dig it up later.
Everything's fine, so don't worry.
READY-MADE CURRY
Sweetheart, where are you?
Is everything all right?
I made your favorite chicken soup, Bom.
I wish
I could enjoy it with my daughter.
Whatever the reason,
I shouldn't have said that to you.
Ms. Seo, are you home?
I need a spare key.
Yikes.
What's wrong with the streetlights?
It's that guy.
What is that?
What do you think he does?
He's obviously a gangster.
He was digging away that night,
sweating buckets...
If something rubs him the wrong way,
he smashes things.
Were you trying to call the cops?
Please don't kill me.
I can't die now.
There's too much left unresolved.
If I had to die, better in Seoul.
At least I'd get a decent funeral.
If I end up dying here
after cutting off my parents and friends,
no one would come to my funeral.
Plus, getting stabbed to death
on a country road?
There would be
a lot of grim talk at the funeral.
What do you mean, stabbed?
- With this?
- Oh, no!
A 30 cm spicy chicken skewer.
Near the dental clinic
at Shinsu Intersection.
I didn't know about your tastes.
I had no idea you were
into chicken skewers.
You were running down an empty street
at night with that in your tattooed arm.
I got it as a gift from the gas station
since I'm a regular.
One shouldn't throw away a gift.
I just moved from Seoul,
so I'm not familiar with the area.
Well then, take care.
Is that your place?
Go on inside. It's not safe outside.
No.
You go ahead. The door's kind of broken.
I'll sort it out,
so please don't worry about it.
No.
This isn't my place, it's rented.
I'd have to pay for the damage.
No, don't do it.
Wait, stop!
I heard the sauce is what makes it good.
I'm leaving
before this skewer gets cold.
But you'll definitely
pay for your mistake.
Crap, I'm late.
ACADEMIC EXCELLENCE AWARD
FILIAL PIETY AWARD
Is Uncle not back yet?
He's not picking up again.
- What took you so long?
- Did you get reported again?
Here. I'm so hot.
I don't need to eat it.
Why'd you run to town
in the middle of the night?
This is it.
My favorite spicy chicken skewer.
Thanks, Uncle.
You like it that much?
Boss,
I'm pretty sure
there isn't a speck of dust.
You wiped it before going
to get the chicken skewer.
"Filial Piety Award, Sun Han-gyul."
"This student is hereby awarded
this certificate
for exemplary filial piety and respect
for elders, serving as a role model
for others."
- Phillip.
- Yes?
Out of all these awards,
this one's my favorite.
Have I ever told you?
Ever since he was a kid,
Han-gyul has won tons of awards.
I used small awards
as trivets for hot bowls,
and silver medals--
"To prop up wobbly dressers."
Have I told you?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Sometimes you rephrase it to say
they were used
for wobbly bookshelves or beds.
What was your homeroom teacher's name?
I told you, it's Yoon Bom.
Yoon Bom.
She's from Seoul, right?
Uncle.
Whoever my homeroom teacher is,
don't worry about school stuff.
I'll manage it myself.
When you tell me not to worry,
that's when I worry the most.
A kid needs to act up sometimes
to make raising them worthwhile.
If I didn't care about you at all,
how could I even deserve these?
Okay.
From now on,
I'm going to say whatever I want
and ask for whatever I want,
so you have to say yes.
Sure, whatever you want.
I'd bury or stab anyone.
Hell, I'd even kill if you said the word.
Come on, Uncle!
Eat that. I'll go take out the trash.
Let's go, Phillip.
Sure.
Boss.
Did someone report you?
With that car damage incident before,
you can't get reported again.
I didn't get reported,
- but I got ignored.
- Ignored?
She really didn't recognize me.
Beauty.
She made the mistake
of not recognizing me today.
I'll make her pay for that somehow.
What are you looking at?
Phillip.
Cherry blossoms have bloomed.
I guess spring is here.
You've never liked spring.
You said nothing beats
the coolness of winter
and spring just makes you itchy.
Let's see
if I start liking spring.
PURE SPIRIT BRIGHT DREAMS
SHINSU HIGH
MOTTO
SWEAT NOW, CRY LESS LATER
- Hey.
- What?
I'm sure you all know
that parent-teacher conferences happen
right after midterms, correct?
Dae-han and Min-guk,
with their parent in the staff room.
TOTAL SCORE, NUMBER OF STUDENTS, GRADE
Se-jin, whose parent is the governor.
And Han-gyul, whose guardian
is out for revenge.
Ms. Yoon, is my little brother
in last place?
We came out of the same womb,
why are you acting older?
Who was last on the last mock test?
Quiet.
You all know
parent-teacher conferences start
right after midterms?
Yes, ma'am.
I'll reach out to parents
to set up dates from today.
Ms. Yoon.
Parents don't have to attend, right?
What are you talking about? They have to.
But Han-gyul's parents aren't coming.
That's because Han-gyul...
Let's talk about this later, okay?
Ms. Yoon.
Please?
It's not like you don't have parents.
It's basically like not having them.
As you know, my dad
has got his hands full
with his re-election campaign.
- What about your mom?
- She's even busier
because of the campaign work.
In that case,
I'll adjust to your parents' schedule.
All right?
A daughter shouldn't stand
in the way of her parents.
I'm sure you know what it's like
to live under your parents' name.
Push back the meeting by a few days.
No, that can't be.
There's no way she'd know.
Sure, I'll look up info
on art school applications
and go over it during the meeting.
Sure, 7:00 p.m. on Tuesday.
I'll see you then. Thank you.
SUN HAN-GYUL, 2ND YEAR, CLASS 1, NO. 11
GUARDIAN: SUN JAE-GYU, UNCLE
You'll definitely
pay for your mistake.
Try to schedule a meeting
with Han-gyul's uncle
for the latest date possible.
Keep dragging it out
and make it through the end of the week.
No way.
Ms. Bom would never do that.
She's been in Seoul for six years
and has met all kinds of parents.
Why would she be scared
to put off the meeting?
Am I right?
See? She said I'm right.
Do you know what this is?
This is the scar Sun Jae-gyu gave me.
He slashed me
with a piece of glass this big!
You just don't know what he's capable of.
Last time, he let it slide
because the female teachers were watching.
But meeting with him alone?
Who knows what he'll do or how he'll turn?
I'm staying out of this.
Handle it yourself.
Even a lowlife wouldn't treat
his nephew's homeroom teacher like that.
And it's not like
Ms. Bom made a mistake with him
the way someone else did.
Here we go again.
Listen.
The more you delay this,
the harder it gets.
Go on, pick up the phone.
Fine, call him.
He's likely picking on people
for money at a market.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Boss.
Who's the owner here?
You can't just show up like this.
We talked on the phone already.
I promised we'd pay you back next month.
Ma'am, we're not that kind of people.
Do you accept groups?
Sorry?
What's the current situation?
How much tteokbokki is left here?
Is there enough for all of us?
Honey, no more customers today.
Yes, we have enough.
Have a seat.
Let's take a seat.
Yes, sir.
This is our first meal since last year's
pork bone soup place, right?
I haven't eaten since yesterday.
I did an enema just so I could eat this.
Take your time picking.
Yes, ma'am!
Why do you keep following me?
Who's calling at lunchtime?
Well, I'm...
I'm Yoon Bom, Han-gyul's homeroom teacher.
Hey.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
I'm calling to ask
when you'd be available
for the parent-teacher conference.
- I'm on my way now.
- Right now?
He's coming now?
Mr. Hong, Ms. Jeong, pack your bags.
If I run, I'll get there soon.
I can eat later.
I'm scared. Let's get out.
No, you can't come right now.
I just called today to schedule a time.
I believe it's best
if I go through what Han-gyul wrote first
and have a meeting later.
I'll have to wait.
Yes, how about 4:00 p.m. next Monday?
What do you like?
Sorry?
If there's nothing, I'll bring whatever.
Sure, I'll see you next Monday...
Go ahead and order.
Ms. Bom.
Brace yourself.
We're only halfway through the semester.
To manage the whole year,
you've got to hold your ground.
If you need anything, let me know anytime.
Oh, my goodness. This is bad.
So,
you got caught trying
to report Han-gyul's uncle?
I have to stay strong.
If something happens at this school too,
I have nowhere to go.
And now I've been told
I'll pay for my mistake.
I knew it.
You got into big trouble in Seoul
and came here, right?
What kind of trouble was it?
How should I deal with him?
Is there a way I can win?
Has anyone ever beaten him?
Who in this town could ever beat him...
- Yes, there is.
- Really?
Yes, I've seen it once.
Han-gyul's uncle didn't make a sound
and completely froze
at that person's words.
I'd like to meet that person.
Wow, this is tasty.
Someone here can beat him?
Order first.
I'll have the spicy squid and pork.
One spicy squid and pork
and a soft tofu stew, please.
Please make the tofu stew mild,
and skip the green onions.
And a smaller serving of rice--
Are you seriously
out of your freaking mind?
Don't test me,
I'll knock your teeth right out.
I'm working my butt off,
and you pull that crap?
I'll slam that stupid mouth shut.
You take what you get.
Some scrawny little thing
shows up, acting picky
and demanding this and that? Please.
I'll slap your cheeks off your face.
I'm not serving you.
Eat spicy squid and pork
or stop yapping and get lost.
Get lost.
Two spicy squid and pork.
Damn it, today's rough.
Han-gyul's uncle couldn't have
soft tofu stew
and had to eat spicy squid and pork.
You think you can do it? Give it a try.
"Some scrawny little thing
shows up, acting picky
and demanding this and that? Please."
"I'll slam that stupid mouth shut."
What the hell? Are you kidding me?
How are you going to beat him
when you're this soft?
I'm not built for this.
I don't think it'll work.
Maybe we should try a different approach.
Then, Ms. Bom.
Let's go back to square one
and revisit what it means to be a teacher.
Right now, I'm thinking
of a true educator of our time.
Someone who left
a lasting legacy in education,
earned the nation's admiration,
and carries an unmatched dignity
and presence.
Who could that be...
DAMAGED HAIR TREATMENT MASK
Exactly, this is exactly
how you should look.
Ms. Seo, this isn't
the approach I had in mind.
I was thinking of something
more strategic, logical, and reasonable...
Ms. Bom.
This style commands such authority
that even Gangnam parents
tremble in respect.
Trust me on this one.
- Is it too tight?
- Yes.
Loosen it a bit.
I don't think I can do it.
MEETING WITH HAN-GYUL'S UNCLE
11TH GRADE
Ms. Yoon, is today your birthday?
You've always worn
bright black, dark black,
dull black, or light black.
Why are you dressed like that?
There's a line in the Art of War by Wuzi.
"Treat righteous forces with respect,
and powerful forces with humility."
In other words,
you treat honorable forces with respect,
but when dealing with bullies
who think strength is everything,
you start by lowering yourself.
In other words, I chose to win by losing.
Are you going off to a fight?
Ethics and Philosophy, page 35.
"Humanity is something
that humans..."
Good luck, Ms. Bom.
- Sorry I have to go.
- Prepare yourself.
Are you all leaving already?
Ms. Seo!
You've got this.
Ms. Seo.
Han-gyul, you heard
your uncle's coming today, right?
Yes, I did.
Then stay for a little while.
You can go with your uncle
after the meeting.
- Ms. Yoon.
- Yes?
"What needs to be done needs to be done."
Good luck.
Wish me luck.
I'm switching off my ego
starting now.
No matter what happens, stay polite.
No matter what you hear, stay calm.
SHINSU HIGH SCHOOL
NO RUNNING IN THE HALLWAY
KEEP RIGHT
SHINSU HIGH BULLETIN BOARD
BUILDING A SAFE SCHOOL
NO SMOKING
Hello?
I'm busy at the moment, so keep it brief.
LAW FIRM SOOJUN
Actress Jeong Nan-hee.
I may be the head of your fan cafe,
but are you going
to make me work this hard?
You need help?
Am I the kind of guy who helps anyone?
One moment.
Thank you.
You do know I'm rude and selfish.
I'll meet you out of loyalty.
Let's talk later.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Attorney Choi.
Mr. Choi, the plaintiff,
has submitted his complaint.
You should've sued that jerk sooner.
Why've you been holding off until now?
There's assault, damages from theft,
and breach of contract.
Right.
The defendant's address is unknown.
If we submit it like this, the court will
order us to correct the address.
Then we can check it at the local office.
Then we can find out where he lives.
Wait a minute. So are you saying
you filed the complaint
to find out where he lives?
Why?
I really didn't want to use this tactic
since it felt underhanded. But...
I've been searching for ten years,
ever since I became a lawyer.
I've gone everywhere I could think of
and checked every place he might be.
But he's nowhere.
It's like
he never even existed to begin with.
There's no trace of him at all.
That's weird.
If he's still nowhere to be found,
could he be dead?
- No, he can't.
Do you know why I'm always fully dressed
in a wrinkle-free shirt,
spotless dress shoes,
and a silk tie that screams success?
Gosh, I know the answer.
You never know where you'll meet a woman.
Because I don't know
when and where I'll run into that jerk.
I'll carve it into his memory.
"Look."
"Even after you're gone,
my life is brilliant."
"Feel it. Your life turned out that way
because you betrayed me."
You know what?
I just saw in your eyes
a kind of madness that comes with success.
He has to
see it too.
He picked the wrong person to mess with.
PLAINTIFF CHOI I-JUN
DEFENDANT SUN JAE-GYU
ADDRESS UNAVAILABLE
So please be alive, Sun Jae-gyu.
Wait until
I find you.
SUN JAE-GYU
It's great to meet you properly.
I'm Yoon Bom, Han-gyul's teacher.
Hi. Here.
Sorry, but I'm not allowed
to accept gifts.
It's not a gift, it's compensation.
The staff room plant broke because of me.
I see.
No way.
Your hands could break too.
Over there.
- Please put it down over there.
- Sure.
MAY SHINSU HIGH SCHOOL BECOME RICH
- Please have a seat.
- Sure.
It's too small.
Let's start the meeting.
We should do this face-to-face.
No, that's not necessary.
Well...
I saw the counseling form, and it says
Han-gyul doesn't plan on going to college.
You're from Seoul, right?
I'm half Seoul-born.
- Half?
- Yes.
My mom's from Seoul.
I grew up hearing the Seoul dialect,
so I can speak it well.
I see.
Hi, I'm Sun Jae-gyu.
Do you want to be my friend?
I sound like someone
straight from Seoul, right?
I speak two languages, bilingual.
I see.
But in my opinion,
given his grades, I just can't understand
why he wouldn't go to college.
If he's not interested in college,
finishing high school will do.
As you know, our school's college
admission rate wasn't great last year,
and the school
has high expectations for Han-gyul.
He knows what to do about that.
How's he with his friends?
Does he respect the teachers?
No doubt about it.
His friends and younger students
follow him,
and the girls follow him
a little too much.
That's great.
That's all I needed to hear.
So,
let's focus on academics
rather than his social interactions.
How old are you?
You keep asking personal questions.
In a parent-teacher meeting,
that kind of...
Last name, Yoon?
A one-syllable name?
Yoon is your last name,
and Bom is your first?
Yes.
If you look
at Han-gyul's report card, his grades...
His grades...
Here, his grades...
Bom.
Boss!
Who eats tofu outside a police station
this early in the morning?
What a killer view.
Why are you peeking at me?
I'm busted.
Wanna go watch a movie?
You're dying to have coffee with me.
Exchange teacher? What's that?
She's going back to Seoul.
What? When? Why?
Where's Han-gyul?
- Seoul.
- Are you sure he's here?
I'm on my way. Wait right there.
Translated by: UGKim