EPISODE 6
What is it, then?
If it's not because
I might cross the line,
what made you that angry?
Ten seconds.
Nine seconds.
I was afraid I might cross the line.
So, what you mean is…
that you want to cross the line with me?
No.
I mean that I will not cross the line
with you.
Goodness, you Seoul people have
such a strange way of talking.
Why do you not want to cross the line
with me?
Hello?
I'm in front of your place.
Come out for a bit.
Why won't you answer my texts?
That makes me miss you more.
How on earth did you know where I live?
Don't do this ever again.
Or I will report it.
Report it?
But…
you're the one
who hit on me first, no?
You said you liked me first.
I mean,
you said you liked a caring guy like me!
Ms. Yoon!
I made two promises to myself
when I came to Shinsu.
First,
"I will not get involved
with a parent again."
Second,
"I will never get involved with a parent."
So,
nothing can happen between us
because I'm your student's parent?
Yes.
What if I'm not a parent?
If I weren't Han-gyul's uncle,
would you cross the line with me?
-No.
-Yes.
"Yes"?
-No.
-Yes.
-"Yes"?
-Oh, no.
You see, my brain clearly meant to say no,
but this darn mouth
keeps saying anything it wants.
I think my neurotransmission system
is seriously malfunctioning.
I'll wait, then.
What?
But there are still two years left
until Han-gyul graduates.
Two years will go by fast.
In days, from today,
it's 620 days.
In hours, it's 14,880 hours.
And in minutes… How many?
It's 892,800 minutes.
It's long.
It is long, but--
It's like waiting for a soldier
to be discharged.
You think
waiting for two years would be easy?
Of course not.
Well, if I did what I usually do,
we'd have coffee
and go to the movies together.
We'd celebrate our special days,
and I'd hold your hand and hug you.
But if you don't want, I'll never do it.
I've been waiting for Yoon Bom
for 36 years,
so what's two more years?
So...
trust me.
But the day Han-gyul graduates,
let's meet here again.
That's the day
Sun Jae-gyu and Yoon Bom become
a couple.
Okay?
Who are you fighting with?
The air?
Sun Jae-gyu's nowhere to be seen,
and all the others have left.
Why are you working so hard alone?
What's a single guy to do at home
except play video games?
What about you?
Why are you still here at this hour?
Those drama shows aren't that fun anymore.
Watching this live here is much better.
Well, suit yourself.
Excuse me?
Are you a new student?
It's closed for today.
Oh, hello.
We just opened an office upstairs,
so I brought some rice cakes.
It's Choi I-jun Law Office.
Isn't Choi I-jun
Choi Se-jin's older brother?
Yes, that's right.
Goodness.
Thank you.
I'm Oh Seong-tae, a paralegal.
I'm Seo Hye-suk.
-Have a seat, please.
-Okay.
Legal counseling
on criminal and civil cases.
Family lawsuits and divorce cases
are also welcome.
I think when it comes to divorce,
she's better than you.
What are you doing?
Why are you humiliating me
in front of a stranger?
Why is divorce...
a humiliation?
Sorry?
Actually, I'm divorced too.
Really?
I mean, since you're fashionable
and smell good,
I thought you were a bachelor.
Are you divorced?
Yes. I thought you were a bachelorette
at first too, Hye-suk.
Oh, my goodness.
He's calling me Hye-suk. Oh, my.
By the way, when did you get divorced?
In 2017.
March 2017 for me.
May for me.
Settlement? Lawsuit?
-Lawsuit.
-Me too.
My goodness. We divorced the same way!
I think we're on the same wavelength.
Yes!
Where is this rice cake from?
It's so tough.
Of course rice cake is tough.
What, should it be crispy?
Aren't you going home?
Go ahead if you're busy.
Let's go.
I'm going to talk more
with my friend here. You go first.
Hye-suk, what do you do on weekends?
On weekends,
I usually catch up on laundry and…
Nothing special.
I'm new here,
so I don't know my way around yet.
Then should I give you a tour?
Really? Is that okay with you?
I have a lot of free time.
Then I'm going to trust you.
But you can never show it
in front of others,
especially in front of
students and teachers.
Six hundred and twenty days.
From today on,
Yoon Bom is nothing more
than Han-gyul's teacher.
Don't be kind to her. Don't smile at her.
And never do anything personal
for her. Okay?
THAT WOMAN
What are you guys looking at?
Hurry and take a look.
There. Look at that.
That…
That's the woman I told you
I saw with him last time.
She's so beautiful.
I think she was born
to delight all of mankind.
Isn't it unbelievable?
Why is that punk Sun Jae-gyu so lucky
to meet such a pretty woman?
I just don't understand.
Did you see that, Ms. Bom?
I've been waiting for Yoon Bom
for 36 years,
so what's two more years?
Trust me.
That's mine.
Whoever a parent meets
is none of your business.
As educators shaping this country's
future, if you have free time,
I recommend that you use it
on your teaching aids and student records.
Well, then.
What's she saying?
What's with her?
What, he said he'd wait two years,
and he's two-timing me?
Or as Ms. Seo said, does he just fall for
every pretty woman he sees?
She's so beautiful.
I think she was born
to delight all mankind.
Well,
I look like I was born to represent
the bleak future of mankind.
I'll show you what happens in Shinsu
when I decide to make myself attractive.
I'm Yoon Bom. Brace yourself, mankind.
Should I wear my hair up?
I'm mankind's goddess from now on.
What happened with her?
It's over.
What's over?
Sun Han-gyul.
Do you...
like me?
I saw the sports festival video earlier,
and you were smiling when I won.
But I just don't get it.
How could you smile?
A thriller suits us better than a romance.
A thriller?
Have you ever heard of Salieri
and Mozart congratulating each other?
Shouldn't we snarl at each other forever
and only smile at the other's funeral?
You mean you can only smile when I die?
-Is that it?
-Right.
Actually, no.
I can't smile if you die.
Without you, I wouldn't get Grade 1
because of the grade ratio.
Sure, it's a thriller.
It is?
Didn't you see at the sports fest?
All the girls at our school
are crazy about me.
Why would I like a girl like you?
You gave it your all
when it wouldn't even affect our grades.
I was laughing at you.
Goodness, why did you do that?
When she suddenly went on
about a thriller,
I got upset and said things I didn't mean.
I couldn't tell her how I feel anyway,
so I'll just bury it and move on.
Men should be straightforward.
Just tell her.
Now that you have feelings for her,
it's too late
to escape that fate.
If you're done, go to school. It's late.
Did things work out with Ms. Bom?
Your uncle manned up and--
-Are you seeing her?
-Two years.
I'm waiting for her.
For two years?
Two years is long enough
for the Earth's temperature to rise 2°C
and for newly joined soldiers
to be discharged.
How will you wait that long?
If the one I like says so,
I do it no matter what.
You know?
Come on, Uncle. Just go already.
It's heavy.
Let me go up to the front gate.
Wow, she's shining.
She looks like a celebrity.
She's so pretty.
What's going on?
What's happening?
It feels like spring.
I love you!
She's a goddess!
Hey. Hi, Han-gyul.
She's pretty.
She's so pretty.
Mr. Sun, I have a question for you.
What? Is he avoiding me?
Where is he going in such a hurry?
-Hey.
-Yes?
Why is he plowing the field like crazy?
Remember what I said?
It seems like he needs something
to distract himself
from all the evil thoughts in his head.
I don't know
if his head is full of evil thoughts,
but I do know
what my artificial joints are saying.
What's that?
They want his head to be
full of evil thoughts every day.
Goodness.
I love him.
I'm Sun Jae-gyu.
I will wait.
I'm the uncle Han-gyul is proud of!
Why is it acting up again?
I'm sorry, Bom-sik.
I'll hurry and come in soon. Sorry.
Darn it.
Gosh.
Hey.
Are you coming from the skewer place?
You left in such a hurry earlier,
so I couldn't ask.
Let's talk after we open the door.
The key is acting up again.
Could you go over the wall
and open it for me like last time?
Mr. Sun?
What on earth?
Wait, Mr. Sun! Hey!
You cowardly jerk!
Darn it.
Han-gyul.
Are you back, Uncle?
Here.
What?
You must've run like crazy.
It's still steaming.
Do you want to drop out of school
and get your GED?
Why would I do that?
You don't want to?
-I don't.
-Got it.
Time machines won't be invented
anytime soon, right?
No.
-According to the theory of relativity--
-Don't.
What are the scientists doing?
They should work harder.
Bom-sik.
He's definitely doing that on purpose.
He doesn't even look me in the eye
or answer me.
You'd open the door for a dog
if it's locked out.
"Tread softly on me as you go."
Thank you.
I did hear from Ms. Seo
that you opened an office,
but I didn't know you take this path.
In Seoul, I used to run
in Hangang River Park every day,
but I don't know
anywhere good to run here.
So I'm trying to find
a good running route in Shinsu.
Actually, I have something
to talk about with you.
Do you have time this weekend?
Thoughts come to you
when you let your guard down,
and make you feel low from time to time.
Don't be a slave to your thoughts.
And don't regard
those thoughts as your true self.
Thoughts are just thoughts.
In order to breathe smoothly,
sit straight.
CERTIFIED LETTER
"Certified Letter."
Wow, it looks good.
"In 2025,
during the Shinsu High sports festival,
-you made the promises listed below."
-Yes.
"One."
If I participate,
I'll join the military again.
"Join the military again."
"Two. At barbecue places…"
Only vegetables.
"...you'll only eat vegetables."
"Three. For the rest of your life…"
I'll call you "honey."
"...you'll call the sender 'honey.'"
Hey, honey.
I actually called
the Ministry of Defense about it,
but they say I can't serve
in the military twice.
But...
as for the other promises written here,
I promise to fulfill them faithfully.
Honey.
On second thought,
I think I can let the last clause go.
No, no. A promise is a promise.
If you're done, can I go now, honey?
I'll get going.
Was the rumor true?
At that house,
did you do that…
to your father?
This is why we can't be friends.
You see, friends aren't
supposed to believe rumors.
They're supposed to trust each other.
Come if you need my help.
I… opened an office in Shinsu.
Well,
you have the right to choose
where you live in Korea,
so you can live wherever you want.
But even if I commit a crime
and end up in jail,
I will never go to you for help.
So you can throw this out for me.
Okay, honey?
Yes, Ms. Bom.
Coffee?
I'd love that.
Then I'll see you there soon.
Why would Ms. Bom call you?
"Honey."
Why would Ms. Bom call you, honey?
Gosh, at this rate, I'll end up
plowing all of Dong-pyo's grandma's field.
I should buy a field for myself.
She doesn't know how I feel.
She keeps confusing me.
What's with her?
Darn it!
There are no CCTV cameras around here.
Then where were you last night, ma'am?
-What is it?
-Dong-pyo, what is it?
Ms. Seo, our house was robbed last night.
-Oh, my.
-Robbed?
This damn thief
took my medal from the sports festival,
the meju I hung in the yard,
and the dried bracken. They took them all.
My goodness.
The thief must be a gourmet.
How did they know
how good your doenjang is
and take all of it?
There are no CCTVs
around your place too, right?
Make sure to lock your doors.
Oh, my. I should warn her.
"Meet a successful professional."
You're treating me to coffee
and even a nice meal at a good restaurant
because of this.
My school is in such a remote area,
so the students can't meet
people from various professions.
MS. SEO HYE-SUK
So we hold a public lecture
for the students every year.
I didn't know my first job in Shinsu
would be a lecture instead of a lawsuit.
I was actually wondering,
why did you open your business here?
November 2020,
a teacher's teeth were damaged
after an attack by a parent.
Because they felt the teacher
failed to stop students from fighting.
And in 2023,
because a teacher gave zero points
to students who cheated on an exam,
one of the students' parents
assaulted the teacher
in front of students.
Why are you telling me this
all of a sudden?
I'm bragging.
Those lawsuits, I won them all.
People get wronged everywhere,
and I'm the only lawyer in Shinsu.
Wow, I've got a monopoly here.
You see, words like "the only one,"
"unrivaled," and "unprecedented"
get me more excited than money.
So if something unfair happens to you,
make sure to hire me.
If it's about you,
I'll take the case, no questions asked.
It looks good.
You told me
about the teachers' lawsuits earlier.
Yes.
This is about what happened
to my colleague's colleague's colleague.
Go ahead.
During class,
one of the students' parents
barged into the classroom.
And…
they slapped the teacher's face…
What? That's my place.
-Hurry!
-He's in there.
Ms. Yoon, where have you been?
What happened?
We were passing by, and some guy was
trying to break into your house.
So we called the police.
What?
Yes, you have the right
to remain silent and…
Stay still!
Anything you say
can and will be used against you…
Why is this punk so strong? Stay still!
I live here.
Did you catch the thief?
His uncle is... a thief?
Ms. Bom!
Even I would think I'm a thief, but…
Do you know him?
I know him,
but I can't say he's not a thief.
Wait, why would you…
Why did you cuff me?
Ms. Bom, today is the day I visit Bom-sik.
I came to pick him up and…
He's the one! The thief is here!
Where are you going? Stop there.
You little punks, get out of the way.
-You go.
-You punks, I'll…
Uncle, he's the thief.
You're dead today.
Come here.
No, no! Get in!
What? We're busy.
In this day and age,
we shouldn't use our legs.
We should use our brains.
It's this guy! Catch him!
This guy in the red shirt.
What?
I have important materials in my phone,
so I'm using a GPS tracking app.
Look here.
The location of my phone
is the thief's location.
That crazy jerk.
Why does he keep following me?
Stop!
Warm sunlight and a gentle breeze.
Doesn't Shinsu feel so peaceful
for the first time in a while?
Yes, but I don't think
that's really the case.
-What?
-Look.
Get out of the way!
Get out of the way! Move…
You…
I'm not a bad guy. I'm…
Isn't that Han-gyul's uncle?
Yes.
What kind of trouble did he cause
that got him handcuffed?
Put it down.
Who are you?
Don't move!
It doesn't make sense.
Why am I an assailant? Why?
Officer.
You can never let him go, okay?
Well, don't worry.
Your registration number?
Hey. What happened?
This woman told me to do it.
What?
3 HOURS AGO
Gosh, I don't have time to wait.
I'm fully booked today.
Gosh, why won't she pick up?
With the door lock in this state,
she might get robbed at night.
What should I do? Change it or not?
It's better to come back
when she's home, right?
Then I'll have to charge you
another trip fee.
Fine, just do it.
I'll just replace it and give her
the passcode. That'll be fine.
Right?
Yes, I should do it
since I'm already here.
That saves me another trip.
I have a lot of reservations,
so it's hard to book me.
I was just changing the door lock
like the owner told me to.
Save, my foot.
What's the number for the police?
Hello? Is this the police?
This is Kim Min-guk,
a future brave citizen.
This won't do. I should go get a crowbar.
Bom-sik.
Bom…
What?
Why is it open?
You see,
the door was open, so I was worried
there was a thief, so I went in.
But I thought there could be
a misunderstanding from the start.
Because the door lock
was so beautifully removed.
Gosh. Then you should've said
you were a locksmith right away.
Why did you run away?
Everyone got you wrong.
Look at the look in his eyes.
He was running toward me,
saying, "You're dead today!"
My knees started to tremble, you know?
I was petrified.
-I couldn't say anything, okay?
-This is crazy.
Lock this punk up if necessary.
And his twin brother, lock him up too.
Why me?
Calm down.
There was a bit of a misunderstanding,
but no one's hurt, so let's settle this…
Officer, wait. I feel weird.
I'm not feeling well.
I think when I fell down, I hurt my hips.
All of a sudden? Why are you…
Do you want to die?
Hey, be quiet!
Let go, you brats!
Goodness, I don't think
I can squat in this state.
If I can't squat, I can't do my job.
What do I do? My wife and kids…
How will I provide for my wife and kids?
Oh, no.
Ms. Bom.
I'm okay. What about you? Are you hurt?
Why are you so reckless?
Reckless?
The police officers were there. Why did
you have to butt in and make this mess?
Don't you know when to jump in
and when to step back?
Ms. Bom. You know what?
If it's about you, I'm always jumping in.
I'll never step back.
If the same situation happened again,
and there were even a 1% chance
that guy was the thief,
I'd go after him. That is…
the Sun Jae-gyu way.
And that's being reckless.
Look at Mr. Choi.
Didn't you see
how he found where the guy was?
Can you please stop using your muscles
and start using your brain?
Hold on.
Why do you keep
comparing me to Choi I-jun?
Because you two are so different.
I wasn't going to be petty and say this,
but what did you even do today,
forgetting about Bom-sik?
Do you think I didn't know you went
to have coffee with I-jun?
You're turning this on me?
This is ridiculous.
What about you?
You mean I can't…
What?
I can't do the same?
What do you mean?
What will you do?
The current situation.
The victim flatly refused to settle.
And the only lawyer in Shinsu
is me, Choi I-jun.
Why aren't you taking it?
I, Sun Jae-gyu, never go back on my word.
Five hours ago,
I told him I'd never take help from him...
even if I ended up in jail.
Ms. Bom…
That little… Darn it.
He's always so reckless. No wonder
there are strange rumors about him.
What? End up in jail?
If you go to jail...
then what about me?
I tried so hard to keep the promise,
but she goes and has coffee
with another guy?
All right.
This place is comfortable. It's better.
It's nice and spacious.
This is nice.
Bom-sik, let's go to sleep.
Let's sleep.
Let's sleep now, okay?
Sun Jae-gyu, out.
CHOI I-JUN LAW OFFICE
"With this settlement, the victim
agrees not to raise objections,
both civil and criminal."
"If the assailant doesn't carry out
the agreement,
he is liable to compensate
for all the damages
caused by it."
Let's make it clear.
I didn't hire you to do this.
You asked me to do it.
SETTLEMENT
But why are you helping me
all of a sudden?
And that guy refused to settle yesterday.
Why did he suddenly agree to settle?
In Seoul, my hourly rate was 400,000 won.
If you're willing to pay me,
I will kindly explain it to you, sir.
No.
What now?
First things first, right?
TEMPORARILY CLOSED
Is he away?
SHINSU LOCKSMITH
Gosh, I wanted to talk to him.
No.
If I want to apologize,
I shouldn't come empty-handed.
Hi, auntie. The sikhye looks good.
Hi.
Well, I…
She's not even curious
about how I got out?
Hold on, miss.
Give this a try.
I made it with the pumpkins I grew myself.
It's really good. Try it.
-It's good.
-Right?
I'll take five bottles of this.
Five bottles?
Goodness. It'll be so heavy.
How will she carry them?
You see, ma'am, so many upsetting things
have happened lately.
So I need to drink this much
to feel better.
-Give me five bottles.
-Okay. Thank you.
Why do my shoulders hurt so much?
Did I sleep funny?
Geez.
She might end up hurting her back.
Goodness.
Oh, right.
Ma'am.
I'm looking for a pot for repotting.
This wide
and this tall.
Do you have a pot like that?
Over there.
Sun Jae-gyu.
Why is that darn tree growing so well
when I don't even water it?
I don't need your help. Just go.
No.
Do you think I'm doing this to help you?
My Jae-gyu pot
isn't being watered properly.
I want it to be in this big pot.
Let's go.
I'll leave after repotting it.
Gosh, it's too late to ask now.
If I ask him about the woman
he met last week,
will I not look nonchalant anymore?
Why did you lay out your comforter?
It's nothing.
Do you have something to tell me?
Well, no.
I was just wondering
what you did last weekend.
I washed Han-gyul's uniform
and made some jangjorim with beef.
Oh, is that so?
He'll never tell me first.
Anyway, Ms. Bom,
do you know that you've changed a bit?
The way you talk is cold as a freezer,
and you make those weird faces.
Unlike the Ms. Bom I knew.
Who are you to talk?
You see,
I thought you were a man of his word.
How could you say that?
Because of you, I got freckles,
and I say a Buddhist mantra every morning.
What are you saying?
Even though I get sunburned,
I'm trying so hard to be loyal to you.
"Loyal"?
Am I someone you try to be loyal to?
Why would you put it that way?
I'm just saying it's that hard for me.
If it's that hard, then break it.
Wait.
What did you just say?
You mean, break the promise?
If you're waiting for me out of loyalty,
then I don't want it.
You know,
I…
What I want is…
All right.
I told you.
I'll never do
what you don't want me to do.
If what you want is to break the promise,
then I suppose we should.
Then take care,
and I wish your family peace.
And I hope all your efforts go well.
Bom-sik.
Daddy's leaving now, okay? Take care.
Don't cry.
Wait…
I guess she doesn't like me.
I was such a fool,
making a fuss over keeping the promise.
SHINSU LOCKSMITH
What?
I wasn't sure,
but something must be going on
with that woman.
That's why he left
without even looking back.
I had no idea and…
Sir.
He may look scary,
but he's not a bad person.
We'll compensate for your injury, so--
Gosh, stop it. Why are you bothering me
so early in the morning?
No settlement. I was very clear.
What's wrong with you, seriously?
Oh, no. They bent automatically again.
Sir, I think there's some sensor
embedded in my knees.
They automatically bend
when I need to apologize.
And since I'm already kneeling,
I'll ask you once more.
If you show mercy just this once…
You want to add obstruction of business
to the assault charge?
Is she gone?
Come on!
From here to there.
I'm here as a customer.
All of the door locks here,
I'll buy them. Here.
What, you got 100 doors at your house?
What are you buying so many for?
My neighbor's house was robbed.
So if they change all their door locks,
it'll be safer. Just do it.
Geez, you think I'd settle
if you buy so many door locks?
Goodness. Not a chance.
Let's see.
LOVELY SONG GA-IN
You must be a big fan of Song Ga-in.
Gosh, who in Korea
doesn't like Song Ga-in?
I wanted to go to her concert today,
but the tickets sold out so fast.
Sir, you know what?
Darn it.
I know Song Ga-in a little.
-For real?
-Yes.
I was very close with someone
who is very close
with her.
She's close with someone
you were close with?
Are you saying
you're close with her or not?
Don't.
Before you're a teacher,
you're Jeong Nan-hee's daughter.
You think people are interested
in your innocence?
What they're interested in
is not the truth, it's gossip.
Look at that. I knew it.
How can you be close with Song Ga-in?
That's just absurd.
You're obviously lying.
If that's true, I'm her brother.
She wouldn't make friends
with just anybody.
MOM
DAUGHTER
I barely fell asleep.
Who calls so early in the morning?
Darn it.
Honey.
What? Who is it?
Answer it.
Now.
Is that you, Bom?
How have you been…
Yes.
What? Who?
No, I'm not saying I can't…
Okay. I'll do that.
You…
Bom.
Bom? Yoon Bom?
She hung up.
What did she say? What's going on?
You know Ga-in. Song Ga-in.
The trot singer at your company?
She asked for a ticket for her concert.
What?
That's how
I closed my shop
and went to her concert today!
Check this out.
Have you ever seen anything like this?
You see, I got this autograph
from Song Ga-in in person.
"May your business prosper,
Shinsu Locksmith. From Song Ga-in."
I bet you have nothing like this.
Of course you don't.
Mr. Sun?
You left saying "take care."
Why are you here?
Why did you do that?
What do you mean?
I just heard all about it
from the locksmith.
I did it because it happened at my place,
so don't read too much into it.
Even if it happened at their house,
who would buy that many door locks?
Who would kneel down for me?
Who would even get him a concert ticket?
Why are you being like this?
You do so much for me without me knowing,
but why do you act so cold in front of me?
What…
Why are you crying suddenly?
You met up with another woman.
Last weekend, I saw you
with another woman.
She was pretty.
So pretty.
I haven't even touched
your fingernail, but…
But you had...
coffee with her...
and held hands with her.
So…
you were mad at me because of that?
You told me to trust you,
and you did that with another woman.
You're right, Ms. Bom.
What?
I, Sun Jae-gyu...
don't keep my word.
I'm not as strong as I look,
and I'm not intelligent, cultured,
refined or patient.
I'm sorry.
I can't wait any longer.
Welcome to our plant, Green Narae!
Something's going on
between you and Jae-gyu? The twins saw it.
He's the best husband material.
He's strong, influential, and rich.
Do you like it?
Why do you keep asking?
-What if we get caught?
-I'll find the perfect place.
-No one's here.
-I told you to trust me.
-Mr. Sun.
-Yes, Ms. Bom.
Can I say what I couldn't earlier?
Translated by Wayne Ryu