Ra Mi-ran
Lee Do-hyun
Ahn Eun-jin
Yoo In-soo
Sam-sik's Mill
Choi Moo-sung - Jung Woong-in - Hong Bi-ra
Seo Yi-sook - Jang Won-young - Kang Mal-geum
Kim Won-hae - Park Bo-kyung
Happy Farm
The Good Bad Mother
Oh Tae-soo
Final Episode
I'll Be Taesocrates Dissatisfied
Rather Than a Pig Satisfied
I'm surprised to see you.
I heard you were badly injured in an accident.
I was surprised too.
I thought it was an accident.
But it turns out,
it wasn't an accident.
Just like how your mistress
Hwang Soo-hyun's corpse was discovered.
Are you here to...?
No.
I wouldn't have bothered to
come here if I was coming after you.
If a prosecutor were to
leak damaging information,
your opposing party...
No.
This entire country would be bent...
on taking you down.
Choi Kang-ho.
I'll be straightforward with you.
I only have one goal.
It's to catch...
Chairman Song, the man who
murdered my father and attempted...
to kill my mother and me.
I want you to testify against him...
regarding all his crimes and corrupt deeds...
you swept under the rug.
Then I won't disclose your crimes.
What are you talking about?
Oh Ha-young.
She's with me right now.
Her resentment and hatred
for you seems quite deep.
If you refuse to testify,
then Ha-young will take the stand instead.
I'm not asking you for a favor.
I'm giving you a chance.
So what will it be?
Will you take down Song Woo-byeok with me,
and become President?
Or will you side with him...
and go to hell together?
The Good Bad Mother
Goodness, you're working hard night and day.
Is our food here yet?
Hotel Captain
Why did you put it back here?
- What are you doing?
- My gosh, you startled me!
What are you doing to our food?
Give it to me!
I was just curious about...
what people at the Prosecutors'
Office have for a meal.
But I guess they're no different from us.
Don't tell me...
you spiked our food.
Hey.
Do you think it's that easy to get drugs?
I'd rather spend that money
on buying myself supplements.
I haven't slept well since you guys arrived.
Look at how haggard I am.
Can you tell?
You should just quit drinking.
Sam-sik.
By the way,
is this what people call an office romance?
What are you talking about? What romance?
The prosecutor and his investigation officer.
They're on fire!
Why are you crying?
Next, tell me what you and your dad
talked about on the day of the accident.
I'm not sure about this.
What? What do you mean?
Even if I claim he made me do it,
I have no evidence.
Then I'll end up taking all the blame.
I know I should pay for what I've done.
But I'm afraid I may not be of any help...
to Kang-ho.
You're already helping him greatly...
by doing this.
He said he'll find evidence,
so let's trust him and wait.
Song Woo-byeok has ties with
the prosecution and the court.
So it won't be easy to get a warrant.
If you attack him without being fully prepared,
he'll catch on to your plan.
And that'll put everyone in danger.
When will you return from the U.S.?
If I could,
I'd love to stay and watch the
World Series before coming back.
Are you saying you'll neglect
the Woobyeok Beasts this season?
You're right.
I must be getting senile.
My goodness.
What a killer view.
I get to see this thanks to you.
By the way,
why are you here alone?
Did you have to do that?
I devoted my entire life...
to serving you, sir.
Did you really have to try to kill me?
What are you...?
Are you crying?
A grown man crying is embarrassing.
Sir, we should get going.
Hey.
If you made it out alive,
you should've fled to
another country to survive.
Why would you come back here
and drive a nail into your coffin?
In any case, I want to thank you.
When I heard you were still alive,
I was hesitant about
going on this business trip.
But now I can leave at ease.
Goodbye, then.
You asked why I came alone.
Mr. Cha will hear everything you just said.
One of us...
must stay alive to expose you.
You douchebag!
You were crying all this time,
and you start bargaining with me...
when it's almost time for my flight, you jerk?
What do you want?
Tell me! You'll be dead soon enough.
Do you need a home? Or money?
Do you want me to adopt
you as I did with Kang-ho?
I had the opportunity to farm thanks to you.
Interestingly enough,
I reaped everything I sowed.
You'll also reap what you've sown.
How dare you?
Die, you douchebag!
- Chairman Song.
- What?
Kang-ho.
You're alive?
My goodness.
I don't care about anything else.
I'm completely fine as long as I have you.
I'm sorry.
But I've only just begun.
Song Woo-byeok.
You're under arrest for special assault...
and attempted murder.
What are you doing?
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
Kang-ho.
Will you be okay?
Please don't skip your meals.
Take him.
So
Hello?
- Hey.
- Let me talk to Choi Kang-ho.
Kang-ho?
Kang...
Hold on.
It's for you.
- Hello?
- Choi Kang-ho.
Run away.
It'll be difficult to obtain
an arrest warrant...
for Chairman Song's past crimes.
That only leaves us with one option.
We need to catch him red-handed.
But I heard he'll be going
on a business trip to the U.S.
When is that?
Here's the plan.
Once I get to the rooftop, I'd
like for you all to accompany me,
and carry out a search-and-seizure
of Woobyeok Group. Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Now that he's back, I'm motivated to work hard.
Recently a victim claimed to
have received death threats...
from Chairman Song Woo-byeok, and
thus we conducted an investigation.
And yesterday at 2 p.m.,
we arrested him at the scene...
at Woobyeok Group's headquarters,
after he assaulted again and
attempted to murder the victim.
Since the suspect attempted
to destroy the victim's phone...
and was due to fly out to the U.S.,
we deemed it likely that he might
try to destroy evidence and flee.
How will you carry out this investigation?
- Sir.
- A civil servant...
must be impartial when serving the country.
As per the Prosecutor General's
words to carry out fair investigations,
even against the powerful,
we'll carry out an honest,
transparent, and thorough investigation.
- What's the victim's current state?
- Did the suspect admit to the charges?
Sir.
It's me, Oh Tae-soo.
Young-soon, hurry up. It's starting.
Coming.
♫ When did you enter my heart ♫
♫ and make me fall in love? ♫
Come on.
- You're...
- My babies.
I brought you some snacks.
Sweet potatoes again.
You don't like sweet potatoes?
Do you want mung bean pancakes?
- That's enough.
- Come here.
Can we please just watch?
Is that the song that Mr. Baek wrote?
That's right.
Apparently the song is very popular
now. What was the title again?
- "Intrusion into My Heart."
- That's right.
- Come here.
- Goodness.
How nice!
You're blocking the TV.
This is great!
Let us watch the TV.
Hold on.
Move aside! You're blocking the TV.
- What?
- What is it?
- What is that?
Song Woo-byeok from Woobyeok Group was arrested?
What?
Chairman Song has allegedly engaged
in assault and death threats...
prior to this incident.
People are in an uproar after learning
that there have been many victims.
Recently a victim claimed to
have received death threats...
from Chairman Song Woo-byeok,
and thus we conducted an investigation.
What am I looking at?
Is that Kang-ho?
Can you slap me?
It's him.
It hurts, so that must be Kang-ho.
It hurts, so that's Kang-ho!
Our son...
Kang-ho is back!
Kang-ho!
That's Sam-sik's best friend,
What is this?
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't trust me?
Answer me!
We're in-laws!
- What?
- "In-laws"?
- With who?
With me!
Right, Mother?
How about...
we all visit Seoul together?
- Sure!
- We must!
Let's go!
Is your seat belt on?
Do you like fish?
Feel free to rest your head on this.
Move.
We could've gone by ourselves.
Why is he here?
Shut it.
If something happens to you
on the way, he'll suspect me.
Easy on the brakes.
I just had them replaced.
I bought this car to drive
to the award ceremony.
It fits five people perfectly.
You're right.
Gum-ja must've become a widow for this very day.
What did you say?
I'll buy a bigger car soon,
so let's go again another time.
That sounds great!
Your son is still considered a suspect.
We still have an eye on him.
I don't want to hear it.
Just keep your eyes on the road.
Yes, ma'am.
Honey.
Are you watching from above?
The day has finally come.
Our son will carry out the judgment...
we failed to do.
Please help him stay strong.
Please help him not to doubt, falter,
or be intimidated.
Let him stay strong.
Prosecutor
Help him look them in the eye...
and state the truth.
Defendant
Just like how you did...
in front of them,
please help Kang-ho...
remain confident...
until the end.
All rise.
With sincerity,
resentment,
and desperation...
I pray to you.
You may be seated.
Case 133 of the year 2023.
We'll now begin the trial.
The assault that occurred
in Jou-ri on January 20...
was just a simple fight between colleagues...
over their pecking order.
Soh Ji-seok's claim that
Chairman Song Woo-byeok...
ordered an assault to be
carried out is completely false.
The recent incident transpired...
due to Mr. Soh's attacking Chairman Song.
And the latter...
simply reacted to defend himself.
Did you just say that the
victim attacked the defendant?
Are you talking about this?
Please play it.
Mr. Cha will hear everything you just said.
One of us...
must stay alive to expose you.
- You douchebag!
- What is that?
You were crying all this time,
and you start bargaining with me...
when it's almost time for my flight, jerk?
I'll submit this as evidence.
I'd like to question the victim who's
also the witness to that incident.
After the assault in Jou-ri, you
came to me for help and claimed...
that the defendant was trying
to murder you. Is this correct?
Yes.
Why did he want to kill you?
Because as his trusted secretary,
I had a great deal of
information about his actions.
The defendant spent about 30 years as the CEO...
of Yongra Construction and Woobyeok Group.
He must've had many employees
who worked closely with him,
and they must've known a
lot of private information too.
Are you telling me they're all dead?
Yes.
Objection, Your Honor.
- It hasn't been verified...
- Right, so I verified his claim.
In the past 30 years,
the defendant had four other secretaries...
who worked closely with him.
Two committed suicide
and one died in a car crash.
And the last secretary's body was
recently found near Jemyeon Island.
It was Hwang Soo-hyun.
Your Honor, the prosecution is
referring to a case that's irrelevant to...
I'm verifying the witness' statement.
How is that irrelevant?
Prosecution.
You may continue.
That's right.
This USB was found at the defendant's office...
during a search-and-seizure.
Do you know what it contains?
It contains confidential documents
related to Woobyeok's corrupt deeds,
Chairman Song's double bookkeeping,
breach of trust, and embezzlement.
It belonged to Hwang Soo-hyun.
What's he talking about?
Hwang Soo-hyun?
Could you explain this video...
found on your secretary's laptop?
Please play it.
Don't be ridiculous.
I already know the hit-and-run accident
and suicide were in the contract.
A year ago, Chairman Song ordered
me to visit Yang Gu-man's wife,
and retrieve his money.
Gosh.
All right. Then I'd like to ask the defendant.
According to the investigation,
Hwang Soo-hyun was last seen before her death...
on October 3, 2021.
It's the same day the last
video on this USB was saved.
So why was this USB found in your desk?
Look.
How would I know anything
about the USB or that Mr. Yang,
when he's the one who schemed everything?
So you're claiming that the
victim schemed everything himself,
and you never murdered or abetted murder?
Correct.
That's a lie!
He also ordered me to kill people.
He ordered you to kill people?
Who were they?
Jung Jong-gu, the defendant
in the murder case...
that Chairman Song's grandson was involved in,
and Park Cheol-su, the defendant in
the Woobyeok construction site case.
So did you carry out your orders?
They were both incarcerated,
so I couldn't.
I found a few odd things
during this investigation.
It's the fact that...
not only the defendant's
secretaries, but also many of those...
who raised suspicions about
the defendant or his company,
or were involved in the trials,
suddenly passed away or disappeared.
Objection, Your Honor. The
prosecution is distorting the truth...
solely based on the victim's claims.
Then let me summon another
witness who can verify this.
Approved.
Witness, Mr. Oh Tae-soo,
please come forward.
Oh Tae-soo?
What is this?
Why is he testifying?
"I pledge this."
"I solemnly swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth,"
"and agree to be punished..."
"in accordance with perjury
should there be any falsehood."
"Witness, Oh Tae-soo."
If Song Woo-byeok is arrested,
Bareun Hanguk Party, the political and
business worlds, and even the media...
will find fault with you.
Because everyone knows about...
your secret ties with him
and how far they go back.
But what if...
you testify against him?
It'd be a perfect chance to
dispel all the suspicions...
regarding the relationship between you and him.
You have indicted Chairman Song many times...
for 30 years since 1987.
- Is this true?
- Correct.
However, most of these
indictments were dismissed.
The majority of these cases,
13 in total, were dismissed...
due to the victims' deaths.
That's correct.
Did you ever find the repeated deaths...
of the plaintiffs or victims rather odd?
There was no issue in the
investigation of their deaths,
and the bereaved families
didn't raise any suspicion.
So I didn't find them particularly odd.
However, I found something odd...
in this trial.
It's the death of Hwang Soo-hyun,
his secretary.
She worked as my secretary...
from 2018 to 2020.
Then one day in 2020,
she told me she wanted to quit.
The reason being...
that getting pregnant
had put her life in danger.
Her pregnancy had put her life in danger?
Correct.
She said Chairman Song was the father.
If you do this,
all the disgusting work...
I forced myself to put up with will go to waste.
I was even willing to serve time in jail...
to make you become President,
you douchebag!
Defendant, please sit down!
How is that baby mine?
Like killing that poor baby wasn't enough,
are you trying to turn him into a jerk now?
You even plotted...
to kill Choi Kang-ho with your daughter!
- You douchebag!
- Defendant!
- How dare you utter such nonsense?
- Please calm down!
You douchebag! I'm not going down.
No, not yet, Honey.
If I waver right now, our son will waver too.
Everything he's done up to now will be ruined.
Please, Honey.
Keep me here for a little longer.
Please...
Just a little longer.
Sit down!
- Sir. Please.
- I ought to kill you.
Darn it!
It's true.
I slipped...
Prosecutor Choi Kang-ho sleeping pills.
We'll accept the prosecutor's request.
We believe verifying the facts
is of the utmost importance.
You may cross-examine the two witnesses.
I was deceived into believing that
Prosecutor Choi, my then fiancée,
had another woman and a baby.
And that he even killed them...
so he could marry me.
Who told you that?
It was my father,
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo.
It's all my fault.
I've been threatened by Chairman Song
ever since I decided to run for President.
He wanted me to protect his corrupt company...
and himself.
When I refused, he attempted
to use my daughter...
to get rid of Prosecutor Choi.
Why did Chairman Song want me dead?
That's because 35 years ago, Chairman Song...
murdered Prosecutor Choi's father.
Is that true?
Simply put,
there were two people Chairman
Song needed to get rid of.
Hwang Soo-hyun, his mistress,
and Choi Kang-ho, Choi Hae-sik's son.
That's why he killed her,
and framed Prosecutor Choi for it.
And after that, he ordered my
daughter to kill Prosecutor Choi.
Stop lying.
It was you who wanted him dead.
It was also you who killed
Hwang Soo-hyun and her baby.
They were your mistress and son.
I saw the DNA test result...
with my own eyes.
This is my daughter's medical
record from the mental hospital.
That's right.
My daughter isn't sane.
I've been hiding it...
in fear that my dear daughter would
be caught in political mudslinging.
Dad!
Dad.
What happened to you?
Who made you like this?
Dad.
It's me.
It's me, Ha-young.
I'm Oh Ha-young, your beloved daughter.
I'm so scared right now.
I'm in so much pain.
Dad.
Can you please stop here?
I beg you.
Please come back, Dad.
Please?
Let's stop here.
Please consider that she qualifies
as an individual with a mental disorder,
as per Article 10, Paragraph 1
of the Criminal Act.
There's another reason...
I helped my father.
It was because...
my father schemed with Chairman Song...
and murdered Choi Hae-sik,
Choi Kang-ho's father, 35 years ago.
Unbelievable.
At that time,
he bribed the detective in charge...
and fabricated the marks on the victim's body.
I believe my daughter is
very unstable right now.
I request that you adjourn this trial.
Witness, please sit down.
The court will decide whether to adjourn.
Taking their testimonies into consideration,
I believe the answer to this case...
lies in the death of Hwang Soo-hyun,
Chairman Song's former secretary.
Witness Oh Tae-soo claims
the defendant, Chairman Song,
murdered Hwang Soo-hyun.
But Song Woo-byeok and Oh Ha-young
claim that Oh Tae-soo killed her.
In addition,
the police consider me,
Choi Kang-ho, as a key suspect.
And it's most likely...
that the baby's father killed her.
Then there's only one solution.
We'll see if the baby's DNA...
matches any of ours.
What's he saying?
Prosecution.
You're not allowed to summon any more witnesses.
The baby...
is alive.
Choi Kang-ho.
You said you'd rather be...
Taesocrates dissatisfied
rather than a pig satisfied.
But you're wrong.
No matter how hungry a mother pig is,
she wouldn't move recklessly
so as not to harm her piglets.
Someone like you who used
his child as a murder weapon,
and heartlessly attempted to kill them,
could never fathom such parental love.
Prosecutor Choi...
is trying to taint my reputation
before the presidential election.
This is a political maneuver and slander.
I'll find out who's behind this
and hold them responsible.
Please sit down.
- I refuse to testify anymore.
- Witness.
Stop, or I'll consider it an attempt
at destroying evidence and fleeing.
Prosecutor Choi Kang-ho!
You jerk.
Oh Tae-soo.
You, and your accomplice Song Woo-byeok,
are under arrest for abetting the
murders of Hwang Soo-hyun and her son,
myself and my mother, Jin Young-soon,
and Choi Hae-sik who died in
the 1988 arson case in Bongu-dong.
You have the right to remain silent.
Hurray!
Hurray for Choi Kang-ho!
- Hurray for my son!
- Hurray!
- Hurray for Choi Kang-ho!
- Quiet down, everyone!
- Hurray!
Breaking news.
This afternoon, Jeilmirae Party's
Candidate Oh Tae-soo...
was arrested for abetting murders.
The prosecution is investigating...
Chairman Song's slush fund worth hundreds
of millions of dollars and the embezzlement...
He colluded with Oh Tae-soo
and destroyed evidence.
And in return, monopolized the
distribution rights for hand sanitizers...
This is the CCTV footage of
the culprit in front of the VIP ward.
Suspect Yoon Jae-min was
found guilty of using drugs and rape.
A retrial was filed after
digital-forensics results...
revealed that the fall of
Jung Min-ho at the construction site...
was in fact the fault of Woobyeok Construction.
The public is keenly interested
in the Bongu-dong fire incident...
and Choi Hae-sik's death.
- Release Assemblyman Oh!
They say you shouldn't bark if you can't bite.
You'll have to resign if
you want to take me down.
So what'll you do?
You're the one who taught me,
"Hit a home run or strikeout."
Now that I've hit a home run,
I'll gladly take a strikeout.
We Believe in You, Assemblyman Oh
Excuse me.
Ye-jin.
"Happy" is spelled with a "p."
Turn the "d" letter upright.
Okay? Try it.
- Gosh, they look so happy.
- Here.
- Here, let me.
- All right.
All right.
- You little brat.
- What?
You should've told me
sooner that he'd recovered.
I thought you'd urge me to
marry him if you found out.
What do you mean?
I didn't want to make you look bad.
Goodness.
Hey, did you hear?
Kang-ho and Mi-joo...
You heard?
I watched it.
What do you mean? Watched what?
The JBC drama.
Darn it. Move aside.
Hey.
Sam-sik, let me.
You must be tired from the trial.
You should just rest.
Since Mr. Sam-sik never works,
he can serve the food today.
In other words, he's jobless.
Seo-jin, you...
Sure, laugh while you still can.
Once you find out who Kang-ho really is,
you won't be laughing anymore.
Hey, watch what you say to a kid.
- Sam-sik, why are you idling around?
- Let's go.
What did you say to them?
Goodness.
I don't think I've ever felt...
this happy and proud in my life before.
- Prosecutor Choi.
- Yes?
You were absolutely amazing today.
"Oh Tae-soo."
"You're under arrest for abetting murder."
Now...
let me introduce the woman who
raised this wonderful prosecutor.
The star of the day!
I bring you...
Ms. Jin Young-soon!
Mom.
- Come on, Mom.
- Gosh.
- Hurray for Jin Young-soon!
- Jin Young-soon!
- My mom!
Gosh.
You're embarrassing me.
It's already been 35 years...
since I moved here with
a single pig on my truck.
I had no money or knowledge.
I was just...
an unwelcome pregnant woman
who suddenly barged in here.
But you all welcomed me with open arms.
No, we didn't.
We hated the stinky pig
smell and protested your move.
You even carried Sam-sik on your back.
It's true.
You're right.
You barged into my home...
wielding farm tools.
Then I suddenly went into labor.
And you helped me deliver Kang-ho.
Me too.
That's right.
- You were born in that room.
- Yes, Mi-joo too.
Just like how we can't
predict when we'll be born,
we can't predict when we'll die either.
I'd like to thank you all...
while I still have a healthy mind.
People might say...
I'm the most unfortunate woman.
I lost both my husband and my parents.
And then my son was seriously injured,
and I have an incurable illness.
I doubt there's anyone
who's more unlucky than me.
But you know what?
Life is so fascinating and makes you grateful.
When it takes one thing from you,
it always replaces it with something else.
Losing my parents...
taught me to value my husband.
And losing my husband taught me to value my son.
And when my son was unwell,
I learned to value myself...
so I could take care of him.
And because my life was cut short,
I learned to value everyone here,
who'll be in his life in my stead.
Not many people are lucky enough...
to encounter all these
blessings in their lifetime.
I'm truly blessed...
for being able to live this precious life.
Mr. Son.
Yes?
Mr. Bang.
And Sung-ae and Gum-ja.
Thanks to you,
I've never felt lonely,
and lived...
such a chaotic, happy life.
Later...
Much later in life,
when you move into the neighborhood up there,
I'll be the one...
hurrying out and welcoming you with open arms.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Please.
Until then,
I pray you'll be healthy...
for a very long time.
All right.
You'd better welcome us with open arms.
Sing for us too.
Gosh, I'm embarrassing myself.
One, two, three, four.
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
♫ Happy birthday, dear Young-soon ♫
Wait.
Make a wish first.
Happy Birthday, Mom
All right, hop on.
I'll make rounds for getting
into college, passing the bar exam,
and becoming a prosecutor.
- Goodness.
- Yes, Kang-ho!
- Come on.
- You're awesome!
- Oh, no!
- Gosh!
- Oh, my!
- Goodness.
- You're still very healthy, Mom.
Do it again.
- You should lose some weight.
- Carry me again.
All right. Here.
- All right.
- Let's do it again.
This is for getting into college!
Here.
This was the very first ring
your father-in-law got me.
And here.
This was the very first ring I got your dad.
People say to love like it's your first time.
But...
I'd like you to love like it's your last time.
"These are the last words
they're going to hear from me."
"This is the last image of me..."
"they'll remember."
That mindset will make you
think twice about how you speak...
and act towards each other.
Just like how...
I still remember your
dad's last words to this day.
What were his last words?
"See you later."
He hated saying bye because it implied an end.
That's why he always said,
"See you later," instead.
"See you later."
Saying it over and over gave me butterflies,
because it really felt like
we were going to meet again.
Think of each other as gems
and treat one another preciously.
Take good care and love each other.
And live a happy life.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
Come to think of it, both of you were born...
in that room on the same day and time.
Right?
Mi-joo, your grandma once said this.
"We say it's meant to be..."
We say it's meant to be...
to someone we meet for the first time.
But fate is...
what we say to someone who
stays with us until the end.
Don't you think our kids were
fated to end up with each other?
What?
Why are you here?
Are you going to sleep here?
Of course.
I'm going to sleep next
to you until I get married.
Goodness.
I should start looking for a venue tomorrow.
What?
Do you hate it that much?
It's gross. You're a grown man.
It's not like you're Seo-jin or Ye-jin.
Seo-jin's eyes and lips remind me of you...
when you were his age.
And Ye-jin...
is excellent at drawing.
They're definitely your kids.
Whatever. I'm going to sleep with you.
- Lie down.
- Gosh, what are you doing?
Just lie down. Let's sleep side by side.
All right.
- Goodness.
- Here.
There.
All right.
Are you tired?
Yes.
I'm a bit tired.
It's been...
a long journey.
Right?
All right. Let me massage your legs.
Goodness.
That's okay.
Lie down.
Sing me a lullaby.
- What?
- That song.
The song you sang for me...
after our first date.
I want to fall asleep to that song.
Okay. Your wish is my command.
♫ A tiring day passed by ♫
♫ Two are under the moonlight ♫
♫ as one shadow ♫
♫ That distant happiness is ♫
♫ still there seemingly within my reach ♫
♫ When I ♫
♫ close my eyes ♫
I'm so happy.
♫ Though your wounded heart ♫
♫ may cast a shadow ♫
♫ on your dream ♫
♫ But don't forget ♫
♫ that someone ♫
♫ who loves you dearly ♫
♫ is with you ♫
♫ At times, this road ♫
♫ may seem endless ♫
♫ and you may shed tears of sadness ♫
♫ But until the day ♫
♫ we can reminisce these moments ♫
♫ let's become ♫
♫ a place of shelter for one another ♫
♫ Even if the dreams we yearn for ♫
♫ can't be found ♫
♫ over the rainbow in the future ♫
♫ These moments ♫
♫ we spend ♫
♫ together ♫
♫ are more important ♫
♫ than anything else ♫
Mom...
Mom.
See you later.
Late Jin Young-soon
Rest In Peace
When will I need to do this?
Later.
Much later.
So let's try it.
Goodness.
♫ I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy ♫
♫ The long-awaited day has come ♫
♫ I'm ♫
♫ happy ♫
♫ I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy ♫
That's right.
♫ I'm happy
I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy
I'm very, very happy ♫
♫ I'm happy
I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy
I'm very, very happy ♫
♫ I'm happy
I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy
I'm very, very happy ♫
♫ I'm happy
I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy
I'm very, very happy ♫
♫ I'm happy ♫
I told you to stop calling me.
What if the kids catch on to us?
You released another new song?
"The Lovely Gumja Tower"? Get out.
I told you not to name your songs so obviously.
So tell me.
When will you be visiting again?
Visit at dawn.
When everyone is still fast asleep.
That was Grandma Jung, the crazy...
I mean, that was Grandma Jung
who's crazy in love.
By the way, what are you doing?
I'm searching for stroke symptoms.
Her pronunciation is off.
♫ I'm happy ♫
Where is Sam-sik?
What is it? Is something missing again?
He stole my brand-new cashmere longjohns, socks,
and underwear!
What could he possibly use them for?
I'm speaking from experience.
Goods from outside are much better.
These are...
cashmere longjohns, so
they're extremely light...
and warm.
And these socks are from a famous brand.
You'll look awfully stylish if you wear these...
under that cobalt uniform.
As for the underwear...
Would they be too big for you?
My mom does have a big rear end.
Thank you.
Gosh, don't mention it.
Two years will pass...
in the blink of an eye.
They'll just fly by.
What's truly important...
is that we're meant to be.
Meant to be.
Do you need anything else?
Do you need sesame oil?
Red chili powder?
We grew some tasty cabbage this year.
Would you like some?
♫ I'm happy
I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm very, very happy
I'm very, very happy ♫
Gosh, what's your secret?
You always have a bountiful harvest.
There's no secret.
You just reap what you sow.
What's with the cars in front of Mr. Son's home?
No, don't come out, Tiger.
Honey!
Wait!
What's happening?
Why are you leaving out of the blue?
Thank you for everything you've done.
My father re-established a newly-rising Yakuza.
So I must return.
You irritated everyone with your perfect Korean.
But now you speak with an accent.
This isn't fair.
Then what were all those
years we spent together?
No.
What was I to you?
Was I just for your enjoyment?
I couldn't even enjoy you.
You know that.
It's time. Please get in the car.
Wait.
Pregnant?
What?
Tell Father I'm carrying someone's child.
How is that possible?
Honey.
Happy Farm
There he is.
Mom.
- Jong-gu!
- Mom!
- What took you so long?
Mom, don't cry.
My poor son.
Seobu Penitentiary
Mr. Jung Jong-gu.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Don't be.
I knew you'd come back for me.
Thank you.
Sir, here.
Your mother has been sending us kimchi,
side dishes, and red chili powder.
We wanted to refuse,
but they were so delicious.
So we've been accepting them all this time.
Please tell her she doesn't have to anymore,
and that we're grateful.
I will.
Kang-ho!
Be careful.
Dad!
- Seo-jin!
- Ye-jin!
He's my dad? I'll never accept that.
How could she steal her own daughter's man?
Where are you going?
Let's play together.
Come on.
Ye-jin.
Hi.
We just moved here today.
Where does the village head live?
The trip there will be quite rough.
So let me escort you there myself.
This way, Mother.
Happy Farm
When did you decorate all this?
Where did you get the money?
Do you remember this?
It's the bank book you gave me.
I wanted to throw this at
your face the next time we met,
so I didn't spend a single penny.
But you know what?
Your mom told me...
to think of you as a gem
and treat you preciously.
- Right. Come here.
- What?
Pig Farm
Office
Welcome, Happy Farm
Take a look.
Look.
That's Father, and that's Mother.
And I love this photo.
We took this to commemorate...
the donation we gave under
the name of Happy Farm,
after receiving a prize
for our pig farm business.
This was such a proud moment, wasn't it?
It was.
This is the cutest photo of
you taken on your first birthday.
And that's a photo of your parents' wedding.
And...
I thought long and hard about
what photo to hang next to it.
And I think...
it'd be nice to hang
something similar to this one.
If you have any good ideas, let me know.
Okay?
- Next to that one?
- Yes.
Get changed.
Okay.
To my beloved son, Kang-ho.
Do you remember the very first
letter you'd written to me?
"We may be apart,"
"but I still live..."
"in the memories I shared with you and Father."
By the time you read this letter,
I'll be feeling the same.
Kang-ho.
The Chinese character for "connection"...
contains the characters
for "thread" and "pig head."
The connections we build with
others are just as difficult...
as leading a pig with a thread.
We were connected as mother and son.
It's such a precious bond,
so I wanted to become the best mom for you.
But you only get one life,
and it was my first time being a mom,
so I'm sorry I wasn't good enough.
I made a wish before blowing
out my birthday candles.
I prayed that I'd become your mom once again.
If that ever happens,
I promise to be a better mom.
I won't tell you not to be
sad about not having a dad.
I won't say that your grades
are all that matters in life.
I won't ignore your talent for drawing.
I won't turn away...
when I know you want to eat more.
I won't hold back my tears...
when I see you in pain.
I'll help you get up when you fall.
I'll embrace you when you're afraid.
I'll say, "Good job,"
"thank you,"
and "I love you,"
every single day.
And I won't...
leave you so soon.
I love you, my son.
I hope you live a long, happy life...
with Mi-joo, Seo-jin, and Ye-jin.
And we'll meet again...
on the day my prayer is answered.
From your bad mother.
Today...
is the day I propose to Mi-joo...
to ask her to live a long
and happy life with me.
But you ruined everything.
Please watch over me...
so I won't be too nervous.
No.
Protect us.
Lee Mi-joo!
You're under arrest for becoming my wife!
You don't have the right to remain silent.
You can't ask your mother
for help when we argue.
How childish.
This isn't a proposal.
- Why not?
- What you just said...
might be used against you later in life.
So watch out, okay?
- This won't do.
- What?
All right. I need your help.
- All right.
Lee Mi-joo!
I saved your life three times.
So even if I get so annoying,
even if we argue,
and even if I get downright childish,
promise to live with me
happily the rest of our lives.
All right, go ahead.
- Come here.
- Go to mommy.
- No!
- Oh, no!
- Kang-ho! Hang on, I...
- We have to look good.
Come on, think of our age.
♫ He's a napa cabbage flower
Napa cabbage flower ♫
♫ A new wind will blow ♫
Sam-sik's Mill
I don't even eat marinated crab,
because it's so good I'd steal to eat them!
I hate stray cats even more.
They're like little thieves.
Do you know how shocked I was...
when "The Thieves" was released?
Hey!