Ra Mi-ran
Lee Do-hyun
Ahn Eun-jin
Yoo In-soo
Sam-sik's Mill
Choi Moo-sung - Jung Woong-in - Hong Bi-ra
Seo Yi-sook - Jang Won-young - Kang Mal-geum
Kim Won-hae - Park Bo-kyung
Happy Farm
The Good Bad Mother
Episode 9
Look at that color.
This year's kimchi will be delicious.
Of course.
It's due to these fully-ripened red chilies.
We couldn't sun-dry the chilies last year...
because of all the rain.
I'm glad the weather's nice this year.
Hello.
You're here.
Oh, my. Look at the color
of the red chili powder.
Wait.
That's her, right?
You're right.
Grandma!
That lady who came with Kang-ho last time...
is getting married.
- What?
- Oh, my.
- What are you talking about?
What?
- What?
- Let me see.
- Oh, my. She's right.
So she was Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo's daughter?
Does that mean Kang-ho...
almost became the President's son-in-law?
- Goodness.
- My goodness.
That's not what's important right now.
Goodness, that cursed brat.
It hasn't been that long
since Kang-ho's accident,
and she's already marrying someone else?
If it were the son of Dosang Group,
I'd get married in an instant too.
Don't say something like
that in front of your husband.
Knock on wood right now.
- Knock, knock, knock.
Young-soon's already so stressed out.
She'll be really upset when she finds out.
What are you saying?
We can never let her find out, okay?
- Make sure you all keep it a secret!
- Okay.
I already know.
- What?
- Goodness!
Everyone has the right to live their own life.
She's right. The living have to go on living.
The Good Bad Mother
That's enough.
Mr. Bang, may I speak with you?
Me?
- Push it in until it clicks.
- Yes.
- Then you'll see this window.
- Right.
Put the cursor right here.
- Do you see the cursor?
- Yes.
Click twice quickly,
then you can see it like this.
Thank you so much.
It wasn't anything.
If you have any further questions,
- call me anytime.
- Okay.
Kang-ho, I'll be going now.
Okay. Thank you.
- My goodness.
- My back.
All right.
Click here twice, right?
Click-click.
What's this?
Password.
- Password.
Password. 0907, my birthday.
That's for our bank account.
But you never know.
Zero, nine, zero, seven.
Enter Password
Of course. It wouldn't be this easy.
What could it be?
What could it be, Kang-ho?
Any numbers you remember?
Numbers?
Numbers...
- Mom.
- Yes?
Isn't your birthday on March 12?
Oh, my.
Do you remember my birthday?
Mom, this is weird.
This was written on September 7,
but it says I'll see you
next week on your birthday.
You're right.
"I'll see you next week on your
birthday." Could this mean...?
Zero, three, one, two.
- It's correct!
- We did it, Mom!
You're so smart. How did you catch that?
All right. Let's see what's in here.
Kang-ho,
this looks like your journal.
"March 3, 2008."
March 3, 2008
I finally got into SNU School of Law...
Welcome, Freshmen of 2008
Join a Club
I finally got into SNU School of Law.
Choi Kang-ho, the top student
in this year's entering class.
Tell us why you chose law school.
Korea is a constitutional state
that protects liberal democracy.
Law is meant to provide public welfare...
for the happiness and benefit of the majority,
as well as justice for all...
As well as justice for all...
For what reason did your dad die?
I need to know that!
Actually,
I wanted to find out for myself.
What?
I want to find out the reason...
I had to attend law school.
That's why I'm here.
Kang-ho!
Detective Unit 1
Kang-ho.
What...?
What happened to you?
What happened to my son?
They got into an argument over grades at school,
and Mr. Choi initiated a physical altercation,
so he'll be booked on charges
unless they can reach a settlement.
Settlement?
I don't want to settle.
He didn't attend class, take
tests, or complete homework,
yet he's at the top of our class.
How could they fabricate his
grades and award him a scholarship,
just because his mother's a judge?
- And at a law school at that.
- Darn it.
I'd like to add defamation...
and dissemination of false information.
No, wait.
I'm sorry.
Let me apologize on his behalf.
He's always earned scholarships...
to help out his mom who's a pig farmer,
and was probably disappointed to
not come out as the top of the class.
Please.
Darn it.
Darn, I was wondering what that smell was.
If it seemed so unfair, why didn't
you major in livestock production?
Then your farmer mom could've helped you.
You jerk.
Ma'am!
I'm sorry.
Please forgive him just once.
Come here and beg.
Tell him you were wrong.
Beg him, or you'll go to jail!
- Beg for forgiveness!
- Mom.
- Beg him for forgiveness!
- Do it!
- Mom!
So you're saying...
I have to beg this jerk?
You're telling me to kneel
before this douchebag...
because I can't take
the bar exam if I go to jail.
Right.
That's what you want.
You want me to become a cowardly
snob who'd do anything to get my way.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know my place and got cheeky.
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me just this once.
Please let me take the bar exam.
Please forgive me.
No, please forgive me, sir.
- On that day,
- Just this once.
I realized why,
for what reason...
June 18, 2009
...I had to attend law school,
and what I must do now.
Excuse me. I'm the bereaved.
I'd like to see my father's
trial record and the ruling.
Son: Kang-ho
Family Head: Choi Hae-sik
I can only view the ruling?
I followed the procedure to get his
trial and witness examination records.
So why can't I see it?
Trial records and witness examination records...
include sensitive contents,
so we can't release them.
But my father has already passed.
Disclosure of trial records...
falls within the jurisdiction of the
prosecutor the case was transferred to,
so we can't give them to you if they decline.
Defendant: Song Woo-byeok
Prosecutor: Oh Tae-soo
Judgment
The evidence corresponding to arson...
Defendant: Song Woo-byeok
Prosecutor: Oh Tae-soo
Locate the suspect and bring him in, you punk.
What arrest warrant?
What?
Why are you still here?
Please show me.
According to the Official
Information Disclosure Act,
the bereaved family is entitled
to the investigation report.
This is a dereliction of duty.
What?
Dereliction of duty?
I can't believe this.
Hey, who do you think you are, you punk?
Are detectives a joke just
because you study law?
- No, that's not...
- Forget it.
You need to leave.
Take the bar exam,
become a prosecutor,
and then arrest me for my dereliction of duty.
Then I'll give you every investigation report...
from 22 years ago, no, even from 100 years ago.
- Get out of here.
- Detective.
Get lost, you punk! I'm busy!
Once you study hard and become a prosecutor,
no one will be able to look
down on you or bully you.
That's true power.
Do you understand?
A Prosecutor of Principles and Conviction
The Story of Oh Tae-soo
SNU Graduate School
Oh Tae-soo
"My Duty is to Oppose Injustice"
Top graduate of the School of Law, Choi Kang-ho.
The student has graduated as the
top student of the Class of 2013...
Pre-Law and Law School Graduation
I'll start sending money
to this account monthly.
And find a bigger place too.
Okay?
Bank Book
That's when I met her.
The one who shed a ray of warm light...
into my dark, cold, and rough life.
Joongang Ballet Company Gala
Judicial Research and Training Institute
Look at that.
The nerdy Kang-ho has a rather elegant hobby.
You're going to ballet?
I'm not going for the ballet.
It's to see Chief Prosecutor Oh Tae-soo.
Oh Tae-soo?
Oh Ha-young is his daughter.
No matter how busy he is, he
always attends her ballet galas.
It's a perfect chance to see him up close.
I might even get to greet him if I get lucky.
You aren't just a fanatic. You're a stalker.
Guys!
Big news.
Chief Prosecutor Oh Tae-soo...
is coming to our next special lecture!
Really?
Good for you, Kang-ho.
You were dying to meet him.
Hey, my mom told me...
Chief Prosecutor Oh will resign next year...
and run for office.
He is? Instead of becoming
the prosecutor general?
It means he has bigger plans ahead.
No way.
The presidency?
Bingo.
Prosecutor Oh Tae-soo, who was in
charge of my father's trial 28 years ago,
became the chief prosecutor of
the Seoul High Prosecutors' Office.
Have we met before?
You look familiar.
No, sir.
- We've never met.
- Dad.
We're late. Let's go.
Okay.
The newly-appointed
probationary judicial officers...
of Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office, welcome.
I'll debrief you on the locations of
each office and their current tasks,
so make sure you keep up.
All right.
Penalty Enforcement Division
One and Two work over there.
That's the archives.
You'll find all files and case
records regarding a trial.
Next, the Criminal Department.
Come on, chicks.
- Peep, peep.
- Chicks.
Peep, peep.
Medical Malpractice
Excuse me.
Hello.
I'm Choi Kang-ho, a
probationary judicial officer...
- of Criminal Division 8.
- Hello.
Pardon me,
but may I ask you for another case file?
Sure.
Case 614 of the Year 1988
Records
I finally got my father's trial
record that I always longed to see.
I'm sure the beginning of my
mother's and my twisted fate...
can be found in this record.
Charged without detention
Charged with arson
List of Evidence
Report of Trial
Hey, it's that exam meal punk...
I mean, it's Bar Exam Meal.
Hey.
- Should I wait?
- I'll be out.
He's so devoted.
He doesn't miss a single day.
Just get married if you two are so in love.
He hasn't even been appointed yet.
It's too soon to think about marriage.
That's it. The appointment ceremony.
His mother will come to Seoul that day.
He'll officially introduce
you to her and propose.
You think so?
Of course!
Darn it. He's messing up the window.
- Hey, wipe that off!
- Okay.
Sun-young, I'm off now.
You clean up the window!
Okay, Sun-young. Love you. Bye.
Make sure you wipe it tomorrow!
- Okay, bye!
- Okay.
I'll do it.
- Here.
- What is this?
You were curious about the
food at the Prosecutors' Office.
You packed all this?
Yes. I'm the best, right?
Of course you are.
You stole food from the office.
What if they catch you red-
handed and arrest you for theft?
Goodness, Mi-joo. You know the law?
I've learned plenty being around you.
Feel free to ask me if you have any questions.
Yes, ma'am.
All right.
Tell me what you can make out of this situation.
Sure.
- A prosecutor requested a witness...
- Okay.
...for his case.
And that witness...
made a statement against the victim in court.
Why did he do that?
Wait.
The prosecutor must've called that witness...
- to help the victim, right?
- Yes.
But the witness testified against the victim?
That means the witness changed their mind.
- Exactly.
- Hey.
Then it's obvious.
The witness could've held
a grudge against the victim.
Or they purposely decided to mess them up.
Or something must've changed
their mind before the trial.
For example, they could've
been threatened or bribed.
Right?
That's obviously the case, right?
Kwak Sang-cheol.
A firefighter who was close to my father,
and often came to inspect
his farm for fire prevention.
But during the trial,
he gave a questionable testimony
that there were many problems...
with the electrical facility
at my father's farm.
Excuse me.
Are you Mr. Kwak Sang-cheol?
I never should've done that to Hae-sik.
I'm so sorry.
But I thought we'd all be in
danger if I continued to resist.
Danger? What do you mean?
Mr. Kwak, you're a civil servant, right?
If a civil servant hinders a state project,
it makes them a communist.
I get that it's for our country,
but how could you set his farm on fire?
Right? I agree with you.
I shouldn't have burned his farm down.
If I set his home on fire,
we wouldn't be in so much trouble, right?
Yongra
A fire begins without warning.
It can start at your home,
or even at your mother's hospital.
Right?
Always beware of fire.
Let's not let down our guard!
You have a great place here.
Goodness.
I thought something was off when
I heard Hae-sik had passed away.
I had a feeling that those men were behind it.
But there was absolutely no
evidence after the investigation,
and I had to keep my mouth shut,
afraid of Director Song's retaliation.
By Director Song, you mean...
You're right.
Director Song Woo-byeok of Yongra Construction,
who fought against your father in court.
He's now Woobyeok Group's chairman.
Woobyeok's Chairman Song...
I'm home.
- Hey.
How have you been?
Fine.
Your mother is coming to your
appointment ceremony tomorrow, right?
No.
What?
She's not coming? Why not?
You didn't tell her about it?
Kang-ho, you shouldn't...
Mi-joo.
All right.
What about me? When and
where should I go tomorrow?
I'm sorry.
I should go alone tomorrow.
I have to be somewhere right after.
- It's important.
- But...
All right then.
It'll be weird for me to go if your
mother won't be there either, right?
Instead, let's have a party tomorrow night.
Let's do that.
I'll wash up.
And now...
the parents and families of new prosecutors...
may come up and put the gown on them.
Please show your support by putting
the untainted black gown on them,
a symbol for them to maintain
fairness and impartiality...
in their journey as prosecutors.
Newly-appointed prosecutors shall
relay a warm regard to your parents...
for supporting you over a long period of time.
Please encourage one another.
Congratulations.
Prosecutor's oath.
- Our oath!
As of this moment, I accept the
call of my country and people,
and receive the honor to serve as a prosecutor.
So you're a prosecutor?
Your mother must be quite disappointed.
I heard about your baby. Congratulations!
Hae-sik is so thrilled that he's
already wondering whether it'd be...
a son or daughter and thinking of names.
I'll be happy with either a girl or a boy.
I just want our baby to be healthy,
and raise them to be a painter.
- A painter?
- Yes.
I always wanted to be a painter.
My parents passed away while
I was preparing for art school,
so I had to give up.
I have a feeling that our baby will
take after me and be good at drawing.
Isn't that true?
I'll courageously lift
the darkness of injustice.
I'll stay warm-hearted for those
who are weak and underprivileged.
The 32nd
Hanju Daily National Youth Art Contest
Why are you doing this?
What's wrong with you?!
I'll only follow the truth and remain impartial.
I'll remain strict and upright.
I hereby take my oath to
serve our people and nation...
as a prosecutor, upon my honor.
Choi Kang-ho
Supreme Prosecutors' Office
Bring me the investigation record
for Choi Hae-sik's death in 1988.
Investigation Record of
the Death of Choi Hae-sik
Suspect: Song Woo-byeok
Charged Without Detention
That's how I finally met my father.
Scene of Incident
Photos of Victim
There was no evidence of murder.
And the autopsy result showed it
was suffocation due to airway blockage.
It was a suicide.
Ligature mark 1.5" under the chin
12 nail mark abrasions
Are these from the scene,
and are these from the autopsy?
Yes, that's correct.
Who was the detective in charge?
These are photos of the
victim taken at the scene.
Doesn't it seem odd?
I'm not sure.
Take a close look at his neck.
The only wound you can see...
is the pressure from
the rope, the ligature mark.
It means there was no struggle...
until the moment he suffocated to
death although his hands were free.
Well, that's possible.
There are cases where a suicide
victim dies from a broken neck,
depending on the weight of the
victim and the height of the noose.
Then what do you think about this?
This is from his autopsy.
The nail marks that were absent at the scene...
suddenly appear clearly during the autopsy.
I'm not sure.
This is...
Someone must've questioned
whether it was truly a suicide.
Look at this.
Isn't this weird?
The scar on his neck is too smooth.
Even if he was determined to die,
there should be some trace
of struggle due to pain, right?
His neck was too clean for
someone who suffocated slowly...
to his death.
Of course one could've argued
he died from a broken neck.
Unfortunately, the victim
wasn't found at a scene...
high enough for him to die instantly.
Therefore...
there was a high possibility
the victim's suicide was staged...
after he was murdered or made unconscious.
Someone was afraid the truth
might leak, so they created...
such false resistance marks before the autopsy.
Who was it?
Sorry?
Goodness.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I noticed you were promoted...
right after this case was closed.
And you also bought a home and some land.
As I said, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
So you don't know?
I heard you'll be retiring in a month.
I guess I'll find out within a month...
whether you'll retire or be dismissed.
What's with you?
It's been over 30 years!
Yes, it has!
It's been over 30 years.
But I still have to bring
justice to the wronged!
It may have been over 30 years,
but he's still my father.
Prosecutor's Office
Choi Kang-ho
Prosecutor: Oh Tae-soo
Chief Prosecutor: Oh Tae-soo
Defendant: Song Woo-byeok
Prosecutor: Oh Tae-soo
It wasn't Song Woo-byeok.
It was Prosecutor Oh Tae-soo.
All right, we're here.
Let's go.
- I'm hungry.
- Goodness, I'm hungry,
and I want a drink too.
Let's hurry inside.
Do you want to know...
what I want to do?
If you tell me,
will it change anything?
No.
Then I also say...
no.
Petit Nail
Don't ever let her find out...
how much I loved her.
how much I love her.
And please...
don't ever let her find out...
why our love must end so painfully like this.
Let her loathe and resent me...
as she forgets me...
and erases me from her memory.
Let her forget that she must forget me,
and let her be happy.
See you next time
"My daughter teaches me
how the world is changing"
Former Chief Prosecutor
Oh Tae-soo running for...
Prosecutor Choi Kang-ho
A Dancer's Dream
I received a tip about drugs.
It was my first time clubbing.
I couldn't have injured my knee at a worse time!
Seriously!
I'm so frustrated right now.
Kang-ho, buy me a drink.
Let me call you back.
No. Wait, don't hang...
Do Not Litter
CCTV in Operation
Yoon Jae-min, the guy who always came to our bar
- What are you doing?
- You crazy wench.
Let go of me, you crazy scumbag!
Hey! Let go!
Hey, get up.
Get up.
What's this?
The CCTVs near Woo Mi-jeong's
incident were either broken or wiped,
so the case was almost abandoned.
Thankfully, I found one nearby
installed to monitor littering.
So what do you want to show me?
Do you see this car?
If you consider the time
and location of the incident,
there's a high chance this car's
dashcam recorded the incident.
It'll take a while to process
the license plate number,
but I'll reveal the truth soon.
Kang-ho, let's just let this one slide.
Is it because of Yoon Jae-min?
He might dispose of Jung Jong-gu?
He'll stage Jung Jong-gu's
suicide like he did it out of guilt.
He'll think it's the easiest
way to tie up loose ends.
He'll go as far as to kill an innocent man?
Don't you know what Chairman Song is like?
He can do much worse things.
Sir, let me take on this case.
What?
You're about to become
the deputy chief prosecutor.
You want to avoid getting tangled
up in a messy case like this.
Please allow...
your junior prosecutor the
opportunity to run with this case,
Sir.
I mean, Deputy Chief.
I'll oversee this case with care.
I didn't kill Mi-jeong.
But even my lawyer doesn't believe me.
Mr. Jung,
you didn't kill Ms. Woo.
I'll find the evidence.
So until then,
you must stay alive in here.
You must trust me and do as I say...
until I find indisputable evidence.
I'll save you at all costs, Mr. Jung.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Why did Woo Mi-jeong forget her
lipstick and leave your stall in a hurry?
Because...
she was angry with me.
Why was she angry?
Because...
I tried to wipe the tteokbokki sauce off of her,
but she suddenly hit my face.
You must've been offended.
You were just being considerate.
Yes.
I mean...
Despite that, you went out to
give the lipstick back to her,
all the way into an alley
250 feet from the main road.
However,
when you saw Woo Mi-jeong with another man,
you returned to your stall...
in case you incur a misunderstanding, correct?
Yes.
If you didn't have any feelings for her,
you should've returned the lipstick...
even if you saw her with another man.
So why did you return to your stall?
And why did you go back to the alley?
It shows the defendant didn't
go out to find Woo Mi-jeong...
just to return the lipstick.
Jung Jong-gu, the defendant,
was assaulted by Woo Mi-jeong,
who he liked, as he showed kindness.
While he was ashamed and humiliated,
he saw her with another man
and decided to commit this crime.
Defendant.
Do you admit to the crime?
That's absurd!
Goodness!
Jong-gu!
You didn't kill her!
Tell him you didn't.
- Jong-gu!
- Tell him no!
- Please be quiet.
- Defendant.
Do you admit to the crime?
- Mom, I want to go home!
- Jong-gu, say it!
- Defendant, calm down!
- I want to go home!
- Defendant.
- That is all.
Sir, he's here.
You're here.
Leave this letter on my desk.
Goodness, thank you for coming a long way.
Please excuse my clothes.
Things have been hectic lately.
You look nice and comfortable.
This is Prosecutor Choi Kang-ho,
who took charge of the trial.
It's a pleasure.
Hello, I'm Choi Kang-ho...
with the Seoul Central
District Prosecutors' Office.
Your grandson's name won't be mentioned
during the course of this trial.
Prosecutor Choi will ensure
discretion throughout it.
This trial, I mean.
Are you after money or power?
If I want it,
can you give it to me?
You just saved my grandson.
So why not?
In that case, both.
In return,
you'll be a part of my family now.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
That's enough.
I'll do my best, Mr. Song. Thank you!
Find out the plate number of the car...
and recover the dashcam footage, no matter what.
Kang-ho.
How about this one?
You should wear this today.
Okay?
No, I'll wear the one you gave
me for our first anniversary.
No, that's too flashy.
This is perfect.
Let's go with this one.
Yes, this is perfect.
Dad.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
I'm glad my daughter...
Who is he?
Hello, I'm Choi Kang-ho.
You must be surprised.
Ha-young
You reek of something.
Ever since we first met.
What could it be?
Is it the smell of dirt since
you came from the bottom up?
Someone like you can never call me "Father."
Though you must not understand
since you don't have a father.
Sir, it's me, Choi Kang-ho.
It's good.
Have some of this.
That's it. Good.
It's good.
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo used to
cover things up for Woobyeok Group.
Why is he suddenly siding with Dosang Group?
You really don't know?
Hey.
Chairman Song used to be a thug.
Think about all the shady acts...
they've committed in their 30 years together.
There are rumors that those
two are behind the death...
of the chairman of Yongra Construction,
which is now Woobyeok Group.
It doesn't matter if it's true or not.
He's cleaning up after himself...
before it becomes a problem.
But if Assemblyman Oh runs for President,
Chairman Song wouldn't just sit by and watch.
Did you seriously think Oh Tae-soo
wasn't prepared for that...
when he dropped this bomb?
If things go sour, only
Woobyeok will get destroyed.
That's why Chairman Song...
is dying to take down Oh Tae-soo.
Anyway,
Chairman Song is a tactless brute to the bone.
All he did was bribe and seduce him with women.
A sly man like Oh Tae-soo
would never fall for such tricks.
I'd be a sucker for that.
Who are you?
Are you Ms. Hwang Soo-hyun?
Chairman Song was always anxious that...
Oh Tae-soo might betray him.
Corporate sales...
have actually increased by
21.5% compared to last year.
That's why...
he sent me to work as Oh Tae-soo's assistant...
to keep an eye on him.
At first I was just doing my job.
I'll move abroad and live quietly.
No, can you please tell
him we're both already dead?
"Both"?
Okay then.
Let's do this.
I'll keep you...
and your baby safe.
I give you my word.
To do that, I must get
Oh Tae-soo under my thumb,
and I can only do that through Chairman Song.
Can you share with me the
confidential files you have...
regarding Woobyeok Group?
In return, please do as I asked you.
Your baby is adorable.
I'm going to show the DNA test
result to Chairman Song tomorrow.
The day has finally come.
The moment Oh Tae-soo finds out about the baby,
you, your mother, and those
around you might be put in danger.
You know that, right?
Prosecutor Choi, please be careful.
Okay.
You have a call from the lobby.
Yes?
Hello, sir. This is the security office.
Your mother is here.
Tell her I'm not home.
Happy Farm
Please take me in as your real son.
- What did you say?
- I want to become...
your legal son.
Then as your son,
I'll marry Oh Tae-soo's daughter.
You'll have Oh Tae-soo.
Oh Tae-soo will have me.
And I'll have a father.
None of us will be able to betray one another.
We'll become a true family.
- Hello.
Take a look at this.
Woobyeok Group set up this paper
company in Singapore two years ago...
Pack up.
Sorry?
You'll be safer there than in Korea.
No one will be able to find you.
Don't worry about it. It'll all work out.
Thank you for doing as I asked.
Ms. Hwang.
We're here.
Over there.
Here.
He's the owner of a
restaurant where I used to work.
He'll take you to a stowaway ship
that'll take you to the Philippines.
You may get seasick on the boat,
but hang in there for an hour.
The larger ship will be more stable.
Also,
here.
This is the address to your
home in the Philippines, passports,
and money for living expenses.
Oh Tae-soo may look for you,
so try to remain out of sight, okay?
Thank you so much.
Don't worry.
If my plan goes well,
you can return and live happily with your baby.
I'm counting on you, sir.
Don't worry. I'll see her off
and get in touch with you.
Okay.
All right.
This way.
I took care of it.
Sillim Fresh Raw Fish
Be polite to his mother.
And remember what I told you earlier.
Okay?
You must be feeling uneasy to
share difficult news with your mother.
The moment Chairman Song accepted me as his son,
she became a stranger to me.
I'm only going there to
seal the legal procedure,
so I feel at ease.
We'll get going.
Sillim Fresh Raw Fish
I got this at the biggest jewelry shop in town.
They're diamonds.
Take a look.
Can you wait outside?
Okay.
Why?
May I have something to drink?
Sure. Give me a moment.
Goodness.
Come to think of it,
your fiancée was born in the Year of the Pig.
It must be destiny.
Who am I?
I'm a pig farmer.
She was destined to marry
into our family, right?
What is this?
"Adoption Agreement"?
Are you going to adopt a child?
Why?
She can't get pregnant?
I'll be adopted by Chairman Song
who's been raising me all along.
Please stamp your seal there.
I can't fight against them with Father's case,
since the statute of limitations
had already expired.
October 3, 2021
No, perhaps...
Father's case probably didn't
mean much to me from the beginning.
What I really wanted to avenge...
was your life they utterly destroyed,
and the pain you felt...
living as a bad mother to your most beloved son.
I'll now become Song Woo-byeok's son,
and Oh Tae-soo's son-in-law,
to destroy everything they've ever built.
Since I know how difficult and
dangerous this journey will be,
I have to sever my ties with you.
Please forgive this awful son.
Someday when everything ends...
and I can return to you,
I wish to lie in your arms...
and eat mung bean pancakes just
as I did when I was a little boy.
Don't do it.
Don't do anything now.
Mom.
Mom, where are you going?
No.
Mom.
Mom, are you okay?
Mom, what's wrong?
So that's why you were so cold to me?
To pursue revenge by yourself?
To take all the risks by yourself?
My poor boy.
It must've been so tough.
It must've been so scary and lonely.
You have to stop everything.
Okay?
Happy Farm
What's that?
Goodness.
Their son is about to die any day now.
How long do these old geezers want to live?
"Prostate Medicine"?
I might end up getting a sibling.
Good grief. I made a mess.
Darn it.
What's that?
My goodness.
Where should we meet tomorrow?
I don't accept credit cards.
Only wire transfer or cash.
Goodness!
Darn it.
Mom, what are you doing?
- Give it to me.
- These are mine!
You said these were mine!
Choi Kang-ho!
Listen very carefully.
These are bad things.
It'll put you in danger if you keep it.
You might end up like your dad.
Like Dad?
What happened to him?
We have to get rid of them.
Choi Kang-ho
Supreme Prosecutors' Office
If you destroy yourself in revenge,
that isn't revenge.
True revenge...
is forgetting everything completely,
even the reason you wanted revenge,
and living a good life.
Let's forget.
Let's forget it all now.
You,
me,
and...
you too.
What's that?
My goodness!
The Good Bad Mother
You are now...
the owner of Happy Farm.
I want to be a prosecutor.
Goodness! You look so handsome.
The most eligible bachelor of Jou-ri.
I want to marry him off.
Please don't let him
regain his memory until then.
Tell me, Kang-ho. What
were you going to do to me?
Something's going on, right?
Please tell me.
Kang-ho, let's play.
How about this? We'll give each other a gift.
It all went down the drain!
He's a prosecutor.
Babe, put him behind bars this instant.
Mi-joo, I can't hold back anymore.
Kang-ho still should've known.