Ra Mi-ran
Lee Do-hyun
Ahn Eun-jin
Yoo In-soo
Sam-sik's Mill
Choi Moo-sung - Jung Woong-in - Hong Bi-ra
Seo Yi-sook - Jang Won-young - Kang Mal-geum
Kim Won-hae - Park Bo-kyung
Happy Farm
The Good Bad Mother
Woobyeok's Leap Forward
Beasts' Victory
Look who it is.
Episode 12
Did you watch the news?
The news?
Hang on a second.
Are you here...
to talk about Hwang Soo-hyun?
So that's why you're here.
I thought you never wanted to see me again.
This is no time to be so casual.
Even her bereaved family
member is so nonchalant.
- So why shouldn't I be?
- "Bereaved family"?
She was your son's mother.
That makes you her family.
Are you serious right now?
You're the one who started it!
If the police start investigating this case,
both of us will be done for.
Let's end this...
by making Kang-ho the baby's father.
But of course...
we'll have to take care of him before that.
That's right.
This is how a President
should manage his affairs.
Right.
Sometimes you have to appease the masses,
and sometimes you have to
sacrifice some for the greater good.
A man like you should be President.
But then...
Hwang Soo-hyun appears out of nowhere.
What a shame.
Right?
Mr. Song!
Did you have that much fun with her?
You douchebag!
Do I look like a pushover
because I worked with you?
Did I have fun with her?
Do you have proof?
Because I do!
I have proof you killed Choi Hae-sik!
I have proof of all the
dirty deeds you committed...
to turn Yongra Construction into Woobyeok Group!
I also have proof you ordered Choi Kang-ho...
to kill Hwang Soo-hyun just
to have something on me!
Do you get it?
As of today,
I'm cutting ties with Dosang Group.
This country will now...
protect Woobyeok Group.
There are so many boats.
Wouldn't it be so beautiful to
see them all floating out there?
They'd look like Christmas lights.
Come on.
You've been checking your phone all day today.
Are you expecting a call?
No.
You must be cold. Come here.
It's okay.
You need it. Put it back on.
Listen to your guardian.
Gosh, you're scary.
Okay, Mr. Guardian.
All right.
Here you go.
- Kang-ho.
- Yes?
Look at the name of that boat.
It's my name.
- It's my name, Mom.
- No way.
It's "Choikangho."
Stand next to it. I'll take a photo.
A photo?
Say "piggy" on the count of three.
Piggy.
One, two, three.
That looks great.
- Take one of me too.
- Okay.
Unbelievable.
All right.
Hwang Soo-hyun.
What did you say?
What?
It's nothing.
I'll take it now.
One, two, three.
Piggy.
The Good Bad Mother
Hello?
What?
There's smoke coming from the farm?
Yes, okay.
Yes, I'll check now.
Kang-ho.
Kang-ho, wake up.
There's smoke coming from the farm.
Kang-ho...
Shouldn't we call 119...
if the farm is on fire?
It could be a prank call, so let's check first.
Can you open the gate?
Kang-ho!
Kang-ho.
A fire?
Their farm is on fire?
Wait. Kang-ho.
- Kang-ho!
- No, Sam-sik!
What is it?
What's the matter?
Is Sam-sik home?
I don't think so.
I had a nightmare.
Goodness. What did he do this time?
- Goodness.
- What's wrong?
Did you dream that he stole something again?
Where are you going?
You don't think he reported it, right?
Of course not. He lost the evidence.
If anything, he'd be accused
of threatening Oh Ha-young.
Do you think he's on to us?
That's why he ran away.
We must get him before things get out of hand.
Yes, sir.
Kang-ho!
Wait. Isn't that Bang Sam-sik?
Get him!
Sam-sik's Mill
What did they just say?
"Threatened"? "Ran away"?
They couldn't have been
talking about our son, right?
What did that punk do this time?
Goodness.
That punk!
Wait for me!
What's going on?
Fire!
What do I do?
Who are you?
Did you do this?
- Who are you?
- What's going on?
Darn it.
Hey, get them!
- We need to catch them!
- Help...
Help me...
- Who is that?
- What's going on?
- Is that a fire?
- A fire?
- Fire!
What?
Isn't that Sam-sik?
- Sam-sik! Goodness!
- Sam-sik!
Goodness, Sam-sik!
What do we do? There's a fire!
Call 119!
- Right, 119!
- Goodness, Sam-sik.
- Call 119.
What's going on? Sam-sik!
- Get up!
- Fire!
There's a fire!
You guys are such a loving couple.
Were you guys having a late-night date?
How romantic.
Romantic, my foot.
We were tossing and turning in bed,
so we decided to get some fresh air.
In this cold weather?
It's 14° F tonight.
It's already past the season to make kimchi.
Why do you have all this garlic?
I heard black garlic is good for your stomach,
so I'm going to make some.
For who? Does someone have a bad stomach?
Look, Mr. Son.
Actually...
She just wants to take good care of her health.
Black garlic is good for you.
Could you give us some too?
Sure.
But why? Do you guys have a bad stomach too?
Our stomachs are fine,
but his area down there...
What?
It says that black garlic is good for men.
He may look fine, but he's very weak.
You darn woman.
Enough with that nonsense of yours.
- Fire!
- What?
- Fire?
What are you talking about? A fire?
Here you were.
What were you doing?
It's a disaster! There's a fire!
Where's the fire? I don't see it.
I was praying in the mountains...
when I saw a fire blazing from Kang-ho's farm.
What?
Oh, dear!
Goodness!
Goodness, Mr. Son!
Mr. Son! This is bad!
Goodness, what's going on?
- Oh, dear!
- Call 119!
- Okay!
- Isn't this Sam-sik?
What's wrong with him?
Did he set this fire?
Shut your mouth!
Where are Kang-ho and his mom?
Her truck is here,
- but she won't pick up.
- Oh, no!
We don't have time!
Let's put out the fire!
- Okay!
- Over there!
Hurry!
- Goodness.
- Why are you lying here?
- Goodness!
- Stay with him!
What about our Sam-sik?
Go on. Pull it out.
Who's that?
Isn't that Young-soon?
- Ms. Jin!
- Goodness!
- Young-soon!
What's going on?
Goodness!
- Oh, dear!
- Be careful!
Be careful!
- You're okay now.
- Kang-ho.
- Where's the water?
- Kang-ho?
- Where is he right now?
- Kang-ho...
He's in there.
- What?
Are you saying he's in there?
- Kang-ho!
- Oh, no.
- No!
- Kang-ho!
- Oh, dear!
- Kang-ho...
- Mi-joo!
Stay here.
Sam-sik, are you okay?
- What?
- Mr. Yang.
Turn on the water.
- Right.
- Turn it on!
Stick it in there!
- Goodness!
- Hey!
What are you doing?
Goodness me!
Goodness!
You lunatic! What are you doing?
Spray it in my direction.
What?
Okay.
- No!
- Sam-sik!
Sam-sik!
Don't go in there!
- Don't do it!
- Don't go in!
No, Sam-sik!
Kang-ho!
Sam-sik!
- What do we do?
- Sam-sik!
- Goodness!
Sam-sik!
There they come!
They're here!
- Goodness!
- Over here!
Hurry up!
Wait!
Look! Someone's coming out!
Goodness! Sam-sik is
carrying Kang-ho on his back!
- Well done, Sam-sik!
- Well done!
- I'm so proud of...
- Sam-sik!
Hold on!
Isn't that Kang-ho?
- What?
Kang-ho is carrying Sam-sik!
Kang-ho!
- Kang-ho!
- Sam-sik!
Sam-sik!
They're okay.
It's Kang-ho.
Sam-sik.
- Goodness!
Kang-ho. Oh, dear.
- Oh, dear.
- My Sam-sik.
Wake up, Kang-ho.
Call the ambulance!
Are you okay?
Goodness, my Sam-sik.
Sam-sik!
You should be lying down. You're unwell.
They said his oxygen therapy went well,
and he'll wake up soon, so don't worry.
You've been so busy today because of us.
I'm sorry, Mi-joo.
Don't worry about that.
Ms. Jin, you should lie down.
- Sam-sik.
Where am I?
You darn punk. Where do you think you are?
It's the hospital.
The hospital?
Why would you jump into the fire?
Are you a moth drawn to a flame or something?
Why would you do such a thing?
You lunatic.
That's enough. He's still recovering.
Why would you call me a moth?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Is this funny to you?
Come on. Don't be so serious.
You almost died back there.
What?
What if something happened to you?
What if we lost our precious only son?
I got angry with you first...
so others wouldn't.
She beat you first...
because she couldn't stand the thought
of your being beaten up by others.
Do you even know how it feels to be so harsh...
to your own child?
It's okay to cause trouble.
You can even become a jobless thug.
Just stay alive, will you?
Is that so hard?
It's not, right?
Goodness me.
You son of a gun.
How dare you make my man cry?
It's not hard, is it?
Don't cry now.
You're awake. What a relief.
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Right.
How is Kang-ho?
They need to run a few more tests,
so they're transferring him to a general ward.
You're awake.
We're looking into the cause of the fire.
We found traces of gasoline...
near the farm's entrance where the fire started.
We suspect that there were
explosives around the area.
I can explain.
You see,
I went to the farm to look for Kang-ho.
And some suspicious-looking
guy was coming out of the farm.
I did it.
- It was me.
- What?
It was a mistake.
What was?
So...
It was my fault that the fire broke out.
I shouldn't have put the gasoline near the fire.
I was in a hurry.
Ms. Jin, what are you talking about?
I saw him.
This guy...
No. It wasn't just one guy.
Do you see this on the back of my neck?
- They hit me really hard.
- I see.
That's not the only place you're injured.
- Sorry?
- Goodness, you're a mess.
What happened to your lip?
- Goodness.
- Well, this...
There's no need to further investigate this.
I'm the victim, so why would I lie?
I'm sorry for taking up your time.
- I'm so sorry.
- What...?
But...
What are you doing?
Who's the suspicious guy you saw?
Did you eavesdrop?
Answer me.
He isn't a villager, right?
No one in our neighborhood would do that.
Let me go.
He was really tall and burly.
He was as big as Don Lee.
When I got there,
I saw him running out of the farm.
You saw it too.
The gate to the farm was latched.
It couldn't have been done from the inside.
Then why did Ms. Jin lie?
Beats me. I'm baffled too.
Maybe she caught on to it.
Caught on to what?
What?
Goodness.
That came out wrong.
Sam-sik, you know something, don't you?
I've never known anything in life.
Really?
Then why were you there so late?
That was because...
I went there to see Kang-ho.
Are you serious? At that hour?
Looking like this?
What happened to your face?
Who beat you up?
I wasn't beaten up.
I fell down the stairs earlier.
Do you really want to fall down the stairs?
- Do you?
- What are you doing?
Tell me the truth,
or I can't help but think you set the fire.
What? Darn it.
That makes no sense!
Why not?
You've been jealous of
Kang-ho because I like him.
You like him?
I... No, I don't.
Anyway, so why did you set the fire?
Why?
It wasn't me! It was Oh Tae-soo's guys!
Oh Tae-soo?
- The Oh Tae-soo we all know?
- Yes.
Mi-joo.
I'll be honest.
Kang-ho is in danger.
Mi-joo.
What's going on?
I thought you'd left with Sam-sik.
Report them to the police.
What? Report who to the police?
Those people who want Kang-ho dead.
Ms. Jin.
What did you hear?
Sam-sik told me everything.
He said Kang-ho knew about
Assemblyman Oh's secret.
Assemblyman Oh Tae-soo's secret?
His illegitimate son.
Apparently Kang-ho had the
original copy of the DNA test.
He did?
You didn't know?
They went after Sam-sik because of it too.
Why him?
The test result was in the bag...
you'd given to Ms. Park.
What?
So tell me. Where is it now?
Sam-sik had it,
but Oh Tae-soo's men took it from him.
Then it's over now. They have the evidence.
So why are they doing this to Kang-ho?
He must feel uneasy about
Kang-ho knowing the truth.
But why? Kang-ho has lost his memory.
Because if Kang-ho ever regained his memory,
he'd find the evidence again.
That's why he's doing this.
So we must report this now.
No, don't.
Ms. Jin.
We don't have any evidence of this.
Provoking them could put
Kang-ho in further danger.
You still don't get it?
Kang-ho is already in danger.
I know.
That's why...
we're going to leave.
What?
I don't have much time anyway.
Once he wakes up,
we're going to move and go into hiding,
and prepare for emigration.
So Mi-joo, you don't need
to worry about him anymore.
This is ridiculous.
Why must you guys run away,
when Oh Tae-soo is the guilty one?
Let's just report him.
Then the police will reveal the truth...
and protect Kang-ho.
That's how his dad died.
What?
A fire broke out at our farm in the past.
He lost his life...
trying to expose the truth.
No one protected him.
Neither the court nor our neighbors.
Even I, his wife,
was powerless.
That's why...
I was so strict with Kang-ho.
I wanted him to become a powerful person.
He must've resented me so much...
throughout those lonely and painful years.
I'm going to protect Kang-ho.
I won't let him meet the same fate as his dad.
Kang-ho was only able to endure
those lonely and painful years...
because of you.
During those long years he
was preparing for the bar exam,
he always sang "I'm Happy."
That's your favorite song.
♫ I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm ♫
♫ I'm happy
I'm happy ♫
♫ I'm happy ♫
Keep it down. You're being too loud.
There are so many places
that make pancakes in Seoul.
We visited most of them.
You see,
he was craving mung bean pancakes.
But he wasn't happy with any of them.
How is it? Is it good?
How...?
- Looking back,
- Sorry.
It's okay.
He was looking for the taste
of your mung bean pancakes.
Kang-ho...
didn't resent you.
He was worried about you,
and missed you a lot.
Was it you?
Sorry?
Were you the girl...
he wrote about in his journal?
You were the girl he loved to death.
It was you.
That's why...
despite losing his memory,
he still searched for you
and had those feelings.
Mi-joo.
It must've been so hard and painful for you.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry.
I know it's late,
but let me apologize on his behalf.
- I'm truly sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
I should've told you sooner.
It's taken me too long.
That's okay. What could
you possibly be sorry about?
It's all our fault.
- You had no choice...
- I'm...
not married.
Ye-jin and Seo-jin...
are Kang-ho's kids.
But they're my kids now.
I only found out about the
pregnancy after we broke up.
And I decided to have them without him.
I never planned to use them as
an excuse to hold onto Kang-ho.
And I don't intend to get back
with him by using them either.
He may not remember right now.
But he abandoned me in the past.
He didn't.
Kang-ho...
wanted to avenge his dad.
So he was going to become
the son of his dad's murderer,
and marry the accomplice's daughter.
What do you mean?
Are you saying his dad was murdered by...?
Song Woo-byeok...
and Oh Tae-soo.
Kang-ho never abandoned us.
If things went haywire,
he knew we'd be in danger...
for being his loved ones.
That's why he chose to leave us.
The only person...
he ever abandoned...
was himself.
Kang-ho.
Kang-ho, are you awake?
Mom.
Mi-joo.
Are you Mr. Choi Kang-ho?
Who are you?
Police.
We already explained
everything to the other officers.
What are you referring to?
Aren't you here because of the fire?
Or did you...?
Mr. Choi.
You're under arrest on suspicion
of murdering Ms. Hwang Soo-hyun.
An anonymous source sent these photos to us.
Then four hours later,
these photos were taken
on the coast of Taebu Island.
As for Ms. Hwang Soo-hyun,
her body was found near Jemyeon Island,
which is about 3 miles from Taebu Island.
She was wearing the same
clothes and bag from that day.
So...
are you insinuating that my son murdered her?
Mr. Choi.
You know her, right?
No.
What about this baby?
You often visited her at
the postpartum care center!
Everyone there thinks you're the dad!
What are you talking about?
He had a fiancée back then.
And we suspect that's the
reason he committed this crime.
He must've had to get rid of
Ms. Hwang Soo-hyun and the baby...
to become the son-in-law
of such a powerful family.
Unbelievable.
I'll be honest.
The woman and her baby...
aren't related to him. They're...
Mom, I'm hungry!
What?
I'm hungry. I want to eat.
- Kang-ho.
- What?
- Food.
- Kang-ho!
What are you doing?
No, don't do this!
Don't do this!
What the...?
- That's not a rag.
- Kang-ho.
You aren't hurt?
Mom, I'm hungry. I want to go home.
I'll bring you some food.
No, I want to go home.
Those men keep yelling at me.
I'm so scared. I want to go home.
- Kang-ho!
- Get him.
Don't do that!
- Get him!
- Mom!
Kang-ho!
Come here!
- Stay still.
What are you doing?
That hurts!
Let him go!
It's okay. It's Mom.
You're all right.
Let's go home.
Tell me.
Does being in the same
car make him the murderer?
Do you have proof he killed her?
How could you use force on
my son who isn't mentally stable?
I want to see your chief.
I'm going to sue you all for violating
the Rights of Persons with Disabilities!
It's okay.
Thank you for lending us your tracksuit.
Should I send it back by courier?
I'm going to gather evidence and come back.
So keep it with you.
Don't even think about running away.
That'll only aggravate his penalty.
Kang-ho.
Gosh, I stink.
I'm going to take a shower.
I've been waiting for a very long time.
Aren't you going to greet me?
You're back.
Welcome back.
It's been a while.
I was so afraid...
I might never see you again.
I knew...
I had to...
ask for your forgiveness
for everything I'd done.
I was afraid I might never be able to do that.
I'm sorry, Kang-ho.
It was wrong of me.
I'm back,
Mother.
Mom, I think you should stay at the hospital.
Kang-ho.
I'm okay.
By the way, how did you know?
How couldn't I? I'm your mom.
You could be an actor.
That was some incredible acting.
I had to get out of there at all costs...
to do what I needed to do.
What do you...?
Don't tell me...
No, Kang-ho.
It's too dangerous. I won't allow it.
Father,
Hwang Soo-hyun, and the fire at our farm.
You still don't get it?
They'll keep coming after us.
All the evidence is gone.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know things would pan out this way.
Kang-ho.
Let's just leave.
Why don't we go somewhere far away?
That's what Ms. Hwang tried to do,
and look...
what happened to her.
They'll find us...
one way or another.
So we must find evidence against
them before they do anything to us.
But how will you possibly do that?
You need seven different lies...
to conceal one.
It's the same with crimes.
To conceal one,
you need to commit multiple crimes.
And there's always evidence left behind.
I'll find it at all costs.
However, no one can find out
I've regained my memory...
until everything is over.
And you should never be alone.
Do you understand?
I got you.
Wait for me.
That's impressive.
Pasta or pizza?
Babe, how are you guys here together?
We ran into each other.
Let me pack up. One minute.
- Sure.
- Gosh.
Gosh, my babies. Aren't you cold?
It's okay.
Hi, Ye-jin and Seo-jin.
It's Mr. Kang-ho.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
Honestly, I didn't recognize you either.
Did you get a new hat?
You're wrong!
He's worn this hat more than ten times!
It's okay if you don't recognize me.
I'd know you from a mile away.
Come here.
Ye-jin and Seo-jin...
are Kang-ho's kids.
Isn't he the prosecutor from last time?
When Nails Come
What...
did you just say?
Petit Nail.
Bar Exam Meal.
Fried-tofu rice balls. Ten square root of two.
I remember everything now.
Does this mean you're all better now?
Yes.
I see.
I'm so relieved.
You're better now?
Then I can give you a beating now, you scumbag.
Hey!
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to die multiple times a day.
I cried, cursed,
and resented you every single day.
How could you put a pregnant
woman through such a difficult time?
You know why Ye-jin and
Seo-jin are bad-tempered?
It's all because of you, you scumbag!
If I ever saw you again,
I was going to kill you.
But you were unwell.
So I just waited until you got better.
Then I found out that...
you were in more pain than I was.
I'm the one who was abandoned and hurt.
So why can't I resent you for what you did?
Why did you have to suffer more than me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mi-joo.
But Mi-joo,
don't forgive me just yet.
What?
The thing I have to do
without you hasn't ended yet.
So don't...
forgive me just yet.
Keep cursing and resenting me...
for now.
Once I come back safe and sound,
I'll beg and ask for your forgiveness.
And I'll be the one waiting...
for your forgiveness.
Hi, Sung-ae.
It's me.
Please come to the village
hall with Mr. Bang by 6 p.m.
And don't eat beforehand.
Okay, see you then.
Who is it?
What brings you here?
I heard there was a fire at your farm.
Is that farm cursed or something?
It's one misfortune after another.
Tell me about it.
I should've just sold that cursed farm...
to a certain despicable guy back then.
What a shame.
"Despicable guy"?
That despicable guy is leaving. I'm moving out.
I have something for you before I leave.
I see.
There's no need for parting gifts,
but I appreciate the thought.
No, not that. I came to return your container.
I see.
Goodness.
I feel bad...
for a lot of things I did to you.
Take good care of yourself.
Here.
You have to survive.
Wait.
A goodbye party?
He's moving to Seoul tomorrow.
Is that why...
you made all this food by yourself?
After everything he's done to you?
Maybe she poisoned the food.
- Goodness.
- Are you serious right now?
Goodness, I'm sorry I'm late.
- Come on in.
- Come in.
Hi, kids.
- Come here.
- My babies.
Welcome. My dear Ye-jin.
You like pancakes, don't you?
I also brought mandu soup and
radish-water kimchi, your favorites.
Sit down.
- Sit down.
- Goodness.
You shouldn't have cooked...
when you haven't even fully recovered yet.
- Where is Kang-ho?
- Sorry?
The doctors needed to
run a few more tests on him,
so he's still at the hospital.
Don't worry. He's much better now.
I'm truly grateful for all you've done...
- to save our farm.
- Please.
I'm also sorry...
I failed to appreciate you all
because I was so focused on working.
- Stop that.
- What's gotten into her?
From this moment on,
I'm going to put aside my worries,
and live happily with you all.
- Sure.
- Do that.
Yes.
There's even a song about it.
♫ Let's put aside our worries ♫
♫ and cha-cha-cha ♫
Cha, cha, cha.
♫ and cha ♫
Come on!
Is this why you brought me?
One, two.
- One, two, three, four.
♫ If you can't stop them ♫
♫ from leaving ♫
♫ don't turn your back and cry ♫
♫ Spare yourself the tears ♫
♫ Tomorrow ♫
♫ there will be ♫
♫ a new wind ♫
- Three, four.
♫ Let's put aside our worries ♫
♫ and cha-cha-cha ♫
Imagine the expectations
I had when I assigned...
such an important task to you.
Didn't I tell you that Woobyeok Group...
and all our lives were at stake?
I'm sorry, sir.
We didn't expect it to drag on for so long.
But thankfully, we caught...
What's so hard about killing that idiot?
Darn it.
Darn it!
Were you the one who sent these...?
Mr. Oh!
What happened to Kang-ho?
He was questioned this morning about
Hwang Soo-hyun and released a while ago.
He was released?
A vehicle was recovered at the
scene of the accident on Taebu Island.
And the doors and windows
were locked from the inside.
So you're telling me...
Hwang Soo-hyun was never
in the car to begin with?
That means Kang-ho duped me.
Then who killed her?
Oh Tae-soo
Tail him,
and make sure you see it through.
Choi Kang-ho
Supreme Prosecutors' Office
- You're home. Goodness.
- Mom!
- Hey. Goodness.
- Did you have fun?
My dear Mi-joo.
My pretty Mi-joo.
- Goodness, here's a kiss.
- Right.
- You let a sick person drink?
- I only had one glass.
Just one.
I'm in such a great mood today.
Tell me about it.
It's unlike you to drink like that,
and insist on sleeping at our home tonight.
I'm going to sleep with Seo-jin and Ye-jin.
- Seo-jin and Ye-jin...
- Goodness me!
- Let's put her to bed.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
Ye-jin.
- Seo-jin. Wait for me.
- Let's go.
- Wait for me.
- You're killing me.
- Well done.
- Let's sleep together.
- Goodness.
- You guys, come here.
- Mi-joo...
Let's go outside.
- Let's let her sleep.
- I want to sleep with them.
- Ye-jin and Seo-jin.
- Turn off the light.
- Okay, you can sleep with them.
- My babies.
- Let's sleep together.
- Ye-jin and Seo-jin.
My babies.
- Everyone was so happy today.
- I'm sorry.
They were all dancing and singing.
Really?
Why were they so happy?
I'm not sure.
I think they were happy to
hear that Mr. Baek was leaving.
What's this?
I took several videos to show you,
but none of them got saved.
Give it to me.
Let me see.
Look.
Your storage is full.
You should've deleted
unnecessary ones beforehand.
None of them are unnecessary!
They're all my work.
Really?
Okay.
What's this?
That?
I filmed Kang-ho's ex-fiancée.
Just delete it. It's the
most useless video ever.
- I hate it.
- Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Do you see this Banz?
My grandma told me that...
only those who are very rich can drive one.
All right. Let's take a peek inside.
I see the lady Kang-ho brought with him.
She took something out of her bag.
No way.
They both could've died,
so why would she slip him pills?
I heard the driver that day was a woman.
Then it makes absolutely no sense.
Why would she spike her own drink?
I'm sure they were some supplements.
What's important is that
Kang-ho drove when they departed.
That means they switched places midway.
They could've done that if he was tired.
But the reason is just strange.
Apparently Kang-ho fell asleep,
and she was outside the car
when the accident happened.
That's why she was unscathed and met me.
Isn't it so odd?
Well...
It's too convenient to call it a coincidence.
This won't do.
I need to meet her.
What? Hey.
You can't do that!
Can't you see the state I'm in?
I even eat in here in case
those men come back for me.
It's too dangerous to go by yourself.
Don't worry.
I won't be going alone.
I can't believe this.
Hey!
Mi-joo.
I'm truly honored and touched that
you chose me to do this with you.
But this isn't right. It's too dangerous.
Then will you live in a closet forever?
A closet is better than a coffin.
You've never met those guys.
If I'm caught again, I really might end up dead!
- Look.
- What?
- Now!
- Hey, Mi-joo!
Are you insane? Goodness.
Who is it?
Hello, is this Ha-young's home?
I'm a close friend of hers.
But I couldn't reach her.
Is she home right now by any chance?
I'm sorry, but she's not home.
Then can I...?
Darn it.
Sillim Fresh Raw Fish
He's not here?
Right.
He sold the restaurant a year ago and left.
Where did he go?
I'm not entirely sure where he went.
But we suddenly lost touch.
Hello?
Hello, who is this?
Prosecutor Choi, it's me.
Investigation Officer?
Your car suddenly disappeared,
so I called your mother to check.
We were the only ones who
knew where the car key was.
I'm truly glad.
I knew you'd come back.
- Sir.
- Yes?
I still have some work to do,
so please keep this a secret until then.
Of course.
I'm forever indebted to you.
You know me.
Have I ever asked you to lend me money?
But my mother is getting surgery tomorrow.
Could you please help me out this once?
I'll pay you back at all costs.
Hello?
Hello...
Woobyeok Paper Company's corporate
transaction records and ledger...
for the third and fourth quarters are missing.
I'm sorry. I'll find them and get it to...
- Sir?
- Take care of your personal matters...
so you can focus on work.
You don't have to come
to work until the weekend.
Take good care of your mother.
My mother would've passed away
without having a chance to get surgery,
if you hadn't helped me back then.
Maybe that's why I couldn't say no
to anything your mother asked of me.
Don't worry.
I'll help you no matter what.
Goodness.
You've been throwing up all day.
You shouldn't have drunk in your state.
Shouldn't we go to the hospital?
We already know what I have.
My body has become too weak to
handle a single glass of makgeolli.
Oh, no.
What a small world.
That was random.
I've met Oh Ha-young before.
What? When?
I won't apologize.
There.
What'll you do now?
In that case, it can't be helped.
Goodness, you're still here?
Ha-young's phone is still off.
Ma'am, I really need to see her.
I've been studying abroad for five
years, and I flew in temporarily.
Once I go back,
I don't know when I'll return.
I can't believe that woman.
Could you please...
help me out this once?
- Please.
- My goodness.
You see...
She's a bit sick, so she's
in a hospital right now.
Which hospital?
- I'll visit her.
- No!
Anyway, it'll be difficult to
see her for the time being.
So meet her next time.
Come by again next time.
Next time when?
After the presidential election.
I'm sure you'll be able to meet her then.
Ma'am, please help me.
Please...
That lady...
looked very anxious.
Did you notice it too?
She's in a hospital,
but that lady won't dare
tell you which hospital it is.
And she said you should
come back after the election.
But that's in four months.
How sick could she possibly be,
to be hospitalized for that long?
I don't think the duration matters.
I think it's the election part that's important.
Right. I saw this earlier.
Maybe...
it has something to do with this.
Assemblyman Oh's Daughter
Disappears at Her Wedding...
No way.
Think about it.
The election is right around the corner,
and this is what his daughter did.
Right.
Plus, she's aware of her
father's illegitimate child.
If I were him, I would've broken her
legs and locked her up somewhere.
Do you think she's even in a hospital?
Would he really risk the doctors and
nurses spreading rumors about her?
And is there even a hospital
that admits you for four months?
- Sam-sik!
- My gosh!
I know where it is.
What are you talking about?
The hospital.
It must be...
Woosung Medical Center.
Hey.
What is this?
Can't you read?
It's a medical certificate.
"14 weeks of recovery"?
You didn't expect something
like this when you kicked me?
You messed with the wrong person.
You know who my dad is, right?
Fabricating a medical
certificate is a cakewalk for him.
He could turn someone like you...
into a lunatic and have you
locked up in a hospital forever.
I did hear that your father...
is an assemblyman who'll
be running for President.
"Oh Ha-young"?
But I only just found out...
his last name.
"Woosung Medical Center."
I see.
I understand that Assemblyman Oh
is a powerful figure...
who can fabricate medical certificates,
and threaten innocent people with them.
I'll make sure to remember him during elections.
Do you think she's really here?
She has to be. For Kang-ho's sake.
You and your dear Kang-ho.
Also for your sake, Sam-sik.
People always mention the
most important person last, right?
Right?
Wait up.
Excuse me.
Have you seen this man before?
I don't think so.
Thank you.
May I ask you something?
Have you seen this man before?
Excuse me, sir. May I ask you something?
Gwangmyeongho
Name, Cho Yeong-jae. Age, 55.
After he sold his restaurant in Sillim-dong,
he changed his address to his hometown.
But no one is living there.
And I looked into a boat named
Gwangmyeongho as you asked.
I found out that...
there are boats by that name
in Dangjin, Pohang, and Haenam.
Mr. Cho!
The Good Bad Mother
You've worked tirelessly to support me,
so I'll make sure you don't regret your effort.
Did Mr. Choi run away?
Don't ever come back without a warrant.
Is everything going well?
- That must be where Oh Ha-young is.
- What?
How could you do something so dangerous?
I do know this very secretive place.
Jin Young-soon!
Come out!
I figured the two of them...
needed some time alone.
You weren't with us,
but I was always with you.