THE JUDGE RETURNS
FINAL EPISODE
MAKDONG RESTAURANT
RESTAURANT CLOSED
WE CLOSED AS OF AUGUST
It's Suni's Sundae Soup Restaurant.
The restaurant closed for good last month.
You'll be safe here.
Pink?
You chose these on purpose, didn't you?
I got a car under someone else's name.
The phone is a bonus.
This is cash.
It has
a 60-month interest-free installment plan.
Don't run away with the money.
You're a judge.
I was so proud to have
a judge as a friend!
Sin-jin, that bastard!
- Calm down.
- I'm just so sad!
Still, calm down.
You're bleeding from your neck
and coughing.
I can't let you
kill me twice.
Right, Sin-jin?
We meet again.
I hear you were very worried about me.
What happened?
Sin-jin tried to overthrow Suojae.
That was how Gyo-hun got killed.
And you're returning to Seoul
because I said I needed you.
I asked Mr. Baek to move you back.
That's great.
Yong-hyeon will be so happy
to see me back in Seoul.
Let's get to work.
I thought you'd be gone for good.
I'm impressed that you made it back.
It's just a witness questioning.
How nice is it that I get to say hi?
I love that.
Gosh
I didn't know young people these days
had the nerve to haul an old man in
just to say hello.
What a tough world it is.
The world has gone crazy!
Hello.
We're closed for the day.
I'm Mr. Lee's colleague.
His surgery went well
and he's doing fine.
Really?
- Yes.
- So...
You're sure
our Han-young is safe?
Yeah.
So, don't worry at all.
Don't skip your meals
and stay healthy
until Mr. Lee returns.
Do you understand?
But by the way
did Han-young...
really do that?
Of course not.
He's just being accused.
My goodness.
My Han-young...
Who did that?
Who's the jerk
accusing my Han-young of murder?
"Father
and mother
I'll find the one who accused me
prove my innocence
and return proudly."
Had Mr. Lee been here
he probably would've said that.
Thank you.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
That'll be 3,500 won.
Don't tell me you believe
what you hear on the news
about Han-young.
Who would believe that nonsense?
Don't cry.
Han-young can tell when you're crying.
Focus on your studies all the more.
And here.
Don't forget your treats.
Okay.
CEO YU SEON-CHEOL
You called me?
Why didn't you just go home? You're drunk.
You told me to come here.
Go to a school abroad.
You brought the evidence for Han-young.
You might get involved
in an unnecessary mess.
I...
didn't like living here, anyway.
Don't tell me...
I'll leave.
I'll leave, okay?
I'll go abroad to study.
Sin-jin was
always close by.
After all, who hasn't gone to court
from political or business circles?
Prosecutors and attorneys can talk
all they want
but at the end of the day
the judge gets the final say.
Who is it this time?
Hmm?
You were the first name he mentioned.
Of course.
I must've disappointed the old man
big time.
You look like you're going to war.
Hurry.
From the Executive Branch
to Hanyang's development
and National Pension investments
Suojae had a grip on everything.
What was going on in Suojae?
So, it's...
Mr. Lee!
How are you? Are you okay?
Your neck.
I'm fine.
Yeah, that's not the focus.
I'm being accused of murder!
Any questions about that?
- Who'd believe that?
- I'd sooner believe in ghosts!
You know, I spent the day
visiting your parents and Na-yeong
before coming here.
I told everyone
you were just being framed
and told them to relax.
Don't disappoint me like that.
Thank you.
That's right.
Sin-jin
overthrew Suojae.
First
we need to clear your name.
Someone definitely took your blood
and smeared it on the corpse
and all over the crime scene.
Whoever did it,
Sin-jin must've made them do it.
We have to find Sin-jin first, then.
He has no family or relatives.
Where could he be hiding?
Find me before the police do.
That's the least you can do
to be cleared of the accusation.
Sin-jin wants me
to find him.
Yes, Han Jeong-hun speaking.
Not only will I hide Mr. Jang's record
of illegal political funds
in the last election
but I'll also bury any proof of his bribes
in the National Convention.
Okay.
I understand.
Everyone is here.
You can talk.
All of you are
in the President’s hands and mine.
I just sent you the files
of all your illegal deeds.
But if you help me return
the world will never see those files.
Mr. President
is confessing all our secrets
to the prosecution.
If Mr. President goes down,
he'll take the fall for it all.
I'll make him.
Nothing will change from before.
I'll replace Mr. President
and work with you all
to lead our nation.
That's impressive for someone
who's on the run.
Sin-jin knows
all the Suojae members' dirty secrets.
He'll try to use them
to go back to where he was.
Sin-jin is a murderer. He killed Gyo-hun.
Whether he accuses someone
or kills more people to silence them
he believes he can do anything he wants.
That's Sin-jin for you.
We can't let him have it his way.
You came sooner than I expected.
How have you been?
Well
it's not too bad.
This has all the files
on the Suojae members.
It contains
their second phone numbers.
But I've been very busy lately.
With the serial cabbage theft
and Kkamang, the breeding goat.
Serial cabbage theft
and Kkamang, the breeding goat?
You can add this
to your list, then. It's nothing big.
You realize this is the southernmost city?
If I get pushed out any farther
I might meet the Little Mermaid
and her family.
There will be a feud in Suojae soon
and they'll all be on their own.
So, first
let's start by tracking
the Suojae members' second phones.
I have to track every single one, right?
LIST OF SECOND PHONE NUMBERS
OF THE SUOJAE MEMBERS
Hey, Mr. Kim.
You know the case of cabbage theft?
I've done some research
and it's a really big deal.
We'll need to ask phone service providers
for location tracking.
I put my job on the line
to track those phones.
We need to find
Nam-yong's flash drive that Sin-jin has.
That's the only way
to wipe everyone out at once.
Aren't we in trouble, even if we find it?
Let's think about that after we find it.
Should we side with Sin-jin or not?
We probably should.
Won't the President-elect
try to strike us?
He'll try to achieve something big
in the beginning.
You say that
as if the President-elect has never run
in elections.
I'm sure
Sin-jin, that snake, doesn't just have
our lives at his fingertips.
Oh!
Illegal campaign funds.
Did you request for support?
Are you crazy? What, to get you arrested?
Roll the window down and raise both hands.
Hello.
I'm on duty.
Yes.
That's a record
of politicians and law firms
bribing judges in court.
Han-young knows about the restaurant
so the police may barge in anytime.
Keep all of it safe
until I return.
Okay.
Will do, Mr. Kang.
That's impressive.
I still have enough power to visit prison.
So?
I need your slush fund account.
And what do I get in return?
I'll bring you back to Suojae.
Didn't you try to kill me last time?
Tables have turned.
It's too late.
I've already told
a little too much to the prosecution.
Including things about you.
Once I provide the proof
all of you will get arrested.
You still have a chance.
Testimonies coerced by the prosecution
can be backtracked easily.
No.
The world has changed.
I have all the files Nam-yong collected
from the Election Commission.
The record of illicit political funds
of assemblymen
and the past and present Presidents
that Nam-yong collected
in the National Election Commission.
Of course, you're in it, too.
I already know that.
Of course.
The new President-elect
wore the badge in the last election.
I'm sure
he didn't just use documented funds
to win in that election.
If you snitch on the illegal funds
of the new President-elect
he won't even have the power
to form a new Cabinet.
They'll be eliminated at the hearing,
the Prime Minister included.
A lame-duck government from the start...
The new President-elect
wouldn't appreciate that.
How about an account
with 30 billion won?
At the end of the day,
only money and power persevere.
He just got out.
Okay.
Get Se-hee out of the country fast.
Thanks.
Hey!
Sin-jin just dropped by.
He mentioned some files from Nam-yong.
He has dirt
on the new President-elect, too.
Sin-jin.
Sin-jin is probably trying to return
by blackmailing the President-elect.
I know, but he offered
to get me back in Suojae.
I know he's lying, but I like the idea.
So
I gave him access to a hidden account
that gets 10% of the monthly donations
from Seojin Happiness Foundation.
What a disgusting laugh.
They're all unbelievable.
This is great.
We can definitely arrest Sin-jin
with this.
REPORTER SONG NA-YEON
Yes, Ms. Song.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Hey, Mr. Park.
I watched the news on your investigation
on Seonjin Happiness Foundation.
Good work.
Have you come to surrender?
Turn myself in?
No, I'm here
to clear up some misunderstandings.
Oh, have you had lunch yet?
Do you admit to having murdered
Mr. Woo Gyo-hun?
I told you. You got the wrong idea.
You know Mr. Gwak Sun-won,
who died from gunshot wounds, right?
Not sure.
Here.
Goodness.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR
The leader of the ruling party
and the Suojae members
all testified that you killed Mr. Woo
instead of Sin-jin.
Sin-jin really might return to power
at this rate.
Don't worry.
The tables will turn again.
You bribed Mr. Kang
to be proven innocent, right?
CHLORIDE
He ran away.
I didn't do anything.
No, more like you couldn't do anything.
That's an attempted murder.
CHLORIDE
How about we say
you refused to collude with Sin-jin
on his instigation of murder?
Sorry?
That's right.
I refused.
The speech detailed
the new administration's plans
to fulfill its promises
regarding the economy
made during its campaign.
Mr. Kim said the economic recession....
Breaking news.
Kang Sin-jin, the former Chief Judge
is a new target of investigation
on allegations of soliciting murder
and forming a large illegal slush fund.
Dr. A at the Mirae Medical Center
testified to have been directed
by Mr. Kang
to murder a patient in a coma.
And before passing,
the late former President Park
testified that Mr. Kang was the real owner
of the secret account
that stole
from Seonjin Foundation's funds.
The investigative authorities found
Mr. Kang
having collected funds
from politicians and businessmen
over a very long period of time
and having taken enormous bribes
to rule in favor of people in court.
The Bible.
Now that Gwang-to is dead
Sin-jin is the only one
gripping on the Suojae members.
Did you find anything in Gwang-to's cell?
I checked every corner of it
and only found some personal items
and the Bible...
The Bible?
I'll get rid of Gwang-to,
the crazy shaman believer
and become the leader of Suojae.
When the day comes
I'll need someone to establish
new justice with me.
Gwang-to is into shamanism.
He wouldn't read the Bible.
Did you find anything odd in the Bible?
Man, you scare me sometimes.
There was a talisman in the Bible.
Huh?
DO NOT ENTER
POLICE LINE
TRANSACTION RECORDS OF POLITICAL FUNDS...
This was the source of Gwang-to's power
over the Suojae members.
Bust everyone mentioned here
and Sin-jin will lose all his power.
Looks like I'll be busy
with a big spring clean.
Even once you're done busting Suojae
Sin-jin will still have
another card to play.
Who is it?
Kim Yoon-hyeok,
the judge at the Seoul Central Court.
CASE INVOLVING JEONLIM CORPORATION
DEPUTY CHIEF PROSECUTOR YOO WON-IK
ORDER OF DISMISSAL
OF HANBIT BANK'S ARREST WARRANT
Mr. Yoo.
You'll need to come with us.
Mr. Baek.
Yes.
Let's go.
PARTY LEADER HAN JEONG-HUN
Now isn't the time for this.
Don't you realize what's going on?
Let's start by deleting the files.
Listen to me.
We're the special investigation team
from Seoul Central Prosecutors' Office.
You're all under an emergency arrest
for allegations of abuse of power
violation
of the National Information Security Act
professional negligence,
receiving and offering bribes
and other charges.
So, we meet again, Mr. Jang.
CHAIRMAN JANG YONG-HYEON
No need to worry about me anymore.
Hey, Dad. I dropped Se-hee off.
She should be on her flight by now.
Thanks.
The prosecution has put
the Deputy Prosecutor General,
Jang Yong-hyeon, the Chairman of S Group
Han Jeong-hun,
the Leader of the Daehan Central Party
Lee Ju-chan, the head of Daejin Daily
along with former and current politicians
and business and media leaders
under emergency arrest.
In the former President Park's flash drive
the so-called "the Suojae X-file"
the prosecution found
numerous counts of crimes
committed by the Suojae members
and the former Chief Judge Kang Sin-jin.
Was the court, the last bastion of justice
just a big hideout for criminals?
Kang Sin-jin, the former Chief Judge
under allegations of murder
and instigation of it
was found taking bribes
from politicians and businessmen
to play in their favor in court.
But that's not the worst of it for us.
Over 50 Presiding Judges were found
colluding with the huge violation of law.
This is absurd, to say the least.
Korea's judicial system has
completely fallen.
Come back.
I'm a murder suspect.
Your blood on the corpse
and the murder weapon is circumstantial.
The Suojae guys will retract
their testimonies, too.
Don't make matters worse
trying to get Sin-jin. Turn yourself in.
I'll make sure
you can stay out of custody.
But what if I really did murder Gyo-hun?
Sin-jin only believed what he wanted to
and assumed his decisions were
always right.
And so, he managed to get
over 50 Presiding Judges
to collude with him.
The Judiciary does not hold
absolute justice.
It only strives to.
From that perspective
Lee Han-young,
the murder suspect and judge
shouldn't get to stay out of custody
for his investigation.
For the law is
equal to all.
I'm glad I have a junior like you.
Okay.
I'm only human. I'm the same.
I might even become like Sin-jin
before I realize it.
Did you give the Suojae X-file
to the prosecution?
Yes, sir.
You could've gained a lot from it.
Whether it be money or power
you could've even built the next Suojae.
I'll stick to reading case files
sharpening my pencils
and writing verdicts.
I'll bust Sin-jin and return to the court.
Okay.
Come back and put Sin-jin to trial.
Former President Park's "Suojae X-file"
has turned into "the Kang Sin-jin Gate"
at an astounding pace.
Questions are also arising
regarding the former President's death.
Some are claiming
that this may be another murder
instigated by Kang
and committed by his person.
Han-young knows about the restaurant
so the police may barge in anytime.
Keep all of it safe until I return.
Return? In his dreams.
I'm about to lose my job
just because I took his orders.
I don't want to take the fall for him.
What should I do with these?
Should I burn them all?
Hold these for me for a sec.
Look at these!
These are some precious documents.
You know how to put them on, right?
Come on, Mr. Park.
This is a little aggressive.
You want me to do it?
No, that's not what I mean...
- Cheol-woo...
- It's all over.
If I send this to the President-elect
will he let me get away
or be pardoned?
KIM YOON-HYEOK
You got rid of the files?
Hey, it's Han-young.
I know you were desperate
but Yoon-hyeok? Really?
Oh.
Cheol-woo says thank you.
For all the proof
of the bribes taken in court.
You want to thank him?
Thank you.
I told you to find me
before the police did.
But you're just wasting time.
Just wait.
Once you lose everything you have
and are begging for your life
I'll be standing right before your eyes.
But I wonder
if you still have more cards to play.
You don't think I do?
What, you'll blackmail
the President-elect now?
I walked out of the Prosecutors' Office
on my own
and I'll return to my place soon.
But you're still suspected
of killing Gyo-hun.
Worry about yourself, not me.
He told me to find him
and now, he's going to return
to his place?
He's lying.
That means...
You made connections with smugglers
to catch Yong-jin.
Yeah, why do you ask?
Sin-jin might try
to smuggle out of Korea.
Man, criminals always want to smuggle out.
Alright.
Witness?
Ms. Yu came to see me.
Ms. Kim.
She confessed to having stolen
some gauze with your blood on it.
She used that
to fabricate the murder evidence.
Sin-jin must've made Seon-cheol do it
who would've made
Se-hee do it.
So, Se-hee
wouldn't have had a choice.
Did you know about this?
Is there something going on
between you two?
We were married in our past lives.
What?
I'm kidding.
What a ridiculous joke.
Seriously, what's going on?
MADAM CHOI
CAPTAIN SONG...
MR. KIM, SMUGGLING PEOPLE
Hey, Mr. Kim!
It's me, Seok Jeong-ho.
Yeah.
How are you?
It's nothing big.
Do you still take travelers
on your night ships?
No, it's not for me.
SEONHWAGAK
You okay?
Didn't you ask the same question
when we first met?
You were so young
yet the most desperate beggar I'd seen.
I gave you a fried dumpling
that'd already gone cold
and you stuffed it in your face,
in fear that someone would take it.
I've never had
any food better than that dumpling.
This is Mr. Cho's number.
He's based in Incheon.
He'll do anything for money.
He'll find you a ship.
See you again.
You'd better keep that promise.
Okay?
SEONHWAGAK
I got a call from a smuggling broker.
He's based in Incheon.
I think Sin-jin called him.
Check the address I sent you.
STONE JEONG-HO
I got it.
I texted the address
to Cheol-woo and Jin-a as well.
I'll get on my way now.
Okay.
WANMYEONG-DAERO, SEO-GU
Oh, hi!
Welcome, sir.
When's the ship leaving?
In two to three hours.
I'll pay you the rest once I arrive.
Sure, we can do that.
What are you doing?
Get a drink for the guest or something!
You know
life is so exhausting.
Here.
Come on. Don't make me feel awkward.
You get awkward about nothing, huh?
Get him!
Sir!
You mind if I check your bag?
Are you carrying a gold bar or something?
Bring it.
What are you doing here?
And what are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be glad to see me?
Why didn't you bring your big friend?
That would've been cowardly.
You guys are ridiculous.
Do you always need the boss
to give you an order?
Get on it!
Get them!
Should've found a proper broker
for smuggling.
Yeah.
I didn't know. I'm new to this.
When we get out of here
I promise to free you
of your murder accusation.
I already got that sorted.
Why are you here, then?
To bring you to court.
You think getting rid of me
will bring your justice to the world?
No, I'll prove
that the justice I've chosen is right.
You alright?
Who the hell are you guys?
Wrap it up.
Han-young!
What?
Freeze!
Come with me. Reap what you've sown.
You think this is the end of it?
There's no end.
It's a world full of criminals.
Mr. Yu Seon-cheol.
You're under emergency arrest
on charges of fabricating evidence
witness tampering
and illicit judicial compromise.
Dad!
Who the hell are you?
Do you know where this is?
Mr. Yu Jin-gwang.
This is an arrest warrant for you.
Let's go.
Ms. Yu Ha-na as well.
The investigators are waiting for you two
for tax evasion and witness tampering.
CEO YU SEON-CHEOL
HAENAL LAW FIRM
The trial for Kang Sin-jin,
the former Chief Judge
will proceed tomorrow.
All legal, political, and business leaders
are paying close attention
to the court's decision.
The prosecution is expected
to request the court
to sentence Kang to a life sentence.
Mr. Lee Han-young,
the judge for the first trial
accepted Defendant Kang Sin-jin's request
to broadcast the trial.
How much time
will I get here?
Will I continue
to make new choices
and live with their consequences?
Is this
the end of the suspension
of Defendant Lee Han-young's sentence?
Please rise, everyone.
COURT
Everyone may be seated.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
DEFENDANT
JUDGE
We will now begin
the final hearing
of Defendant Kang Sin-jin's case,
Number 2025GH1562.
As requested
by the Defendant
the court will broadcast the trial.
At last.
The final hearing date for Sin-jin.
CHIEF JUSTICE BAEK YI-SEOK
Defendant Kang Sin-jin
took someone's life
and instigated five murders.
He used his power and authority
to commit atrocious crimes,
violating laws of humanity.
The Defendant had a duty
to protect law enforcement
turned this sacred temple of law
into his personal killing floor.
He also used his wealth and power
to bribe judges
and threatened witnesses
to coerce them into false testimonies.
He destroyed evidence
to hide the truth.
Your Honor
therefore, the prosecution requests
the court consider
the Defendant's violation of Article 250
on Murder, Killing Ascendant
Article 31 on Instigator
Article 129 on Acceptance of Bribe
and Advance Acceptance
Article 123 on Abuse of Authority
Article 152 on Perjury, Malicious Perjury
and
Article 155 on Destruction of Evidence
and Special Exception to Relatives
all of which are serious crimes
and sentence him to capital punishment.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
Defendant Kang Sin-jin.
JUDGE
Where is justice in Korea?
The prosecution fabricates evidence
to turn victims into perpetrators
judges use legal codes to trivialize
the gravity of the crime
and the press pursues profit over truth.
I...
climbed down into the mud
and got my own hands dirty.
To save my nation
that's been swallowed by corruption
and its justice system rotted to the core!
I sacrificed myself for the change.
If that fool of a judge
hadn't gotten in my way
my sacrifice
could've brought
a beautiful renaissance
to justice in Korea.
Plagues and famines.
Mr. Kang
your renaissance would've been
full of nothing but plagues and famines.
It wouldn't have been glorious at all.
You were the same.
You fabricated evidence
murdered witnesses
and took bribes in court
to define who was guilty and who wasn't.
Those were just sacrifices
to achieve greater justice.
Sacrifices that had to be made.
And who agreed to that?
Nobody
agreed with you.
No.
There's no definition of justice
everyone will agree on.
Justice without sacrifices never improves.
Meanwhile
evilness will barge in
and quickly take over the world.
Lee Han-young!
So, your definition of justice is evil.
We need new justice to change the world.
To scrap collectors
justice weighs a kilogram of scraps.
To 12th graders
their grades and university acceptances.
Therefore
justice cannot belong to one individual.
It must belong to all of us.
That kind of justice is too slow!
It's evil!
No.
Justice is not a race.
It's a moral compass.
An individual's idea of justice
cannot change the world.
The only people who believed
they were the only ones to save the world
were dictators.
No!
Justice isn't anything special.
Therefore
as an ordinary human
who feels like everyone else
I am ready to announce
Defendant Kang Sin-jin's verdict.
The court is now ready!
My only crimes are having trusted you...
The court orders Defendant Kang Sin-jin...
and letting you get in my way
of establishing new justice!
...to death.
Han-young!
Justice is
nothing special.
So, you never found the flash drive
Nam-yong gave Sin-jin?
Sin-jin refused to turn it in
until the end.
He's still clinging to his wicked dream,
even after all this.
How foolish.
I guess
the prosecution didn't need it that badly.
Probably not.
Oh, by the way
I've decided not to join Haenal.
Did Se-hee call you?
Basically.
I was told they'd be canceling
my contract as their legal advisor.
With Mr. Yu Seon-cheol
Mr. Yu Jin-gwang, and Ms. Yu Ha-na
all arrested
I guess Se-hee couldn't handle the firm
on her own.
She seems to have left Haenal
in the hands of the lead counsel.
So, you don't keep in touch with her?
No.
Did he move on to someone new already?
He said she was a colleague.
Come on.
How can a judge be colleagues
with a prosecutor?
Have you never been to the court?
They all work in the legal field.
They're all the same.
Really?
But you know
she kind of seems familiar.
Where have I seen her?
Come on.
Where could you have possibly seen her?
- You're hilarious.
- I guess not.
Those are some loud whispers, huh?
My parents once told me
about you.
They said a teenager visited them,
asking them to forgive her dad.
And that they felt terrible
for not inviting her to a meal.
Enjoy.
I still haven't apologized properly
and owe them so much.
You're paying back by enjoying this meal.
You're paying them back now.
Okay.
The food is extra good today.
Do the dishes suit your taste?
Yes, they're delicious.
Have more.
- We have a lot more.
- Thank you.
Back then, I was too young
that I ran away
without a proper apology.
I'm sorry.
I hope your father recovers.
He's come a long way.
He's much better.
Glad to hear that.
What a wonderful person you've become.
- Thank you.
- She's beautiful, too.
Have some apple slices.
Okay.
THE FIRST FINAL LEET MOCK EXAM
I didn't think
she'd actually apply for law school.
JUDGE
Defendant Jang Su-gyeong
has served her sentence through life
for what happened to Suni.
This was proven
by Reporter Song's interview
of the local merchants
and Mr. Seok Jeong-ho...
WITNESS
who grew up at the market.
JUDGE
I hereby order
Defendant Jang Su-gyeong
to continue living the way she has been
as an earnest and kind neighbor,
sharing love with her neighbors
and living to the fullest
with memories of Suni
for all the years
Suni didn't get to live.
Su-gyeong got married
and had her first child after a year,
named Suni.
One busy day of endless customers
she had no time to check on Suni
and the poor baby had
a blanket suffocating her.
Since then, whoever she met
she referred to her family,
"Suni's family."
Because she felt so bad for Suni,
who didn't even live a year.
And for the guilt
of not having served jail time
which made her feel even more guilt.
So, she made a vow
to live with guilt
for the rest of her life.
Can you rent an office
to a reporter of principles
who's a little poor?
Sorry?
I quit my job at Daejin Daily.
I'm going to run a solo news agency.
"Song Na-yeon TV."
- You want to join me?
- Yes!
That soon?
I'll do anything with you.
Really? How should we split the profits?
I heard you liked these.
What happened to Seonhwagak's owner?
They have great jjajangmyeon.
The chef is the owner.
They can't get rid of the chef.
SUOJAE
WHERE HOPE AND TOMORROW WAITS
CORRECTIONAL FACILITY
Is everything over now?
Does this mean
it's all over now?
Or
do I have to keep living this life
to serve my time
for what I'd done in my past life?
Sure.
Whatever is coming in my way
will I continue to choose
justice over everything?
Here's your order of meat!
The food is amazing!
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE EXPANSION!
JEONGYUK RESTAURANT
Everyone!
Han-young!
Hi!
Welcome to our restaurant!
One soup for Han-young, Auntie!
- Come and eat.
- Is it good?
We'll take some sundae and pyeonyuk, too.
NEW OPENING OF SUNI'S RESTAURANT
THE JUDGE RETURNS
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim