NO TAIL TO TELL
And as for you.
I'll be coming for you soon.
No!
Mr. Lee.
Hey. Did you get it?
Yes, sir.
But what do you need this for?
Move, damn it.
I was… thinking about this all wrong.
Pardon?
I'm done shaking like an idiot
over those wretched things.
Sorcery, spirits, whatever.
I'll just shoot them all dead.
We humans
have our own ways.
EPISODE 11
THE WAY OF HUMANS
THIRTY HOURS AGO
SUNCHEON STADIUM
Eun-ho.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I think it was just a dream.
It has to be.
I guess I'm just anxious.
Anxious about what?
It's just…
This isn't just a breeze.
A storm is about to hit.
What are you thinking about?
- What?
- Man…
Anyway, what happened to the coach?
The game's about to start.
Why isn't he here yet?
We don't even have a starting lineup.
Don't you think
Coach has been acting weird lately?
Do you think he got a scouting offer?
Is he dumping us mid-season
for another team?
Don't talk nonsense.
Guys, it's not like that.
Why not? It could happen.
He's right. Sure, Coach has always
ranked last in the fourth division,
and his playing career wasn't remarkable.
His tactics are old-school,
his training predictable,
but that doesn't mean
he couldn't get an offer.
You know, Si-yeol,
you have a habit of looking down
on our coach way too much.
Whoa! Hi, Coach.
Why don't you just badmouth me,
you punk?
Coach, why are you so late?
What about the starting lineup?
We don't even have any tactics,
and we haven't analyzed
the opposing team at all.
How are we supposed to play?
Forget that. Don't worry too much.
Anyway, that's not what matters today.
I have a really important announcement.
What?
What are you doing out there?
Come on in.
From now on, she'll be working
with our team as our new GM.
This is Ms. Hong Yeon-su.
Come on. Let's give her a hand.
Okay… but Coach,
the game's about to start,
and this is supposed to be
your big announcement?
Not exactly. There's something else.
Well, what's your match fee these days?
It's… 50,000 won.
- Right. And your win bonus?
- It's 300,000 won.
Starting today, our players' match fee
won't be 50,000 won anymore.
It will be 200,000 won.
Did she say 200,000 won?
- It's 200,000 won?
- 200,000?
And the win bonus went up a bit too.
How much?
One million won.
For real?
What…
- Oh yeah!
- One million won!
Hey, hang on. Quiet!
Coach, is this for real?
- Of course it is!
- Yeah!
Hey! Are you guys ready
to play for real today?
- Yes!
- Do you need tactics?
- No!
- Do we need to analyze the other team?
All right, let's go!
Hey! We're going positionless!
- Let's do it!
- Show them how it's done!
DAEHEUNG WINS ANYTIME, ANYWHERE
Maybe it's because
I heard all that crappy nonsense.
I can't believe I had
that stupid dream again.
It's starting to get to me.
Okay. One, two!
- Daeheung, Daeheung, let's go!
- Let's go!
- There's Si-yeol.
- Suncheon!
What's gotten into them today?
I dangled some money in front of them.
Look at them. They're full of energy now.
They're running around like excited mutts.
- You…
- My bad.
I forgot to tell you
that I'm now the owner of that loser club.
The owner?
I did some digging,
and you seem pretty tight
with Kang Si-yeol over there.
Funnily enough, he and I go way back too.
I'm sure
you're already aware of that.
You're acting pretty cocky today.
Last time we met,
you couldn't even look me in the eye.
Not anymore.
I heard
you're just an ordinary human now.
You know, I've got to admit
that I was terrified of you.
I never knew when you'd show up
or what you'd do,
so I just hid like a scared little coward.
Man, that felt…
like absolute shit.
What are you plotting?
I'm just here to let you know
that things have changed.
You must've enjoyed looking down on us,
toying with people
like it was all a game to you.
But now it's my turn.
Here in the human world,
I'll show you how hellish life can get
when you cross someone like me.
Luckily, I still have that much sway.
- Yeah!
Coach, we won a million won!
A million won! I can't believe this!
It's a million won!
- Unbelievable!
- A million won!
I'm going to start
by targeting the people around you,
one by one.
What?
Where's the fun
in ending things so quickly?
Now that the tables have turned,
don't you think it's only fair
for me to toy with you?
Hey, did you see that?
I want you to be terrified,
never knowing when I'll strike,
feeling like shit
for being such a pathetic mess.
We're going to kill her.
- Hey!
- What?
- What's wrong?
What are you doing, Si-yeol?
Si-yeol!
Man, this is fun already.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Oh boy.
- What do you want?
Is this allowed when the game's still on?
Tell me why you keep
lurking around Eun-ho!
You know why.
I have a score to settle with that fox.
You bastard.
Oh my God!
Hey, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
Man, that hurts.
Sir, are you okay?
You really need to control
your players better, Coach.
He's not an athlete. He's a total thug.
You little--
- Hey.
- Come on.
Oh my. You're bleeding.
Seriously, what was that?
We started off strong,
so I thought we'd win.
Si-yeol!
Where is he? Where is that bastard?
- Coach!
- No, Coach!
- Si-yeol, you…
- Whoa, calm down.
Si-yeol isn't here.
- He's not? Okay, fine.
- Si-yeol's gone.
So where did
that bastard go then?
Well,
I think he left early
after getting the red card.
What? He left?
Wow, the least he could do is
get on his knees and beg for forgiveness,
but he just left?
Seriously, is he nuts?
I'm sure he left because he felt
too embarrassed to face us--
Sure! That jerk has it real easy, right?
He has amazing team spirit.
Hey, I'm tearing up.
Seriously, I'm so moved.
But you know what?
Thanks to Si-yeol, our team is screwed.
Come on, Coach.
I mean, Si-yeol did mess up,
but I'm sure it's not that bad.
We'll do better in our next match.
Oh, sure.
Just do better in the next match.
Right. But do you know
who Si-yeol beat up today?
He was none other than
our new club owner.
A member of the family
that owns Geumsu Group!
Wait, hold on. A billionaire?
Wait, does that mean our team
is owned by a huge conglomerate?
Not anymore, you idiot!
Because of Si-yeol, the deal is off!
Your 200,000-won match fee
and the million-won win bonus
are all gone.
And since we have no sponsor,
our team really is shutting down for good!
Si-yeol, that bastard!
He punched the new club owner
right in the face!
And he landed a direct hit!
Guys! What am I supposed to do now?
I'm going to kill…
- Hey…
- Coach! Your knees!
Hey! Call 911!
SUNCHEON STATION
- Where are we going?
- Straight back to Seoul.
What's going to change if we leave?
I know, but…
You know what kind of guy he is.
He tried to kill you back then.
He did.
When he showed up like that,
you should've run or screamed.
That's what you should've done.
You're not who you used to be.
I know that.
It was so unexpected.
I think I just froze.
Still, you shouldn't have
run out mid-game.
It's not like something bad
was going to happen right away.
Si-yeol.
I was so scared.
Seeing him there, right next to you,
I couldn't think of anything else.
I was just scared.
Honestly, I still am.
There's nothing I can do
to protect you right now.
If he tries
to pull something on you again,
I don't even know what I should do.
Don't worry.
Looks like they found out
that I became human
and that I'm trying to change back.
Worst case, I can ask
the eight-tailed fox for help.
It'll be fine.
It's okay.
Sis.
Can you really not hear me?
What just happened?
Wake up.
Hand over your fox bead.
I've got a good use for it.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
What?
My fox bead
isn't on me right now.
Seriously, what do I do?
I already told him where my fox bead is.
And I can't even warn her to be careful.
Let's move as soon as we get to Seoul.
It's way too cramped
and uncomfortable anyway.
And then, we'll get you
back to normal as soon as…
- Wait a second.
- Yeah?
Have you always had that sweater?
You mean this?
I found it while packing. Is it weird?
No, it's just…
I've just never seen it before.
I've had this for a really long time.
My grandma bought it for me.
So it wasn't a dream.
It's a future I can't change or avoid.
Are you telling me to choose?
Kill Si-yeol, or give up who I am?
It may seem cruel,
but fate simply takes its course.
It does not concern itself
with individual human affairs.
Once the storm rises,
everyone gets swept away.
Can you truly handle that for a lifetime?
Si-yeol.
What exactly are we being swept up in
to face a future like that?
Why would you…
Si-yeol.
I can't do this.
- What?
- I've been thinking…
and I don't want to just leave like this.
We came here for a trip.
I don't want to just run away
like we're being chased.
Let's get off this train.
They say this village has been here
since the Joseon Dynasty.
Even these thatched houses
are hundreds of years old--
Did you forget who I am?
What?
I used to live in places like this
back in the day.
You call this a tourist spot?
It's just a regular village.
Oh, right.
I saw that this was a famous tourist spot
around here.
- Should we go somewhere else?
- No, we came all this way.
Come on, let's look around.
Oh man…
Si-yeol.
Give the roof a little shake
with that stick.
The roof? Why?
To make the grubs fall down.
They should be nice and plump
right about now.
What? Aren't grubs bugs?
What would you need them for?
Since we're here,
you should try them as a snack.
No way. What are you talking about?
Try it. Do you want me to catch one?
You don't have to. I said no.
They taste better than you think.
Back in the day, old folks used to use
grubs as medicine, you know?
- I'll catch one for you.
- Wait…
What…
Hey, don't. Don't do it!
- Why? I'll get you a grub.
- Forget the grub.
But we came all this way.
You have to try it.
Wait, just put it down. Seriously.
Come on, you should have a taste.
Hey, I'm not eating it!
SAMSHIN
Samshin. Like this.
Do this one too.
- I'm not doing it anymore.
- Come on.
Forget it, I'm done.
I'm not doing it.
- Here, lie down.
- What? No way.
- Please lie down, just once.
- No, let's just look around and go.
Come on, just lie down once.
- Please?
- No. You're going to hit me.
No, wait.
Hey!
- What?
- Nice!
- Give me your palm.
- No. Let's do it again.
- Come on, give me your wrist.
- No!
Hey, what are you doing?
You can't throw it like that!
Oh my. Look at this.
Wow, look at this place.
Si-yeol, do you know what this is?
- What is it?
- It's cotton.
Do you know how to make clothes out of it?
First, you take out the cotton seeds.
You take out the seed, and then there's
something called a cotton bow.
And if you beat the seeds with that,
it puffs up like cotton.
Then you take a handful of it,
put it on a sorghum stalk, and spin it…
Here you go.
Open wide.
Mm! It's good.
- It's good, right?
- It's even better because you fed me.
Gosh, stop it.
What's with the sudden photo?
Oh, I just thought you looked pretty.
Gosh.
Take it again. I wasn't ready.
You look so pretty.
It came out well. Let me show you.
It did come out well!
You should stand here too.
This looks like a good photo spot.
Actually, why don't we take one together?
- What?
- Come to think of it,
we don't have any photos together.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Could you take a photo of us?
- Sure.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
Oh, jeez!
You scared the hell out of me.
Seriously.
You can't just walk in here. Damn it.
What is it?
You look like you're already
halfway to the grave.
Catching that other fox
must've been tough on you.
Not yet.
- What?
- I said it's not over.
I couldn't get the fox bead.
What are you talking about?
Then nothing's changed at all.
Jeez.
I went to that former nine-tailed fox
and made all sorts of threats.
If that other monster is still with her,
what am I supposed to do now?
No need to get so worked up.
How can I not get worked up?
You took two billion won from me.
If that other fox is still with her,
do you really think she'll let me be?
You really are a coward.
I bewitched the Seoraksan Mountain fox,
just as planned.
But in exchange,
I burned up all my shamanic power
when I already don't have much time left.
So what's going to happen now?
I'll be dead soon,
unless I find and swallow that fox bead
in the next few days.
That's your problem. But what about me?
What's going to happen to me?
Figure that one out yourself, you punk.
But if you're scared of that fox
sticking around her,
you don't need to worry
about that anymore.
She's just a puppet now,
and she can only do what I tell her.
She'll stay that way until I die.
Really? Are you sure
I don't have to worry about it?
Yes. I ordered her
to go fetch the fox bead herself.
You can see for yourself then…
whether that fox does
what I tell her to do or not.
This is nice.
I'm glad.
I thought today's trip was a total bust
because I took you to a Joseon-era village
when you lived through that era.
Walking through that old village with you
made me feel
like we've known each other forever.
I liked that.
It felt like you became
a small part of all those years
I spent alone in my past.
Next time, let's go somewhere better.
Somewhere you've never been.
Then I can be part of your past
and your future, right?
Yeah. That'd be really nice.
Si-yeol.
Should we just…
stay like this and not go back?
What?
I could just be an ordinary human.
And instead of being the famous
Kang Si-yeol that everyone knows,
you'd stay a fourth-division player,
just like now.
Hey.
I was just joking,
but you went all quiet,
and now it feels way too serious.
Okay. Let's do it.
What?
If that's what you want, let's do it.
Are you really okay living like this?
Your dreams, your hard work,
and everything you've achieved
are not part of this life.
How can you be okay with that?
And you saw what happened earlier.
People with a grudge against me
are coming after you too.
If we stay like this,
it won't be a normal life.
We might have to spend our lives
looking over our shoulders.
I'm not saying it would be okay.
I'm saying I'm okay with it not being okay
What does that even--
I know you're hiding something from me.
Ever since we came back
from visiting Woo-seok at the hospital,
you've been acting weird.
I don't know what it is,
but knowing you,
you'd have told me already
if it wasn't a big deal.
You're struggling alone,
and you can't even tell me,
so it must be a problem we can't solve.
Si-yeol…
If it's a matter of choice,
of course I want to go back
to how things were.
Like you said, my life, my hard work,
the dreams that I achieved
all mean a great deal to me.
However,
if you try your best
to change things back and still can't,
it's okay.
I'll just accept it.
It's not over yet, and I haven't given up.
I'll keep trying to find the best solution
for both of us until the very last moment.
I know.
But I'm scared.
I'm scared that we'll get swept away
by fate or that damn will of Heaven.
I'm scared…
that I won't be able to protect us.
Si-yeol,
I think…
I really like you.
What?
I specifically asked for twin beds,
but it's a double.
Maybe we should've
just gone back to Seoul.
Yeah, maybe.
But then again, we are on a trip.
Right. And it's late.
- And we're tired from all the walking.
- Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
Do you want to look around?
Sure.
- Yeah.
Here, give me that.
Yeah, okay.
Hey,
we've been living in the same house.
Why are you being so awkward?
Who, me? I'm not being awkward.
Seriously, I'm not.
Maybe you're feeling awkward.
Not at all. I don't feel awkward.
Oh, right.
I should ask them to switch rooms.
It's fine.
What?
I mean, this room is actually really nice.
It's got an ocean view and everything.
So, you don't have to go ask.
You told me not to, okay?
What?
I love you.
- Are you awake?
- Yeah.
When did you wake up?
Just now.
- Do you want to sleep a bit longer?
- Yeah, just a little.
But seriously…
I just don't get him.
He's a lunatic. Why did he have to
drag us down with him?
And why is he skipping training
like he's done nothing wrong?
Forget all that.
Is there even any point
in training like this?
Most of us can't even transfer anywhere.
We're all just
going to be forced to retire.
I knew Si-yeol
would eventually mess up big time.
Man, I'm tired.
I was so stressed that
I couldn't get a wink of sleep last night.
- Want one?
- Thanks.
Give me one too.
It's kicking in now.
Man, caffeine really helps.
I'm done with Si-yeol.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I mean, if he messed up that badly,
he should be begging
the owner for forgiveness.
Or at least try to fix it.
How can he ghost us instead?
I'm so pissed off.
Should I try calling him or something?
Forget it. Don't bother.
Excuse me. Is the coach in?
- Hello.
Coach didn't come in today.
Oh, really?
What brings you here?
Well, it's just…
I think I know why Si-yeol
acted the way he did yesterday.
I think I might have made a mistake.
I can't believe
that I completely forgot about that.
What do you mean?
Are you sure
you don't need to go to training?
How could I go anywhere
and leave you alone?
I'm not leaving your side for a while.
Jeez, I'm not a child.
It's for the best, actually.
Honestly, we don't have time
to be distracted by training and stuff.
We need to find
the people you listed in your notebook,
and find out where they are
and what they're doing.
You're right.
Oh, wait.
You know that sweater from yesterday?
- Yeah.
- Do you have it right now?
Let's throw it away over there.
What are you talking about?
I told you my grandma bought me that.
Is that the only thing
she ever bought you?
No, I have a lot, but--
Then throw it away. It looks weird,
and the color's wrong for you.
Really, it doesn't suit you.
What do you mean? It looks good on me.
Throw it away.
But it's perfectly fine.
I really like this sweater.
Well, I totally hate it.
Should I throw it away?
Man, that temper of yours. Fine.
I was on edge all day yesterday,
thinking something
would happen at any second.
I should've done this sooner.
What?
Nothing.
Why did we come all the way here?
He'll come out when he's ready.
Come on, stop acting all tough
and just come along.
We're already here anyway.
Si-yeol should've told us that earlier.
I would've lost it too
if the guy who ruined my life
in a hit-and-run suddenly showed up.
I looked him up on our way here.
Turns out he's a murderer,
a total scumbag.
We don't want a person like that
as our club owner, either.
- Yeah.
- Si-yeol did the right thing this time.
Si-yeol!
Hey, Si-yeol!
I don't think he's home.
- Damn it.
- Man, it's cold.
Let's just wait inside.
What the heck?
What happened?
Hey.
Looks like he really got robbed this time.
Why are you standing out here?
You could've waited at home.
Sis.
Yeah?
Give my fox bead back.
Who are you?
What?
Wait.
What do you think you're--
Where is my fox bead?
It wasn't at the house,
and you don't seem to have it on you.
Where did you hide it?
What if I give it to you?
Who are you offering it to?
Don't you know what'll happen to you then?
It's mine.
However I use it is up to me.
Snap out of it.
Did you forget what I told you?
I don't know what that damn shaman did,
but you're just an empty shell,
and the real you is gone--
I guess I have no choice.
For some reason,
I can't even feel the bead's energy.
And it seems like you won't just tell me…
so I'll have to find out for myself.
What are you staring at?
Your family.
Family? Way to kill the mood.
Anyway, how much longer do I have to wait?
It won't be long.
I doubt I'll have any time left
after tonight anyway.
You might not know this,
but in here,
there are all sorts of minor spirits
that hold a grudge against me.
They're just waiting for me to die
so they can rip my soul to pieces.
Why say things like that
to someone living a normal life,
unaware of such things?
I used to live blissfully unaware too.
If you get that fox bead,
does that mean you won't die today?
No.
It's more than that.
I'll become immortal.
What do you mean…
I'm going to become a deity.
What?
Spiritual beings like the nine-tailed fox
are like demigods, not mere animals.
So if I steal their fox bead
and swallow it,
I can shed this human form
and become a deity.
So? What's your plan
after becoming immortal?
Revenge.
You must know roughly
what happened to my family,
since you did some digging on me.
Yeah, roughly.
Just that you refused
the shamanic calling,
and that's why your whole family
ended up that way.
At least my wife died quickly.
It was a car accident.
I was the one behind the wheel,
and I slammed
right into an oncoming truck.
It was like I was possessed.
I didn't have control over my body.
The car was completely destroyed.
My wife was torn to pieces
right there on impact.
But I was in the driver's seat
and didn't have a single scratch on me.
Since I was their vessel,
they needed me unharmed.
So you finally accepted
the shamanic calling?
No.
Even then,
I cared more about my own life.
So they went after my daughter.
It started out of nowhere.
She was in so much pain,
like she was dying.
But the doctors couldn't find a cause.
I was desperate to save her,
so I tried everything and went everywhere.
Then, she just couldn't take it anymore.
She took her own life
because she wanted the pain to stop.
Is it even possible to get revenge
on those beings?
Of course. Starting with the deity
that did this to us,
I devoured all sorts of minor spirits.
It took me years,
but I hunted them down, one by one.
These marks are the seals.
They don't control me anymore.
I'm the one who controls them.
Wait. Then you already got your revenge.
No. This isn't just about
these minor spirits.
I'm talking about the greater deities
who created a world like this, and…
even this damn world itself.
I'll destroy them all.
I'll live 100 or 1,000 years if necessary.
And if even that isn't enough,
I'll live 10,000 years to see it through.
How is this…
How did I get home?
I was just…
What was I doing again?
Eun-ho!
Geum-ho?
Shopping just isn't fun without you.
We could've grabbed lunch and some coffee.
You really should've come along.
What were you doing here all alone?
Well,
I was just…
But, Geum-ho…
is it really you?
- What?
- I mean, I swear
you became human centuries ago.
And you got married,
then…
you died.
What are you talking about?
Did you have a dream?
A dream?
Forget about that.
Here, try this on.
I bought it because I thought
it'd look good on you.
It must've been a dream.
Come on. You're not a child.
What kind of dream was it?
I'm not really sure.
It felt so vivid, so real.
But now that I'm awake,
I can't remember much.
Just that you weren't with me
and I was alone for a very long time.
I think there was someone else too.
It was just a silly dream. Let's eat.
I picked up some takeout for us.
I mean, it was a really strange dream.
I became a human,
and I think I even dated a man.
You dated a human?
What kind of guy was he?
I don't know. I can't remember that part.
Was he handsome?
His face was so clear in the dream,
but now I can't really recall.
By the way, Eun-ho.
You know the thing I left with you?
Where is it?
What?
My fox bead.
You have it.
Why would I have that?
Wait, do I?
Where did I put it?
Think carefully.
This place is…
So, my bead is here?
Yeah. Why did I keep it here again?
Oh, right. It was because…
Sis, snap out of it.
Don't tell her anything. This is all fake.
"Sis"?
Wait, she's not Geum-ho?
Eun-ho, don't overthink it.
Just tell me where you hid the fox bead--
Sis, can't you hear that voice?
A voice?
Eun-ho, wake up!
Eun-ho.
- Eun-ho.
- Si-yeol?
Eun-ho, come on. Wake up.
I was almost there. What a hassle.
Tell me where you're keeping my fox bead.
It wasn't in that hospital room.
Geum-ho.
So you're saying
there are weird humans after my fox bead?
Yeah, I heard it from Si-yeol's friend.
Now that they know I'm human,
I think they're looking for you.
But even if he is a shaman,
he's still just human.
How dangerous can he be?
I'm not sure, but we should
take precautions just in case.
So, I'm going to hide your fox bead
without telling you where.
How? Whether you keep it
or hide it somewhere,
I'd be able to sense it.
I need to sever your connection
to the bead, just for a while.
You trust me, right?
Eun-ho… Eun-ho!
What am I supposed to do?
The dagger. That should do it.
This is…
It's the only Sajin Ritual Blade
left in the world.
It's a sacred dagger
that can sever and defy fate.
You'll die at this rate.
Wouldn't it be better
to just give me the bead?
Tell him to put it in your hand. Quickly!
- Hurry!
- In my hand?
- In my hand…
- What?
In my hand.
In my hand…
What's wrong?
What's happening? Hey!
- Something's wrong.
- What?
The plan's ruined.
Damn it.
Hey!
Eun-ho.
Are you okay? Are you with me?
- Sis.
- Si-yeol.
Sis, are you okay?
What happened? Why did you suddenly--
It's all over.
What?
We're safe now.
- Calm down!
- Get away!
Get away from me!
I don't have any power left.
Just leave me alone!
Damn it. Just… kill me!
Just leave me alone to die.
What the hell happened?
Please, I was wrong. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault. I was wrong.
Man, cleaning everything up took forever.
Are you sure nothing's missing?
Yeah.
Eun-ho seems pretty shaken up, though.
Of course she is.
The place was trashed
while they were gone.
Anyway, let's get going.
You rest up too, Si-yeol.
You must be pretty shaken.
No, let's head out together.
I need to get groceries
to make her something to eat.
- Sure thing.
- Okay.
Thanks.
That'll be 22,980 won.
Wait… what?
Oh man. I forgot my wallet.
I'm coming, okay?
Who is it at this hour?
What?
And where did Si-yeol go?
Gosh, all right! I'm coming!
What are you doing?
I was thinking about this all wrong.
Forget waiting for my turn.
Let's just end this right now.
What do you think you're doing?
If you're doing this
because you still trust that shaman--
Trust who?
That bastard's barely conscious.
He's just breathing with his eyes open.
He's basically a vegetable.
You guys did that to him!
No. He brought that on himself.
Just like you're doing right now.
I don't care.
I'm not going to end up like that.
This is the way of humans.
Let's see if you can still use
that sorcery of yours
with a hole in your head.
Hey!
You little--
Si-yeol!
Si-yeol…
Si-yeol, why did you do that?
Are you…
Are you okay?
Why are you worrying about me right now?
You're the one who got shot!
This wasn't in the future I saw.
Why is it you instead of me?
He will eventually die.
That's the fate
you gave him.
How can you do this?
After you finally made me human
and made me fall in love with a human,
how could you do this?
Si-yeol.
Si-yeol…
No, Si-yeol… what do I do?
SPECIAL APPEARANCE BY HONG SU-HYEON
NO TAIL TO TELL
- Please, save him.
- You can't come in.
There will come a time
when you must choose.
If Si-yeol just dies like this,
then there's really nothing we can do.
Even if I die, I want to die as myself.
That's my wish.
It's so strange
that the only people left
who remember Eun-ho are you and me.
You need to let go too.
This is the end for me. My final moment.
RIP KANG SI-YEOL
I never once imagined an ending like this.
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim